[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2008-10-23 06:35:47
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayDepth: 0
PlayResX: 1916
PlayResY: 1076
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 2
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H19000000,&H000E0300,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,2,2,134,120,68,1
Style: eng,Microsoft YaHei,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,26,1
Style: Top,微软雅黑,10,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Git,Comic Sans MS,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Chn,微软雅黑,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Eng,Comic Sans MS,60,&H002AF7FF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.20,0:00:11.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm going down to south park\N gonna have myself a time 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.05,0:00:15.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Friendly faces everywhere\N humble folks without temptation 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.33,0:00:18.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Going down to south park\N gonna leave my woes behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.72,0:00:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ample parking day or night\N people shouting howdy neighbor
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.96,0:00:24.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heading on out to south park\N gonna see if I can't unwind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.54,0:00:28.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I like girls with big vaginas\N I like girls with big fat titties
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.61,0:00:31.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.10,0:21:47.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译制作\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}YYeTs人人影视字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.10,0:21:48.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}校译\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}sunflo
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.10,0:21:49.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1c&HFDC282&}后期\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}csbeyond
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.00,0:00:31.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0150,,{\1c&HFDC282&}南方公园  第12季第1集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.00,0:00:31.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0100,,扁桃风波\N{\rEng}Tonsil Trouble
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.28,0:00:36.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,啊\N{\rEng}Aghghghgh.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.88,0:00:39.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,啊\N{\rEng}Aghghghgh.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.00,0:00:41.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,毫无疑问\N{\rEng}Well there's no doubt about it
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.77,0:00:44.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,需要切除扁桃腺\N{\rEng}Those tonsils need to come out.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.30,0:00:45.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.04,0:00:47.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有什么风险吗  医生\N{\rEng}Oh  what exactly does that entail  doctor?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.50,0:00:49.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这只是个很简单的小手术\N{\rEng}It's a very simple operation.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.06,0:00:50.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们会把你麻醉  埃里克\N{\rEng}We'll just put you to sleep  Eric  
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.61,0:00:52.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当你醒过来时扁桃已经不在了\N{\rEng}and when you wake up you'll be tonsil-free!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.64,0:00:53.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,决不\N{\rEng}No way.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.91,0:00:56.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不去医院  妈\N{\rEng}I'm not going to the hospital  mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.21,0:00:58.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你是个勇敢的小孩\N{\rEng}Oh  I thought you were a tough kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.44,0:01:01.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你不会是害怕医院吧\N{\rEng}You're not scared of hospitals  are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.23,0:01:03.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  当然不是\N{\rEng}No  I'm not scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.10,0:01:03.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我只是\N{\rEng}I just  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.77,0:01:05.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不想切除扁桃腺\N{\rEng}I don't want my tonsils out  that's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.81,0:01:07.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那我想你也不想要\N{\rEng}Well  then I guess you don't want all the
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.77,0:01:11.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,手术后的免费冰激凌了\N{\rEng}ice cream you get after the surgery either.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.75,0:01:12.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,冰激凌\N{\rEng}Ice cream?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.02,0:01:14.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真可惜  冰激凌\N{\rEng}Be a shame to have to
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.27,0:01:15.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,只好给那些\N{\rEng}give all that free ice cream
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.47,0:01:16.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不害怕医院的\N{\rEng}to the big boys who aren't
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.80,0:01:18.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大孩子们了\N{\rEng}scared of the hospitals.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.83,0:01:19.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样\N{\rEng}What do you say  champ?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.67,0:01:21.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你能坚持做手术了吗\N{\rEng}Think you can tough it out?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.20,0:01:25.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你确认有免费的冰激凌\N{\rEng}Well  you did say free ice cream?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.61,0:01:35.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小可爱  醒醒\N{\rEng}Poopsiekins  wake up.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.58,0:01:37.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,醒醒  小宝贝\N{\rEng}Wake up  honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.71,0:01:40.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,结  结束了\N{\rEng}It's  it's over?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.51,0:01:42.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  你做到了 小可爱\N{\rEng}That's right!You did it  poopsiekins!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.98,0:01:44.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,结束了\N{\rEng}It's over!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.30,0:01:45.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我什么感觉也没有\N{\rEng}I didn't feel anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.63,0:01:46.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你说的对  妈妈\N{\rEng}You were right  mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.90,0:01:48.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我真为你骄傲  埃里克\N{\rEng}I'm so proud of you  Eric.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.99,0:01:51.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  我的冰激凌在哪儿\N{\rEng}All right. So where's my ice cream?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.22,0:01:53.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,医生来了\N{\rEng}Oh  here's the doctor now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.58,0:01:54.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你好  医生\N{\rEng}Hi  doctor.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.59,0:01:55.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对  医生\N{\rEng}You were right  doctor.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.17,0:01:58.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一切顺利\N{\rEng}Everything is okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.88,0:02:00.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  不太顺利\N{\rEng}No  it's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.37,0:02:02.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  恐怕我们意外地\N{\rEng}Eric  i'm afraid that we've accidentally
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.47,0:02:05.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让你感染上了艾滋病毒\N{\rEng}infected you with AIDS virus
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.49,0:02:08.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.47,0:02:09.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么意思\N{\rEng}What's that supposed to mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.59,0:02:11.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在做扁桃腺手术时\N{\rEng}During the tonsil surgery we had
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.27,0:02:13.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们给你输了血\N{\rEng}to supply you with donor blood  
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.14,0:02:14.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,中间出了点错  给你输\N{\rEng}a mistake was made and you were given
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.27,0:02:16.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,了感染有艾滋病毒的血液\N{\rEng}blood contaminated with HIV.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.93,0:02:19.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是个十亿分之一的意外\N{\rEng}It was a one in a billion fluke.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.80,0:02:21.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我得了艾滋\N{\rEng}I have AIDS?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.31,0:02:23.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还没有  但是我们确认\N{\rEng}Not yet  but we've confirmed that you
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.14,0:02:25.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你成为了艾滋带菌者\N{\rEng}now have the virus that causes AIDS.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.77,0:02:28.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们非常抱歉\N{\rEng}We are very sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.10,0:02:29.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\rEng}Sorry?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.31,0:02:30.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们让我感染上艾滋\N{\rEng}You gave me AIDS
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.06,0:02:31.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,然后说你们很抱歉\N{\rEng}and you're sorry?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.09,0:02:33.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我可怜的小宝贝\N{\rEng}Oh  my poor little baby!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.38,0:02:34.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,妈  你说过不会有什么问题的\N{\rEng}Mom  you said nothing would go wrong!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.82,0:02:36.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\rEng}Oh  god!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.29,0:02:37.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\rEng}Oh  no!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.69,0:02:39.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不 不  这只是玩笑  对吧\N{\rEng}No  no  this is a joke  right?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.47,0:02:41.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这只是玩笑  我不可能得艾滋\N{\rEng}This is a joke!I can't have AIDS!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.54,0:02:42.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们会尽我们的全力\N{\rEng}We are going to do everything in our
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.93,0:02:45.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来补偿你  埃里克\N{\rEng}power to make this up to you  Eric.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.16,0:02:46.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,作为开头\N{\rEng}For starters  
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.23,0:02:48.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是我欠你的冰激凌\N{\rEng}I think I owe you some ice cream!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.56,0:02:52.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,去你妈的冰激凌\N{\rEng}Fuck your ice cream!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.40,0:02:54.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你说过我会没事的\N{\rEng}You said I'd be fine!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.13,0:02:55.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们都说过我会没事的\N{\rEng}You all said I'd be fine!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.68,0:03:01.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的宝贝感染了艾滋\N{\rEng}My baby has HIV!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.28,0:03:05.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\rEng}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.55,0:03:10.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢各位的到来\N{\rEng}Thank you for coming  everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.35,0:03:12.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们  请坐下\N{\rEng}Boys  please take a seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.86,0:03:15.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,出什么事了  我们有麻烦吗\N{\rEng}What's going on?Are we in trouble?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.89,0:03:18.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们  之所以叫你们来\N{\rEng}Boys  the reason we called you all in is
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.24,0:03:20.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是因为你们一个朋友\N{\rEng}because one of your friends
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.34,0:03:22.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,患了重病\N{\rEng}has a serious illness.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.47,0:03:26.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克·卡特曼被诊断患了艾滋\N{\rEng}Eric Cartman has been diagnosed with HIV.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.35,0:03:29.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.34,0:03:30.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,噢  不\N{\rEng}Oh  no.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.26,0:03:31.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,自从那次惹祸的输血后\N{\rEng}He's been to several specialists
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.52,0:03:33.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他已经看了好些专家了\N{\rEng}since a botched blood transfusion.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.46,0:03:34.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他携带的病毒还处于早期\N{\rEng}The disease is in very early stages
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.89,0:03:36.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是完全可以控制的\N{\rEng}and completely manageable  
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.62,0:03:38.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当然他很自然地感到害怕\N{\rEng}but he's naturally  a bit scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.98,0:03:41.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,卡特曼得了艾滋病\N{\rEng}Cartman has HIV?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.68,0:03:43.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要每个人都明白\N{\rEng}We need everyone to understand that
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.33,0:03:45.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们是不会被埃里克传染的\N{\rEng}you can't get the virus from Eric.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.36,0:03:47.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们依然可以拥抱甚至亲吻他\N{\rEng}You can still give him hugs and even kisses.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.64,0:03:48.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要害怕他  只是\N{\rEng}Don't be afraid of him. Just -
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.63,0:03:50.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\rEng}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.06,0:03:52.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克·卡特曼得了艾滋\N{\rEng}Eric Cartman has HIV.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.64,0:03:55.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  我现在叫埃里克进来\N{\rEng}All right  we're going to bring Eric in now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.86,0:03:58.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让我们都来全力支持他\N{\rEng}And let's all be as supportive as we can
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.33,0:04:01.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,爱护他  好吗\N{\rEng}and show him lots of love  okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.99,0:04:03.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  进来\N{\rEng}Eric?Come on in.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.49,0:04:06.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你的朋友们都想向你问好  好嘛\N{\rEng}Your friends all want to say hi  m'kay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.88,0:04:10.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你好 埃里克  -好啊 埃里克\N{\rEng}- Hi  Eric.  - Hey  there  Eric.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.13,0:04:13.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不可能\N{\rEng}No way.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.07,0:04:14.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么样  埃里克\N{\rEng}How you doing  Eric?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.59,0:04:15.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗\N{\rEng}You know
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.60,0:04:17.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我认为你非常特别\N{\rEng}I think you're a real special little guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.84,0:04:19.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,即使你得了艾滋\N{\rEng}And even though you have AIDS  
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.53,0:04:21.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我也不会对你另眼相看\N{\rEng}i ain't gonna act any different towards you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.15,0:04:27.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,该死  这太他妈的恶心了\N{\rEng}God dammit  this sucks ass!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.13,0:04:29.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\rEng}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.11,0:04:31.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我  我需要离开一会\N{\rEng}I  I have to step out for a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.25,0:04:44.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,可怜的凯尔\N{\rEng}Poor kyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.41,0:04:46.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他很难接受这个事实\N{\rEng}He's really taking it hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.50,0:04:48.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔是在外面笑吗\N{\rEng}Is kyle laughing out there?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.18,0:04:49.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这不是玩笑\N{\rEng}This isn't time for funny jokes!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.58,0:04:50.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我会死的\N{\rEng}I'm going to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.61,0:04:52.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你不会死的  埃里克\N{\rEng}Now  you're not going to die  Eric.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.52,0:04:54.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋不像以前那样大不了了\N{\rEng}AIDS isn't as big a deal as it used to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.68,0:04:55.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在在治疗上已经有了进步\N{\rEng}There are advances in treatment.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.94,0:04:57.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没什么大不了\N{\rEng}Not a big deal?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.11,0:04:58.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都这么认为吗\N{\rEng}Is that how everyone feels?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.45,0:04:59.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,人们需要明白\N{\rEng}People need to understand
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.50,0:05:01.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋的严重性\N{\rEng}the seriousness of this illness
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.03,0:05:01.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,以及与之抗争的人\N{\rEng}and the bravery of the
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.95,0:05:03.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是多么勇敢\N{\rEng}people who struggle with it!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.47,0:05:07.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,希尔顿酒店\N{\rEng}艾尔顿·约翰为埃里克·卡特曼艾滋筹款慈善会
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.73,0:05:08.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,今晚我们在这里\N{\rEng}We are here tonight
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.78,0:05:10.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,向一个患有\N{\rEng}to salute the bravery and the courage
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.68,0:05:12.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋病的男孩\N{\rEng}of one very special little boy
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.58,0:05:14.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,的勇气致敬\N{\rEng}who is living with HIV
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.16,0:05:18.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大家究竟跑哪儿去了\N{\rEng}Where the hell is everybody?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.02,0:05:20.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我们不是应该\N{\rEng}Excuse me. Shouldn't we wait for
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.60,0:05:22.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等到人到齐了再开始吗\N{\rEng}everyone to arrive before we get started?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.63,0:05:24.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这就是所有人了\N{\rEng}This is everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.21,0:05:26.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们只卖出这么多票\N{\rEng}We didn't sell that many tickets.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.24,0:05:27.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很棒的慈善会  埃里克\N{\rEng}Great benefit  Eric.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.49,0:05:30.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,意大利肉丸子很棒\N{\rEng}The italian meatballs are fantastic.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.59,0:05:31.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,只有这么多人\N{\rEng}So this is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.68,0:05:33.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想艾滋慈善会\N{\rEng}I'm afraid AIDS benefits aren't
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.30,0:05:35.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没有以前那样流行了\N{\rEng}as popular as they used to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.03,0:05:37.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋更像是80/90年代的病毒\N{\rEng}Aids was more the '80s/'90s disease.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.21,0:05:38.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在都关心癌症了\N{\rEng}It's all about cancer now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.85,0:05:40.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真是太好了\N{\rEng}Well  that's just great!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.42,0:05:41.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我挑了一个大家对它\N{\rEng}Of all the times to get AIDS  I get it
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.83,0:05:43.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,最不以为然的时间患上艾滋\N{\rEng}right when everyone stops giving a crap!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.35,0:05:45.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,通过大家的帮助\N{\rEng}With all of your help
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.47,0:05:49.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,今晚我们筹到了超过17美元\N{\rEng}we have raised over $17 for aids tonight  
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.30,0:05:50.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这些钱毫无疑问会用于\N{\rEng}and that money will certainly go
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.94,0:05:53.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,帮助埃里克·马特曼\N{\rEng}towards helping little Eric Martman.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.51,0:05:56.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快把艾尔顿·约翰叫出来\N{\rEng}Just bring out Elton John already!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.09,0:05:58.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉\N{\rEng}Uh  we're sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.06,0:05:59.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾尔顿来不了\N{\rEng}Elton couldn't make it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.29,0:06:01.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他去了一个癌症慈善会\N{\rEng}He had to play at a cancer benefit.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.48,0:06:03.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是没关系  我们有更好的人选\N{\rEng}It's all right. We got somebody better.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.63,0:06:05.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吉米·布菲特\N{\rEng}[译注:美国60年代著名的歌手]
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.67,0:06:07.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吉米·布菲特\N{\rEng}Jimmy Buffet?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.03,0:06:08.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大家好\N{\rEng}Hello  everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.33,0:06:11.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我写了一首歌给这个勇敢的男孩\N{\rEng}I wrote this song for a very brave little boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.18,0:06:15.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*天堂里的艾滋汉堡*\N{\rEng}*AIDS burger in paradise*
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.73,0:06:18.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*艾滋汉堡  不是太好*\N{\rEng}*AIDS burger and it ain't nice*
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.76,0:06:20.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,除了南方的\N{\rEng}Nobody likes Jimmy Buffet except for
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.31,0:06:21.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟会男孩和酒鬼女孩\N{\rEng}frat boys and alcoholic chicks
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.71,0:06:22.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没人喜欢吉米·布菲特\N{\rEng}from the south!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.13,0:06:25.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*南方公园的小男孩*\N{\rEng}*Little boy in South Park*
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.35,0:06:28.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*身患艾滋  在寒冷和黑暗中等死*\N{\rEng}*dying of AIDS in the cold dark*
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.05,0:06:31.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我不知道他怎么患上艾滋的*\N{\rEng}*how he got AIDS I haven't a clue*
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.47,0:06:35.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*因为艾滋日渐消瘦*\N{\rEng}*wasting away again because of AIDS*
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.97,0:06:37.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大家今晚开心吗\N{\rEng}how're we all feeling tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.97,0:06:39.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,去你妈的  吉米·布菲特\N{\rEng}Fuck you  Jimmy Buffet!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.28,0:06:40.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你真他妈的逊\N{\rEng}You fuckin' suck!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.62,0:06:42.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小可爱  温柔一点\N{\rEng}Oh  poopsiekins  be nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.91,0:06:44.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,去你的  妈  我他妈的得了艾滋\N{\rEng}Fuck you  mom. I have fuckin' AIDS!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.06,0:06:50.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们\N{\rEng}Hey  guys  
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.70,0:06:51.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,多谢昨天来参加\N{\rEng}thanks a lot for coming to
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.80,0:06:53.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的艾滋慈善会\N{\rEng}my AIDS benefit yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.73,0:06:57.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  那是昨天啊  我们忘了\N{\rEng}Oh  dude  was that yesterday?We forgot.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.20,0:06:58.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  你们忘了\N{\rEng}Yeah  you forgot.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.29,0:06:59.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就像最近很多人忘了\N{\rEng}Just like a lot of people lately have
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.47,0:07:01.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋仍然致命\N{\rEng}forgot that AIDS is still killing people.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.64,0:07:03.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,似乎全美国都忘了\N{\rEng}Seems like all of America has forgot
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.56,0:07:05.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋是一个严重的疾病\N{\rEng}that HIV is a serious disease.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.49,0:07:08.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾尔顿·约翰给你唱歌了吗\N{\rEng}Well  did Elton John sing a song for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.19,0:07:10.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没有  事实上\N{\rEng}No  as a matter of fact
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.21,0:07:12.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来的是吉米·布菲特\N{\rEng}Jimmy Buffet came instead.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.97,0:07:14.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\rEng}Oh  yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.54,0:07:16.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真他妈好笑啊  凯尔\N{\rEng}It's real fuckin' Funny  Kyle!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.36,0:07:19.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\rEng}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.61,0:07:21.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我真的\N{\rEng}I'm - really!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.06,0:07:22.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,卡特曼  我真的替你难过\N{\rEng}Cartman  I feel really bad for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.84,0:07:23.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真心的\N{\rEng}Honestly.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.61,0:07:25.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-不  你没有  -我有\N{\rEng}- No  you don'T.  - I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.24,0:07:26.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果你真的替我难过\N{\rEng}If you really felt bad
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.19,0:07:28.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你就不会笑成他妈的那样了\N{\rEng}you'd wipe that fuckin' smirk off your face!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.06,0:07:31.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我随时都可能死翘翘  凯尔\N{\rEng}Well  any god dammed second  Kyle!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.48,0:07:33.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我要回家了\N{\rEng}I'm sorry. I gotta get home.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.63,0:07:38.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上帝  居然有这种混蛋\N{\rEng}Jesus Christ  can you believe that asshole?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.91,0:07:40.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他真的替你难过  卡特曼\N{\rEng}He does feel bad for you  Cartman.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.24,0:07:41.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他只是觉得很\N{\rEng}He just thinks it'S...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.48,0:07:42.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很讽刺\N{\rEng}ironic.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.43,0:07:43.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么讽刺\N{\rEng}Ironic how?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.32,0:07:44.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你从来\N{\rEng}Well  you know you're always
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.12,0:07:44.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,都是个混蛋\N{\rEng}such a dick and stuff
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.92,0:07:45.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在却\N{\rEng}and now -
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.45,0:07:46.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,却怎么样  我罪有应得\N{\rEng}Oh  and what  I deserve it?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.63,0:07:47.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们是这样想的\N{\rEng}Is that what you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.77,0:07:48.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不是\N{\rEng}Not me!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.59,0:07:50.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他也许是这样想的\N{\rEng}That's kind of what he thinks.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.27,0:07:51.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没人应得艾滋  斯坦\N{\rEng}Nobody deserves this illness  Stan!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.91,0:07:52.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼\N{\rEng}Kenny!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.73,0:07:53.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没人\N{\rEng}Nobody!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.64,0:07:54.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这非常糟糕\N{\rEng}It's awful!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.48,0:07:56.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也许应该给凯尔\N{\rEng}And maybe somebody needs to teach Kyle
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.22,0:07:58.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上一门同情他人的课\N{\rEng}how to have some compassion.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.32,0:08:10.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\rEng}Ugh  okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.60,0:08:11.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没有情况\N{\rEng}It's clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.69,0:08:14.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好  准备好绳子吊我上去\N{\rEng}All right. Get that rope ready to hoist me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.29,0:08:17.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好的  但是你准备做什么\N{\rEng}All right  but what are you going to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.47,0:08:19.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔觉得艾滋很有趣\N{\rEng}Kyle thinks that HIV is funny  
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.11,0:08:20.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们就来让他变得有趣\N{\rEng}so we're going to make him look funny
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.74,0:08:21.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,然后他才会知道\N{\rEng}and then he'll know how it feels
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.81,0:08:23.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,被嘲笑的滋味\N{\rEng}to be laughed at.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.35,0:08:25.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我是不是\N{\rEng}I just  I don't know that I should be
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.23,0:08:27.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,该帮你来捉弄凯尔\N{\rEng}helping you make Kyle look silly.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.63,0:08:29.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  帮助艾滋病患者\N{\rEng}Butters  helping people who have AIDS
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.56,0:08:30.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是世界上最重要的\N{\rEng}is one of the most important things
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.76,0:08:31.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,事情之一\N{\rEng}you can do.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.17,0:08:33.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  但是你确定\N{\rEng}I know  but are you sure
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.46,0:08:35.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔需要接受教训\N{\rEng}Kyle has to be taught a lesson?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.49,0:08:37.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不仅确定  巴特斯\N{\rEng}I'm not just sure  Butters.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.28,0:08:39.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我是艾滋确定\N{\rEng}[译注:英文阳性也有确定的意思]
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.58,0:08:41.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对  我想你是对的\N{\rEng}Oh  yeah. I guess that's true.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.21,0:08:43.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那好  把绳子缠到窗子\N{\rEng}All right. Now get the rope up over
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.28,0:08:44.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上面第三根窗椽上\N{\rEng}that third rafter above the window.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.31,0:08:45.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是最轻松的通道\N{\rEng}That's the easiest access.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.55,0:08:47.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你真是熟门熟路啊\N{\rEng}Wow!You really know what you're doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.31,0:08:49.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我经常潜入凯尔的房间\N{\rEng}Yeah  I sneak into Kyle's room lots of times.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.79,0:09:04.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得艾滋是可以\N{\rEng}You think HIV is something to be
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.05,0:09:05.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,嘲笑的吗  凯尔\N{\rEng}laughed at  Kyle?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.58,0:09:08.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我们就来看看\N{\rEng}Well  let's just see
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.47,0:09:11.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,到底有多好笑  混蛋\N{\rEng}how funny it is now  asshole.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.05,0:09:32.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了 好了  小傻瓜  没事的\N{\rEng}There  there  boobie. You'll be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.48,0:09:35.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,医生  有什么问题  链球菌感染吗\N{\rEng}Doctor  did you find anything?Is it strep?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.48,0:09:38.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是链球菌感染\N{\rEng}No  it isn't strep.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.68,0:09:40.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那太好了\N{\rEng}Oh  well  that's a relief.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.06,0:09:42.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,布罗夫洛夫斯基太太\N{\rEng}Mrs. Broflovski  
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.18,0:09:45.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你儿子以前输过血吗\N{\rEng}has your son ever had a blood transfusion?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.21,0:09:46.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没有  为什么问\N{\rEng}No  why?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.95,0:09:47.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小男孩\N{\rEng}Little boy  
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.78,0:09:49.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你尝试过\N{\rEng}have you been having
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.28,0:09:50.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,未使用安全套的肛交吗\N{\rEng}unprotected anal sex?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.81,0:09:52.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么  没有\N{\rEng}What?No!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.12,0:09:54.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,医生  你在说什么啊\N{\rEng}Doctor  what are you saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.39,0:09:56.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们进行了所有可能的测试\N{\rEng}We've run every test imaginable.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.82,0:10:00.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔感染上了艾滋病毒\N{\rEng}Little Kyle here is infected with HIV
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.61,0:10:02.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -艾滋病毒\N{\rEng}- What?  - Hiv?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.61,0:10:04.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们用了很长时间来确认\N{\rEng}It took us a long time to narrow it down  
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.46,0:10:05.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不会有错的\N{\rEng}but there is no doubt.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.49,0:10:06.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  那怎么可能\N{\rEng}No!That's impossible!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.02,0:10:08.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小男孩  你确定你真的\N{\rEng}Little boy  are you sure you haven't
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.60,0:10:10.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一次也没有尝试过吗\N{\rEng}taken it up the hoo-hoo just once or twice?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.64,0:10:12.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没有  该死  没有\N{\rEng}No!No  god dammit!No!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.79,0:10:13.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉你你错了\N{\rEng}I'm telling you you're wrong!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.65,0:10:15.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不可能感染艾滋\N{\rEng}There is no way I can have HIV.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.27,0:10:16.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,除非也许\N{\rEng}unless maybe...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.08,0:10:18.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\rEng}oh  my god.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.26,0:10:20.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那个婊子养的\N{\rEng}That son of a bitch!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.35,0:10:23.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  凯尔\N{\rEng}Kyle?Kyle!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.12,0:10:26.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,把球传给我\N{\rEng}Pass me the ball.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.11,0:10:29.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,把球传给我  克雷格  你这个蠢货\N{\rEng}Pass me the ball  Craig  you stupid asshole!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.86,0:10:34.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  你他妈干什么\N{\rEng}Kyle  what the F
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.05,0:10:35.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我要杀了你  卡特曼\N{\rEng}I'm gonna kill you  Cartman!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.34,0:10:36.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  什么事情\N{\rEng}Kyle  what?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.49,0:10:37.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他做了什么\N{\rEng}What'd he do?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.58,0:10:39.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么会感染艾滋\N{\rEng}Why do I have HIV?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.86,0:10:41.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,噢\N{\rEng}Ooooh.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.53,0:10:43.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你也得了艾滋  凯尔\N{\rEng}Ooohhhh  you have HIV  huh  Kyle?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.83,0:10:45.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想现在没那么有趣了  是吧\N{\rEng}Guess it isn't so to funny now  is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.52,0:10:47.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-你干了什么  -什么也没干\N{\rEng}- What did you do? - Nothing
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.14,0:10:48.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么巴特斯说上周五晚上\N{\rEng}Then why did Butters say he helped you
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.44,0:10:50.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他帮助了你潜入我的房间\N{\rEng}sneak into my room last friday night?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.47,0:10:52.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,干得好  巴特斯  你个大嘴巴\N{\rEng}Oh  nice  Butters  you big tattle tail!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.51,0:10:53.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大嘴巴\N{\rEng}Tattle tail?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.61,0:10:55.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这样做的严重性吗\N{\rEng}Do you know how serious this is?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.30,0:10:57.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔 也许我只是在证明\N{\rEng}Well  Kyle  maybe I was just trying to prove
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.63,0:10:59.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔\N{\rEng}Kyle!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.24,0:11:04.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  嘿  够了\N{\rEng}Hey  hey  that's enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.94,0:11:06.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,住手   好嘛\N{\rEng}Break it up  m'kay?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.61,0:11:07.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,住手\N{\rEng}Break it up!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.71,0:11:08.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好嘛\N{\rEng}M'kay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.84,0:11:14.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  孩子们\N{\rEng}All right  boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.74,0:11:17.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为什么打架\N{\rEng}Now what is this fighting all about?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.32,0:11:19.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他把艾滋传染给我\N{\rEng}He gave me AIDS!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.06,0:11:20.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.88,0:11:23.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他故意地把艾滋传染给我\N{\rEng}He purposely infected me with his HIV virus!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.58,0:11:26.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是真的吗埃里克  你传染艾滋给凯尔\N{\rEng}Is that true  Eric?Did you give Kyle AIDS?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.24,0:11:27.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他是个混蛋\N{\rEng}Well  he was being a total dick
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.67,0:11:28.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还是个大嘴巴\N{\rEng}and then he's a big tattle tail and
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.69,0:11:29.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,到处说我的坏话\N{\rEng}going around talking crap about me -
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.92,0:11:32.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你传染艾滋给凯尔\N{\rEng}Did you infect Kyle with the HIV virus?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.43,0:11:34.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是还是不是\N{\rEng}Yes or no?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.61,0:11:37.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧\N{\rEng}Kind of.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.13,0:11:39.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  这样做可不地道\N{\rEng}Eric  that is not appropriate behavior
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.90,0:11:41.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你不能故意地\N{\rEng}You cannot purposely
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.21,0:11:43.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,传播病毒给其他小孩\N{\rEng}infect other kids with your disease.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.04,0:11:43.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,说得对\N{\rEng}That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.97,0:11:46.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想你应该向凯尔道歉\N{\rEng}I think you owe kyle an apology.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.89,0:11:48.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\rEng}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.11,0:11:49.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,道歉\N{\rEng}An apology?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.26,0:11:51.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么道歉  埃里克\N{\rEng}You're sory for what  Eric!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.36,0:11:53.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对不起我传染艾滋给你  凯尔\N{\rEng}I'm sorry for giving you AIDS  Kyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.84,0:11:54.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这样好多了\N{\rEng}That's better.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.86,0:11:56.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在  凯尔  你也许也应该\N{\rEng}And now  Kyle  maybe you should also
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.62,0:11:59.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,承认你不应该背后说坏话\N{\rEng}admit you were wrong for tattling.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.29,0:12:01.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.07,0:12:03.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  背后说坏话是\N{\rEng}Kyle  the thing about tattling is that
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.07,0:12:04.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很不好的\N{\rEng}tattling's bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.30,0:12:07.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,因为没人喜欢搬弄是非的人\N{\rEng}Because nobody likes a tattle tail
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.04,0:12:09.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,搬弄是非  他把艾滋传染给了我\N{\rEng}A tattle tail he infected me with AIDS!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.74,0:12:10.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看到了嘛  他又在搬弄是非\N{\rEng}See?He's tattling again.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.98,0:12:13.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他一点也没有吸取教训\N{\rEng}He hasn't learned a thing  you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.17,0:12:17.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  我想我们扯平了\N{\rEng}Well  Kyle  I guess we're even now.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.67,0:12:19.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们言和吧\N{\rEng}Should we just call it a truce?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.33,0:12:22.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  我们言和吧\N{\rEng}Kyle  should we call it even-stevens now?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.93,0:12:25.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  你要到哪儿去\N{\rEng}Kyle  where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.25,0:12:28.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我要去把你\N{\rEng}I am going to break
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.99,0:12:31.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所有东西砸烂\N{\rEng}everything that you own.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.44,0:12:36.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是干什么  凯尔  别\N{\rEng}What is that supposed to mean Kyle  no!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.32,0:12:38.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我道过歉了  凯尔\N{\rEng}I apologized  Kyle!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.19,0:12:41.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔\N{\rEng}Kyle!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.13,0:12:42.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  住手  你这个混蛋\N{\rEng}Kyle  hold on  you asshole.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.28,0:12:51.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈的在干什么\N{\rEng}What the fuck are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.15,0:12:53.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  住手\N{\rEng}Kyle  stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.84,0:12:56.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,该死的  不要\N{\rEng}God dammit don't
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.67,0:13:00.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  凯尔  不要碰克莱德青蛙\N{\rEng}no Kyle  not the Clyde frog
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.26,0:13:01.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,放下克莱德青蛙\N{\rEng}leave Clyde frog alone
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.31,0:13:03.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\rEng}no
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.10,0:13:05.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,克莱德青蛙\N{\rEng}ah Clyde Frog
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.62,0:13:08.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不要摔x-box\N{\rEng}no no not the X-box
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.06,0:13:10.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要摔x-box  停  等一下\N{\rEng}not that x-box  wait   just wait a second
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.72,0:13:12.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对不起我传染了艾滋给你\N{\rEng}I'm sorry I gave you HIV alright?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.02,0:13:15.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是给我一个机会让我治愈你\N{\rEng}Just give me a chance and I can cure you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.56,0:13:17.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,根本就没有治疗方法  混蛋\N{\rEng}There is no cure  you asshole!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.40,0:13:18.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  听着  凯尔\N{\rEng}No!No  listen  kyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.65,0:13:19.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我在研究一些东西\N{\rEng}I'm onto something.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.87,0:13:21.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真的还有希望\N{\rEng}There really is a hope.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.05,0:13:22.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么希望\N{\rEng}What hope?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.46,0:13:23.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你要是摔了我的x-box\N{\rEng}Break my xbox
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.37,0:13:24.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就永远也不要想知道了\N{\rEng}and you'll never know.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.70,0:13:25.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你在撒谎\N{\rEng}You're lying.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.89,0:13:28.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没有  好吧凯尔  魔术师约翰逊  凯尔\N{\rEng}[译注:80年代NBA球星  艾滋带菌者]
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.30,0:13:29.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,答案是魔术师约翰逊\N{\rEng}The key is Magic Johnson!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.91,0:13:30.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,魔术师约翰逊\N{\rEng}Magic Johnson?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.96,0:13:32.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他曾是篮球运动员\N{\rEng}He was a basketball player.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.54,0:13:33.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,又怎么样\N{\rEng}So what?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.50,0:13:35.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他N年前就感染上了艾滋病毒\N{\rEng}So he got HIV like 50 years ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.76,0:13:37.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是现在依然没事\N{\rEng}He's still totally fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.17,0:13:39.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,魔术师约翰逊有某种\N{\rEng}Magic Johnson has some kind of
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.27,0:13:40.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋的抗体\N{\rEng}resistance to the virus  kyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.50,0:13:42.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我从被感染开始就在研究\N{\rEng}I've been researching it since i got infected.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.55,0:13:43.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们找到他\N{\rEng}If we can track him down and
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.76,0:13:45.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,分离出他的基因标本\N{\rEng}iisolate his genetic prototype  
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.49,0:13:46.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们有机会\N{\rEng}we have a chance of
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.32,0:13:47.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,战胜艾滋  伙计\N{\rEng}beating this thing  buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.65,0:13:48.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你和我  凯尔\N{\rEng}You and me  Kyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.71,0:13:49.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们能战胜疾病\N{\rEng}We can overcome our illness.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.69,0:13:51.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我向你发誓\N{\rEng}I swear it to you!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.16,0:13:54.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你最好记住\N{\rEng}You better.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.12,0:13:56.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果你找不到治疗艾滋的方法\N{\rEng}Because if you don't the cure for HIV
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.21,0:13:58.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我会砸了你的x-box的\N{\rEng}I will break your xbox.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.15,0:14:01.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的天啊\N{\rEng}My god.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.78,0:14:07.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要两张去洛杉矶的机票\N{\rEng}We need two tickets to Los Angeles  
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.42,0:14:08.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,越快越好\N{\rEng}as soon as possible!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.99,0:14:10.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,洛杉矶  好的\N{\rEng}Los Angeles  okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.42,0:14:12.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有2点的航班\N{\rEng}Uh  I have a 2:00 flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.45,0:14:15.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,每人400元\N{\rEng}That would be $400 each.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.62,0:14:17.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,先生  你没明白\N{\rEng}Uh  sir  you don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.23,0:14:19.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要马上见魔术师约翰逊\N{\rEng}We have to see Magic Johnson right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.40,0:14:22.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们患了艾滋\N{\rEng}You see we have AIDS.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.38,0:14:24.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋\N{\rEng}AIDS?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.93,0:14:28.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那可真  复古\N{\rEng}Wow!That's really retro.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.57,0:14:30.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是我很抱歉\N{\rEng}But i'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.48,0:14:32.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不能随便提供免费机票\N{\rEng}I can't just give away free seats.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.89,0:14:34.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你还没明白\N{\rEng}Don't you get it?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.16,0:14:36.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们是一对受病痛折磨的伙伴\N{\rEng}We are two pals  afflicted with an illness and
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.49,0:14:37.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,相依相伴\N{\rEng}who only have each other
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.18,0:14:38.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,同时间赛跑\N{\rEng}in a race against time!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.52,0:14:40.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,被绝症无缘无故摧残的\N{\rEng}Innocent  playful children who were
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.02,0:14:42.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,纯真顽皮的孩子\N{\rEng}stricken with a deadly disease for no reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.05,0:14:43.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,算了吧  无缘无故\N{\rEng}Oh  please!No reason!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.00,0:14:45.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的艾滋是他传染的\N{\rEng}I got AIDS from him!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.54,0:14:49.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,噢  你们两是"那个"  是吧\N{\rEng}Oooh  you boys are like that  huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.79,0:14:50.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不是\N{\rEng}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.87,0:14:53.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们确定真的没钱吗\N{\rEng}Are you sure you don't just have any cash?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.84,0:14:56.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不仅确定  我们是艾滋确定\N{\rEng}We're not just sure  we're HIV positive.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.13,0:14:58.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们有时为癌症病人\N{\rEng}Uh  we sometimes offer free seats
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.73,0:15:00.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,提供免费机票\N{\rEng}to cancer patients  
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.03,0:15:02.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是艾滋病人  嘿  米奇\N{\rEng}but AIDS   I just - hey  Mitch?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.76,0:15:05.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们有对艾滋病人的免费政策吗\N{\rEng}Do we have any AIDS patient policies?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.66,0:15:06.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,算了\N{\rEng}Forget it  all right!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.43,0:15:08.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们去另一家航空公司\N{\rEng}We'll use another airline!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.01,0:15:09.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一家真正关心我们的\N{\rEng}One that cares!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.54,0:15:13.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴为你们提供舱位\N{\rEng}We're so happy to help accommodate
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.36,0:15:14.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,勇敢的孩子们\N{\rEng}you brave boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.40,0:15:16.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们说你们得了\N{\rEng}What kind of cancer did
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.19,0:15:17.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么癌症来着\N{\rEng}you say you have again?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.22,0:15:19.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的  全身癌\N{\rEng}Oh  uh  you know  all-over cancer.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.44,0:15:20.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真是抱歉\N{\rEng}I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.95,0:15:22.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,至少好过\N{\rEng}Yeah  well  at least it's not as bad
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.39,0:15:23.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,得艾滋\N{\rEng}as having AIDS!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.62,0:15:25.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋是最糟糕的病\N{\rEng}AIDS is the worst disease.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.23,0:15:26.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  不过现在\N{\rEng}Hmm  I don't know  these days
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.95,0:15:28.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我情愿得艾滋而不是癌症\N{\rEng}I think I'd rather have AIDS than cancer.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.98,0:15:29.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  你会\N{\rEng}No  you would -
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.94,0:15:31.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,听着  你不是应该给客人\N{\rEng}look  shouldn't you be serving people
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.22,0:15:32.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,端茶送水吗  不要呆在这儿了\N{\rEng}drinks or something?Get outta here!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.02,0:15:35.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们上路了  伙计\N{\rEng}We're on our way  buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.67,0:15:37.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,魔术师约翰逊  我们来了\N{\rEng}Magic Johnson  here we come!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.28,0:15:39.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要碰我\N{\rEng}Don't touch me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.47,0:15:42.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我明白  我也害怕\N{\rEng}I know. I'm scared too.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.74,0:15:51.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,魔术师  魔术师\N{\rEng}Magic  Magic  
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.19,0:15:52.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,能到前面来一下吗\N{\rEng}could you come to the front for a minute?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.05,0:15:54.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有两个男孩要见你\N{\rEng}There are a couple of boys here to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.03,0:15:56.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,两个勇敢\N{\rEng}Two  brave little buddies
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.71,0:15:57.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,与命运抗争\N{\rEng}who against all odds have
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.71,0:15:58.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,跨越了整个美国\N{\rEng}journeyed across America
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.71,0:16:00.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来寻找艾滋治疗方法的男孩\N{\rEng}to find the cure for AIDS.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.44,0:16:01.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们互相依靠\N{\rEng}All they have is each other
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.22,0:16:03.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,同时间赛跑\N{\rEng}in a race against time.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.69,0:16:08.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你见我们  约翰逊先生\N{\rEng}Thank you for seeing us  Mr. Johnson.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.48,0:16:09.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们希望\N{\rEng}We were just hoping that
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.70,0:16:10.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也许你有什么关键性的\N{\rEng}maybe you have some kind of
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.90,0:16:12.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,东西可以帮助我们对抗病毒\N{\rEng}key that could help us with our disease.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.49,0:16:16.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们两都感染了病毒  确定吗\N{\rEng}You boys both have the virus?Are you sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.29,0:16:19.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不仅确定  我们是艾滋确定\N{\rEng}We're not just sure  we're HIV positive.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.27,0:16:22.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你能不要再那样说了吗\N{\rEng}Will you stop it with that?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.39,0:16:24.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得这很有趣吗\N{\rEng}What part of this is funny to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.89,0:16:26.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  我们需要找到\N{\rEng}Kyle  we need to try to find -
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.07,0:16:27.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,感染上一个绝症\N{\rEng}What part of being infected with a
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.43,0:16:29.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有什么有趣的\N{\rEng}deadly disease do you find funny?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.01,0:16:31.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不认为那有趣  凯尔\N{\rEng}I don't think it's funny  Kyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.96,0:16:32.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那就不要再说\N{\rEng}Then stop saying
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.99,0:16:35.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你不仅确定  你是艾滋确定\N{\rEng}you're not just sure  you're HIV positive!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.99,0:16:37.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这并不有趣\N{\rEng}This isn't funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.00,0:16:38.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋并不有趣\N{\rEng}AIDS isn't funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.94,0:16:41.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,死亡并不有趣  所以你他妈的住嘴\N{\rEng}Dying isn't funny  so shut the fuck Up.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.53,0:16:43.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那我可真抱歉  凯尔\N{\rEng}Well  excuse me  Kyle  
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.97,0:16:45.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不应该表现得乐观\N{\rEng}for trying to keep some optimism.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.01,0:16:47.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当你身处黑暗的时候\N{\rEng}Sometimes when things seem their darkest
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.79,0:16:49.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你需要尽可能地保持\N{\rEng}you just need to try and stay...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.29,0:16:50.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋积极\N{\rEng}[译注:英文阳性也有积极的意思]
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.32,0:16:51.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果你想表现得\N{\rEng}But if you want to be so
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.00,0:16:52.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋消极\N{\rEng}[译注:英文阴性也有消极的意思]
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.03,0:16:54.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,住嘴  马上住嘴\N{\rEng}Knock it off!Right now!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.06,0:16:57.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这一点也不有趣\N{\rEng}This isn't funny!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.06,0:16:58.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不\N{\rEng}At all!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.46,0:17:01.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-你确定  -确定\N{\rEng}- Are you sure? - Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.74,0:17:03.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-你艾滋确定  -噢\N{\rEng}-Are you hiv positive - ow!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.47,0:17:04.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,靠  凯尔\N{\rEng}Oh fuck! Kyle!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.79,0:17:06.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们  事实是我并不知道为什么\N{\rEng}Boys  the truth is I don't know why
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.49,0:17:08.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的身体能够对抗艾滋病毒\N{\rEng}my body is so resistant to the virus.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.82,0:17:10.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果能帮助别人我会很高兴\N{\rEng}I would love to know so I could help others  
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.43,0:17:11.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是我的确不知道\N{\rEng}but I just don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.96,0:17:13.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在想\N{\rEng}Well  I've been thinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.23,0:17:14.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也许有什么你\N{\rEng}Maybe there's something you've
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.42,0:17:15.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一直在接触的东西\N{\rEng}come into contact with
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.22,0:17:17.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在阻止艾滋病毒的生长\N{\rEng}that hinders HIV from growing.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.25,0:17:19.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你介意我们四周看一下吗\N{\rEng}Do you mind if we just look around?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.70,0:17:21.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当然不\N{\rEng}Well  not at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.47,0:17:22.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,游泳池在那边\N{\rEng}The pool is over there  
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.86,0:17:24.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我可以游泳和保持体型\N{\rEng}where I try to swim and stay in shape.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.49,0:17:26.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,厨房里都是健康食品\N{\rEng}My kitchen is full of very healthy food.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.97,0:17:28.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道是什么让我保持\N{\rEng}I don't know which thing is what keeps
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.38,0:17:30.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很高的T细胞  所以我什么都试\N{\rEng}my T-cell count high  so i try it all.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.01,0:17:32.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是所有人都这样做的\N{\rEng}But everyone tries that.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.44,0:17:33.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你一定有什么\N{\rEng}There has to be something
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.20,0:17:35.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,独特的东西\N{\rEng}you're exposed to that others aren't
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.23,0:17:36.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,能看看你睡觉的地方吗\N{\rEng}Could we see where you sleep?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.57,0:17:37.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当然\N{\rEng}Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.60,0:17:40.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,只是一个普通的卧室\N{\rEng}Just a pretty plain old ordinary bedroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.39,0:17:45.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计\N{\rEng}Dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.36,0:17:47.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,噢对  我不太信任银行\N{\rEng}Oh. Yeah  I don't trust banks.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.49,0:17:49.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我跟钱睡在一起\N{\rEng}I sleep with all my money.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.17,0:17:52.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你每晚都睡在钱堆中\N{\rEng}You sleep with money every night?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.57,0:17:54.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我喜欢把它们放在身边\N{\rEng}Yeah. I like to keep it close.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.43,0:17:57.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你难道认为那是\N{\rEng}You don't think that -
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.43,0:18:00.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋研究中心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.44,0:18:05.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不可思议\N{\rEng}It's incredible.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.10,0:18:07.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,米奇  这两个孩子可能有所发现\N{\rEng}Mitch  these boys could be on to something.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.13,0:18:09.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来看一下\N{\rEng}Take a look.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.13,0:18:11.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那是一个被艾滋病毒感染的血样\N{\rEng}That's a sample of HIV infected blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.40,0:18:12.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你可以清楚地看到\N{\rEng}You can clearly see
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.25,0:18:14.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋病毒攻击白血细胞\N{\rEng}the HIV attacking the white blood cells  right?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.59,0:18:15.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好  让我们放点钞票过去\N{\rEng}All right. Now watch what happens
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.79,0:18:17.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看有什么变化\N{\rEng}when we introduce some cash.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.40,0:18:19.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\rEng}My God!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.44,0:18:21.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋病毒在消退\N{\rEng}The HIV particles are receding!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.84,0:18:25.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,钞票似乎在抑制\N{\rEng}The cash does seem to restrain
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.34,0:18:27.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋病毒变得稳定\N{\rEng}the HIV cells from stabilizing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.37,0:18:28.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等一下\N{\rEng}Now hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.78,0:18:31.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,钞票只是让病毒变得不稳定\N{\rEng}All the cash is doing is destrablizing the virus  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.58,0:18:32.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但没有破坏病毒\N{\rEng}not destroying it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.61,0:18:33.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,听着\N{\rEng}Well  look.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.60,0:18:35.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果接近大量的钞票就能对\N{\rEng}If being around lots of cash negatively
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.77,0:18:37.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋病毒起副作用  那也许\N{\rEng}affects the HIV  then maybe -
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.41,0:18:39.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那也许如果往血液里直接注射\N{\rEng}Then maybe enough cash  shot directly into
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.76,0:18:41.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,足够量的钞票就可以杀死艾滋病毒\N{\rEng}the bloodstream could kill the virus altogether.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.99,0:18:43.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我有足够治疗我们三人的钱\N{\rEng}I have enough cash for all three of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.55,0:18:44.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该试一下\N{\rEng}We should give it a try!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.66,0:18:46.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  这太荒谬了\N{\rEng}No  no. This is ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.50,0:18:47.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要药物管理局的批准\N{\rEng}We need FDA approvals  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.70,0:18:48.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,和病例对照研究\N{\rEng}control studies!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.73,0:18:50.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉  但这是不可能的\N{\rEng}I'm sorry  but this is impossible.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.90,0:18:52.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这两个男孩向我们展示了\N{\rEng}These boys have shown us that
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.59,0:18:54.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么是不可能的\N{\rEng}a lot of impossible things can happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.63,0:18:56.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们用他们的友情征服了\N{\rEng}Their friendship has conquered every
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.47,0:18:58.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,每一个病痛带来的障碍\N{\rEng}obstacle in their illness-ridden lives!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.14,0:19:01.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们伟大的友情\N{\rEng}Their incredible friendship has
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.49,0:19:03.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为世界带来了一线希望\N{\rEng}brought a sparkle of hope to our world.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.21,0:19:05.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那是肯定的\N{\rEng}That's for sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.67,0:19:08.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想我们可以把魔术师的\N{\rEng}I suppose we could try to distill Magic's
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.92,0:19:10.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,钞票进行提炼\N{\rEng}cash down to its most highly
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.55,0:19:12.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,浓缩成精华然后\N{\rEng}concentrated level and
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.45,0:19:13.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在一个人身上试用\N{\rEng}try it on one of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.88,0:19:15.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是风险很高\N{\rEng}But it's very risky.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.13,0:19:16.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,只要有一线能够\N{\rEng}Yeah  well  if there's a chance of
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.48,0:19:17.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,痊愈的希望\N{\rEng}being cured of this illness  
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.01,0:19:20.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔就愿意去承担这样的风险\N{\rEng}then Kyle is willing to take that risk.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.16,0:19:52.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让我们祈祷它有效吧\N{\rEng}Let's hope to Christ this works.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.93,0:20:00.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等一下\N{\rEng}Wait a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.50,0:20:01.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\rEng}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.47,0:20:03.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是的  快看\N{\rEng}Yes  take a look!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.27,0:20:05.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,钞票粒子完全取代了\N{\rEng}The cash particles have completely replaced
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.47,0:20:08.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔血液中所有的艾滋病毒\N{\rEng}all the HIV in kyle's blood!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.54,0:20:11.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们\N{\rEng}Boys  
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.41,0:20:14.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们找到治疗艾滋的方法了\N{\rEng}you've just found the cure for AIDS!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.38,0:20:15.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\rEng}All right!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.98,0:20:17.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们找到治疗艾滋的方法了\N{\rEng}They've found the cure for AIDS!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.96,0:20:19.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,治疗艾滋的方法\N{\rEng}The cure for AIDS!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.69,0:20:20.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是什么\N{\rEng}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.89,0:20:23.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大剂量的浓缩钞票精华\N{\rEng}Large doses of concentrated cash!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.88,0:20:25.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快通知媒体\N{\rEng}Get the media on the phone!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.51,0:20:27.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\rEng}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.24,0:20:28.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,科学家们刚刚发现了\N{\rEng}Scientists have just discovered
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.99,0:20:30.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,治疗艾滋的方法\N{\rEng}the cure for AIDS.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.32,0:20:32.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,把18万美元\N{\rEng}About $180  000
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.34,0:20:34.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,直接注射入血液中\N{\rEng}shot directly into the bloodstream.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.19,0:20:37.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,非洲  尼日利亚\N{\rEng}Nigeria Africa
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.88,0:20:39.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,嘿\N{\rEng}Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.65,0:20:41.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,治疗艾滋的方法刚刚被发现了\N{\rEng}They just found the cure for AIDS!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.57,0:20:43.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们只需要把你们\N{\rEng}You just have to infect yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.27,0:20:45.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所有的钞票注射入血液中\N{\rEng}with all your cash!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.73,0:20:51.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴地宣布\N{\rEng}I am pleased to announce that
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.19,0:20:54.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾滋病毒已经完全从\N{\rEng}there is no trace of the HIV virus in either
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.31,0:20:57.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔和卡特曼身上消失了\N{\rEng}Kyle Broflovski or Eric Cartman.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.62,0:21:01.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们携手击败了疾病\N{\rEng}Together  these boys beat their illness  
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.19,0:21:02.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,两人相依相伴\N{\rEng}with nothing but each other  
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.51,0:21:04.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,创造了奇迹\N{\rEng}and overcoming all odds other  
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.38,0:21:07.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这对勇敢的朋友\N{\rEng}these two brave friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.11,0:21:09.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,算了吧  我们不是朋友\N{\rEng}Oh  stop!We're not friends!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.33,0:21:12.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是他传染艾滋给我的\N{\rEng}He's the one who infected me with AIDS!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.58,0:21:14.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这对勇敢的情人\N{\rEng}Those two brave lovers
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.58,0:21:17.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为世界找到了艾滋的治疗方法\N{\rEng}found the cure and helped the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.61,0:21:20.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为了向两个孩子致敬\N{\rEng}And so to honor these boys  
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.44,0:21:23.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有请  吉米·布菲特\N{\rEng}here is Jimmy Buffet!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.47,0:21:25.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么  噢  不\N{\rEng}What?Oh  no!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.62,0:21:29.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*天堂的治疗汉堡*\N{\rEng}*Cure burger in paradise*
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.19,0:21:32.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*有了治疗汉堡  我再说一次*\N{\rEng}*cure burger there  I said it twice*
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.82,0:21:34.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真他妈的\N{\rEng}Agh  god dammit!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.19,0:21:36.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉你  凯尔\N{\rEng}Well  I tell you this  Kyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.65,0:21:39.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我再也不做扁桃腺手术了\N{\rEng}I'm never getting my tonsils out again!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.54,0:21:42.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我还是要砸了你的x-box\N{\rEng}I'm still breaking your xbox.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.50,0:21:45.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么  不要\N{\rEng}What?No!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.08,0:21:45.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  凯尔  不要\N{\rEng}Kyle  Kyle  no!
