[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2008-10-23 07:50:54
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayDepth: 0
PlayResX: 1916
PlayResY: 1076
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 2
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H19000000,&H000E0300,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,2,2,134,120,68,1
Style: eng,Microsoft YaHei,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,26,1
Style: Top,微软雅黑,10,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Git,Comic Sans MS,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Chn,微软雅黑,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Eng,Comic Sans MS,60,&H002AF7FF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.20,0:00:11.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm going down to south park\N gonna have myself a time 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.05,0:00:15.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Friendly faces everywhere\N humble folks without temptation 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.33,0:00:18.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Going down to south park\N gonna leave my woes behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.72,0:00:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ample parking day or night\N people shouting howdy neighbor
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.96,0:00:24.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heading on out to south park\N gonna see if I can't unwind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.54,0:00:28.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I like girls with big vaginas\N I like girls with big fat titties
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.61,0:00:31.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.60,0:21:45.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译制作\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}YYeTs人人影视字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.60,0:21:46.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}校译\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}sunflo
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.60,0:21:47.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1c&HFDC282&}后期\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}csbeyond
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.33,0:00:31.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0150,,{\1c&HFDC282&}南方公园  第12季第2集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.33,0:00:31.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0100,,小甜甜的新形象\N{\rEng}"Britney's New Look"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.50,0:00:36.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来自伊力诺依州芝加哥的直播\N{\rEng}Live   from Chicago   Illinois  
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.13,0:00:38.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,决策2008\N{\rEng}it's Decision 2008.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.97,0:00:41.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好  欢迎来到希拉里·克林顿和\N{\rEng}Good evening and welcome to the political debate
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.69,0:00:44.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴拉克·奥巴马的政治辩论\N{\rEng}between Hillary Rodham Clinton and Barack Obama.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.94,0:00:47.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,第一个问题  你们认为自己\N{\rEng}First question: How do you see yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.13,0:00:49.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,和对手有什么不同\N{\rEng}as different from your opponent?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.89,0:00:53.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,爸  能不看这个吗\N{\rEng}Ugh   Dad   can we please not watch this?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.40,0:00:54.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这很重要  斯坦利\N{\rEng}This is important   Stanley!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.99,0:00:56.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们应该关心这个\N{\rEng}You boys should care about this stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.81,0:00:58.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,可是我们一点也不关心\N{\rEng}Yeah   but we totally don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.41,0:01:00.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们必须坐下来看\N{\rEng}Well you boys are gonna sit and watch this!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.26,0:01:02.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是真正的大事\N{\rEng}This is what really matters!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.52,0:01:05.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马先生  请告诉我们\N{\rEng}And so   Mr. Obama   why don't you tell us
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.04,0:01:07.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你对于军事开销的立场\N{\rEng}your stance on military spending?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.49,0:01:10.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的意见是\N{\rEng}Well   my opinion is that-
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.61,0:01:12.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们打断辩论\N{\rEng}We interrupt this debate for
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.32,0:01:14.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,插播一条紧急新闻\N{\rEng}an emergency news bulletin!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.44,0:01:16.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这里是  "小甜甜观察"\N{\rEng}It's... Britney Watch!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.64,0:01:18.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让你随时获得最新\N{\rEng}Keeping you up-to-date with
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.04,0:01:19.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,最全的小甜甜新闻\N{\rEng}all your Britney Spears news!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.32,0:01:22.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,噢耶  她又干了什么\N{\rEng}Oh-oh boy   what's she done now?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.73,0:01:24.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜被发现在\N{\rEng}Britney has been spotted
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.13,0:01:26.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,科罗拉多山露营\N{\rEng}camping in the Colorado mountains  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.38,0:01:27.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有报道称\N{\rEng}and one report claims that
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.62,0:01:30.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她在森林中  小便\N{\rEng}she has taken a piss... in the forest.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.64,0:01:32.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,罗伯特·泼纳有更多的消息\N{\rEng}Robert Pooner has more.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.55,0:01:34.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,容  我在科罗拉多州的南方公园\N{\rEng}Ron   I'm standing in South Park   Colorado  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.11,0:01:36.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜试图从我们\N{\rEng}where Britney Spears has apparently
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.47,0:01:38.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,视线中消失的地方\N{\rEng}been trying to get away from it all.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.59,0:01:40.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们  是我们镇\N{\rEng}Aw dude   that's our town!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.14,0:01:41.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜在一个\N{\rEng}Ms. Spears was spotted
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.46,0:01:42.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,山区营地被发现\N{\rEng}at a mountain campground  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.88,0:01:44.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们不会相信她干了什么\N{\rEng}and you won't believe what she did   Ron.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.02,0:01:47.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这个麻烦女王在一个\N{\rEng}The troubled diva took a piss.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.22,0:01:49.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,瓢虫身上撒尿\N{\rEng}Right on a ladybug.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.40,0:01:50.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们对照片中不雅之处\N{\rEng}We've blurred out parts of
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.59,0:01:52.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,进行了模糊处理\N{\rEng}the photo so that it doesn't offend.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.70,0:01:56.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她可真是个祸害\N{\rEng}She's such a train wreck!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.95,0:01:58.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果把照片放大  容\N{\rEng}When the photo is enhance   Ron  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.79,0:01:59.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你可以清楚地看到\N{\rEng}you can see the poor little
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.93,0:02:02.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,可怜瓢虫被尿浸泡\N{\rEng}ladybug getting doused.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.68,0:02:04.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这张照片的流出\N{\rEng}This must be very embarrassing for
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.69,0:02:06.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一定使小甜甜非常难堪  鲍勃\N{\rEng}Britney that this photo got out   Bob  
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.81,0:02:08.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,而且她看起来又长胖了\N{\rEng}and she looks like she's gained weight.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.96,0:02:11.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  容  她的确长胖了\N{\rEng}That's right   Ron   she really chubbed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.17,0:02:12.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果放大她的脸部\N{\rEng}And if you zoom in on her face  
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.92,0:02:15.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你可以看到她还长了青春痘\N{\rEng}you can see that she's got some zits!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.84,0:02:17.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,可怜的女孩\N{\rEng}Aw   poor girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.28,0:02:20.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,莎朗  小甜甜对着瓢虫撒尿\N{\rEng}Hey Sharon   Britney peed on a ladybug.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.70,0:02:21.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,照片是科罗拉多州贝利市的\N{\rEng}The photograph was taken
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.98,0:02:24.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,布莱恩·威利斯拍的\N{\rEng}by Brian Willis of Bailey   Colorado  
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.40,0:02:25.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他把照片以10万美元的价格\N{\rEng}who sold it to 31 News
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.93,0:02:27.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,卖给了31新闻台\N{\rEng}for a hundred thousand dollars.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.49,0:02:30.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,10万美元\N{\rEng}A hundred thousand dollars?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.24,0:02:32.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,都足够买奴隶了\N{\rEng}That's enough to buy slaves!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.26,0:02:33.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,据说小甜甜现在躲在\N{\rEng}Britney is said to be now
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.77,0:02:36.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,南方公园的旅馆中\N{\rEng}hiding out in a South Park motel.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.49,0:02:37.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在让我们回到\N{\rEng}And now back to the
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.90,0:02:39.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,愚蠢的民主辩论中\N{\rEng}stupid Democratic debates.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.29,0:02:42.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,和黑鬼们\N{\rEng}and spearchuckers.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.37,0:02:44.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,听到了吗\N{\rEng}Did you guys hear that?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.69,0:02:45.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜的照片\N{\rEng}A hundred thousand dollars
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.69,0:02:46.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,值10万美元\N{\rEng}for a picture of Britney.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.81,0:02:48.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,而且她就在我们镇上的旅馆中\N{\rEng}And she's at a hotel in our town.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.64,0:02:49.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是肯佛特旅馆\N{\rEng}It's gotta be the Komfort Inn.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.89,0:02:51.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那是南方公园最好的酒店\N{\rEng}That's the nicest hotel in South Park.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.41,0:02:52.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,卡特曼  带上你的相机\N{\rEng}Cartman   go get your camera.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.74,0:02:54.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,爽\N{\rEng}Sweet!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.70,0:02:56.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  伙计们\N{\rEng}Hey   hang on   fellas  
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.35,0:02:58.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们不觉得小甜甜已经够惨了吗\N{\rEng}don't you think Britney's been through enough?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.32,0:02:59.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也许我们应该让她\N{\rEng}I mean   maybe it's finally time
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.92,0:03:02.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,过自己的生活\N{\rEng}for us all to just leave her alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.15,0:03:05.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  别那么唧唧歪歪\N{\rEng}Butters   don't be such a pussy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.60,0:03:06.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\rEng}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.49,0:03:10.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜在瓢虫身上小便\N{\rEng}A hundred thousand for a picture
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.05,0:03:11.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,的照片卖了10万美元\N{\rEng}of Britney peeing on a ladybug.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.27,0:03:12.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,想象一下她在松鼠身上\N{\rEng}Imagine what a photo of her
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.34,0:03:14.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大便的照片会值多少\N{\rEng}crapping on a squirrel is worth!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.36,0:03:15.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是为了复活节音乐剧\N{\rEng}Well this costume was supposed
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.37,0:03:17.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,准备的戏服  伙计们\N{\rEng}to be for the Easter musical   fellas  
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.39,0:03:19.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不是用来发横财的\N{\rEng}not for trying to make an easy buck!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.98,0:03:21.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧\N{\rEng}Oh no.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.55,0:03:25.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我们想拍张\N{\rEng}Excuse us   we're trying to
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.53,0:03:27.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜的照片\N{\rEng}get a picture of Britney Spears!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.15,0:03:28.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等着吧\N{\rEng}Join the club.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.40,0:03:30.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  你们这些业余摄影者\N{\rEng}Yeah   all you amateur photographers are
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.23,0:03:32.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让我们专业的都很难拍照了\N{\rEng}making this tougher on the professionals!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.35,0:03:34.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们也是专业的  你他妈的混蛋\N{\rEng}We're professionals too   you fucking butthole!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.04,0:03:38.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谁也不能上楼\N{\rEng}Ah ah   nobody goes upstairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.40,0:03:40.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们有特别通行证\N{\rEng}We uh   we have special permission?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.03,0:03:42.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  你不认识我们吗\N{\rEng}Yeah   don't you recognize us?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.58,0:03:44.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们是小甜甜的孩子\N{\rEng}We're Britney Spears' kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.82,0:03:46.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\rEng}You are?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.37,0:03:48.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不是  我是松鼠\N{\rEng}Not me! I'm a squirrel!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.41,0:03:52.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在所有人都以为我讨厌瓢虫\N{\rEng}But now everybody thinks I hate ladybugs.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.17,0:03:54.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道那儿有瓢虫\N{\rEng}I didn't even know it was there.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.27,0:03:57.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我受不了了  我实在\N{\rEng}I can't take it anymore. I'm just so-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.76,0:04:00.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  斯皮尔斯小姐  你的孩子们来了\N{\rEng}Excuse me   Ms. Spears   but your kids are here
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.24,0:04:01.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们给你带了只松鼠\N{\rEng}and they've brought you a squirrel.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.36,0:04:05.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的孩子  真的吗  叫他们进来\N{\rEng}My boys? Really? Send them in.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.57,0:04:09.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  我的孩子们来了  我感觉好多了\N{\rEng}It's okay. My kids are here. I feel better now.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.94,0:04:13.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,成功了 伙计们\N{\rEng}We did it guys!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.19,0:04:14.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我说过能行的\N{\rEng}I told you that would work!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.51,0:04:17.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-没错  -太好了\N{\rEng}- Yeah   all right!  - All right!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.44,0:04:19.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你是说那只是玩笑吗\N{\rEng}You mean   it was just a joke?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.05,0:04:21.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的小孩根本没来\N{\rEng}My kids ain't here?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.68,0:04:23.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快  巴特斯  靠近她\N{\rEng}Alright. Butters   go get next to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.14,0:04:24.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不\N{\rEng}I ain't do it
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.36,0:04:26.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不应该欺骗她的\N{\rEng}We tricked her and it wasn't nice!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.31,0:04:27.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  你不想分\N{\rEng}Butters   do you want your share of
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.31,0:04:28.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那10万美元了吗\N{\rEng}the hundred thousand dollars or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.63,0:04:30.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们永远也不会放过我  是吗\N{\rEng}You're never gonna leave me alone   are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.91,0:04:32.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,占任何人的便宜\N{\rEng}It ain't right to take advantage
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.24,0:04:33.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,都是不对的\N{\rEng}of somebody no matter who they are!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.06,0:04:35.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  很好\N{\rEng}All right   fine!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.12,0:04:36.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不需要你了  巴特斯\N{\rEng}We don't need you   Butters!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.24,0:04:36.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我们可以随便拍张\N{\rEng}Yeah   we'll just get a picture
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.93,0:04:38.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她做其他事的照片\N{\rEng}of her doing something else.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.25,0:04:38.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  女士\N{\rEng}All right lady  
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.66,0:04:40.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,把你的裆部亮出来\N{\rEng}just flash us your crotch or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.68,0:04:42.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我有更好的主意\N{\rEng}I've got a better idea
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.24,0:04:42.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\rEng}You do?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.44,0:04:44.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.74,0:04:46.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要\N{\rEng}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.61,0:05:04.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们害死了她\N{\rEng}You killed her!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.36,0:05:11.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  没什么事吧  噢\N{\rEng}Hey   everything all right u-. Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.74,0:05:25.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不应该骚扰她的\N{\rEng}We should have just left her alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.81,0:05:27.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是我们却逼她\N{\rEng}But we just had to push her.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.93,0:05:29.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们怎么知道她会\N{\rEng}How cold we know she would...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.87,0:05:31.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们真是混蛋\N{\rEng}Aw we suck so hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.31,0:05:38.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她还  活着\N{\rEng}She's... alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.94,0:05:40.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢上帝\N{\rEng}Oh   thank God.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.73,0:05:42.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是差一点我们就见不到她了\N{\rEng}But   we almost lost her.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.71,0:05:43.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们为什么就不能\N{\rEng}Why couldn't you boys
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.75,0:05:44.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,放过她呢\N{\rEng}just leave her alone?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.01,0:05:47.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,医生  我们能同她说句话吗\N{\rEng}Doctor   could we talk to her for a minute?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.18,0:05:48.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不想你们骚扰她\N{\rEng}I don't want you making her upset.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.04,0:05:50.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不会骚扰她\N{\rEng}We don't wanna upset her  
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.20,0:05:51.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是想向她道歉\N{\rEng}we just want to tell her that we're sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.05,0:05:54.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\rEng}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.21,0:05:59.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,斯皮尔斯小姐  这些孩子们有话想说\N{\rEng}Ms. Spears   these boys wanted to say something.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.57,0:06:03.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  -不会吧\N{\rEng}- Oh my God!  - Oh no!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.03,0:06:05.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们只是被你的美丽\N{\rEng}The boys are just shocked at how
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.79,0:06:08.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,震惊了  对吧  孩子们\N{\rEng}good you look   Britney. Right   boys?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.30,0:06:12.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  没错  我们什么也看不到\N{\rEng}Oh   yeah. Yeah. It's not even noticeable.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.27,0:06:18.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  说你们想说的吧\N{\rEng}Well   I'll let you boys have your say.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.10,0:06:24.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,斯皮尔斯小姐\N{\rEng}Ms. Spears   uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.91,0:06:26.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们非常抱歉\N{\rEng}we're... really... sorry for
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.27,0:06:28.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让你想要自杀\N{\rEng}making you want to kill yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.39,0:06:30.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  看我们干的好事\N{\rEng}Oh   God   what have we done?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.10,0:06:34.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这里是"小甜甜观察"\N{\rEng}It's Britney Watch!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.39,0:06:35.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让你随时获得最新\N{\rEng}Keeping you up-to-date with
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.43,0:06:36.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,最全的小甜甜新闻\N{\rEng}all your Britney Spears news!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.80,0:06:39.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们不会相信\N{\rEng}You won't believe
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.09,0:06:40.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜又干了什么\N{\rEng}what Britney's done now.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.51,0:06:41.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这个麻烦明星\N{\rEng}The troubled pop star has
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.97,0:06:43.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,刚被发现打扮了一个\N{\rEng}just been spotted with a crazy
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.09,0:06:46.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,"没有脑袋上半部分"的新形象\N{\rEng}"no top part of my head" look.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.33,0:06:48.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是几小时前刚拍到的影像\N{\rEng}This video was taken just hours ago
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.61,0:06:49.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜因某些原因\N{\rEng}as Britney was wheeled into
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.67,0:06:51.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,被送进医院\N{\rEng}the hospital for some reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.59,0:06:52.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们放大图像\N{\rEng}And if we zoom in on the footage  
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.93,0:06:54.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这里  注意看这里\N{\rEng}right   right here  
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.55,0:06:55.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你可以清楚地看到\N{\rEng}you can also definitely
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.94,0:06:57.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她做隆胸手术留下的疤痕\N{\rEng}see a boob job scar.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.50,0:06:58.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,毫无疑问\N{\rEng}No doubt now that she's
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.96,0:07:00.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她曾经做过整形手术\N{\rEng}had plastic surgery in the past.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.92,0:07:04.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  那可真是尴尬\N{\rEng}oh houch   that's gotta be embarrassing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.18,0:07:06.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,克里斯  知道为什么小甜甜会打扮成\N{\rEng}Chris   any word on why Ms. Spears went
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.70,0:07:09.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这个"没有脑袋上半部分"的疯狂造型吗\N{\rEng}for this radical "no top of the head" look?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.40,0:07:10.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,暂时还不知道  汤姆\N{\rEng}No word yet   Tom  
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.59,0:07:12.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但有可能是因为她对我们\N{\rEng}but it could be over the embarrassment
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.71,0:07:14.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚播放的隆胸手术疤痕\N{\rEng}of the boob job scar video
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.07,0:07:16.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,过于尴尬\N{\rEng}we showed just   just now.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.19,0:07:17.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,虽然时间\N{\rEng}Uh   even though the timing
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.23,0:07:18.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不太对得上\N{\rEng}doesn't quite work out
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.27,0:07:25.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计\N{\rEng}Dude!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.22,0:07:29.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,该死的  她现在不能\N{\rEng}Damnit   she can't handle
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.32,0:07:31.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,再受刺激了\N{\rEng}any stress right now!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.14,0:07:33.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我是小甜甜的经纪人\N{\rEng}Excuse me   I'm Britney Spears' manager.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.45,0:07:35.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  小甜甜\N{\rEng}Oh   jeez   Britney!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.18,0:07:36.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜  你在想什么啊\N{\rEng}Britney   what were you thinking?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.02,0:07:40.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,先是剃了个光头  现在又\N{\rEng}First you shave your head and now this.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.40,0:07:42.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当然  我承认这个造型\N{\rEng}Well   it's a ballsy new look  
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.58,0:07:44.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很有性格\N{\rEng}I'll give you that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.75,0:07:45.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜  看这边\N{\rEng}Brit! Over here   Brit.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.70,0:07:47.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为星周刊拍张照\N{\rEng}One for Star Weekly.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.10,0:07:49.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,该死  你们必须把她从这里带走\N{\rEng}Damnit you have to take her out of here;
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.33,0:07:51.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她现在不能再被骚扰\N{\rEng}she can't be around all this right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.42,0:07:52.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我要把她带回家\N{\rEng}Right. We need to take her home.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.90,0:07:54.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们  能帮把手吗\N{\rEng}Boys   can you give me a hand with her?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.82,0:07:56.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当然\N{\rEng}Yeah   of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.22,0:07:59.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快\N{\rEng}Okay   come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.25,0:08:02.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的车在这\N{\rEng}My car is right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.62,0:08:04.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-瞧  -她在那儿\N{\rEng}- Hey look!  - There she is!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.14,0:08:10.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,靠\N{\rEng}Oh crap!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.59,0:08:16.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上帝\N{\rEng}Jesus Christ!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.78,0:08:18.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好  好  总是这样的\N{\rEng}Yeah yeah   it's like this all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.59,0:08:20.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  谢谢\N{\rEng}Thank you! Yes   thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.95,0:08:27.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我们真的感觉很内疚\N{\rEng}Look   uh   we feel really bad   and   and
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.93,0:08:30.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们想尽可能地帮助小甜甜\N{\rEng}we wanna help Britney however we can.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.75,0:08:32.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  孩子们  小甜甜看起来\N{\rEng}That's great   boys. Britney seems
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.75,0:08:34.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真的开始喜欢你们了\N{\rEng}to have really taken a liking to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.67,0:08:35.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不过不用担心\N{\rEng}And don't worry
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.71,0:08:38.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜有很强的自我恢复能力\N{\rEng}Britney is a queen at reinventing herself.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.13,0:08:39.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们只需要把她\N{\rEng}We just need to get her into
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.39,0:08:41.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,马上带到录音棚去\N{\rEng}the recording studio right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.51,0:08:42.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.24,0:08:45.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  小甜甜  让我们从头开始\N{\rEng}All right   Britney   let's take it from the top.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.09,0:08:48.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,记着唱得性感一些\N{\rEng}Remember to bring that sexiness to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.21,0:08:49.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  你们真的认为\N{\rEng}Excuse me   is this really what
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.45,0:08:51.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在是录音的时候吗\N{\rEng}you think she should be doing right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.17,0:08:54.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  小甜甜  从头开始\N{\rEng}All right   Brit   let's try it from the top.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.38,0:09:05.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上帝  真是个灾难\N{\rEng}God   what a train wreck.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.34,0:09:07.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她肯定又嗑药了\N{\rEng}She must be stoned again.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.85,0:09:16.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,能停下来吗\N{\rEng}Would you put a stop to this   please?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.16,0:09:17.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这只会让事情更糟糕\N{\rEng}This is only gonna make things worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.08,0:09:19.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你什么意思  她听起来很不错\N{\rEng}What do you mean? She sounds great.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.17,0:09:23.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜  上一句歌词应该是\N{\rEng}Britney   that last lyric is supposed to be
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.34,0:09:24.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,"爱情美好"  听起来\N{\rEng}"love elation." Sounds more
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.98,0:09:26.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你像是在唱"爱情创造"\N{\rEng}like you're saying "love creation."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.53,0:09:32.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,美-好 M-E-I\N{\rEng}E-la-tion. Really enunciate the L.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.11,0:09:35.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她真是蠢到家了\N{\rEng}Gah   she's so stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.29,0:09:36.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你还想怎么样  看看她\N{\rEng}What do you expect? Look at her!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.65,0:09:38.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她根本就没有大脑\N{\rEng}She doesn't have most of her brain!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.27,0:09:40.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  她真的很蠢  不是嘛\N{\rEng}I know. She's really dumb   huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.41,0:09:42.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  我是说她真的没有\N{\rEng}No I mean   she literally doesn't have
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.22,0:09:44.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大脑  她的脑袋不见了\N{\rEng}most of her brain! Her head is gone!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.14,0:09:46.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  而且她还很肥\N{\rEng}Yeah. And she's all fat   too.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.37,0:09:51.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来自拉斯维加斯的直播\N{\rEng}Live   from Las Vegas  
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.69,0:09:54.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,MTV颁奖晚会\N{\rEng}it's the MTV Video Music Awards.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.65,0:09:56.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,各位晚上好  MTV颁奖晚会\N{\rEng}What's up   y'all? It's the MTV Awards
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.30,0:09:58.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,马上就要开始了\N{\rEng}and we are kicking it off right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.42,0:10:00.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,带来了她的新歌\N{\rEng}Here to perform her new song
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.19,0:10:03.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们独一无二的小甜甜\N{\rEng}is the one and only   Britney Spears!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.22,0:10:10.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,算了吧  你们\N{\rEng}Aw come on now   people!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.45,0:10:13.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天  她可变得真胖\N{\rEng}Oh my God   she's really gotten chubby.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.27,0:10:44.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她绝对是在对嘴型假唱\N{\rEng}Oh man   she's totally lip-syncing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.56,0:10:46.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她连嘴都没有\N{\rEng}She doesn't have any lips!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.20,0:11:02.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,MTV颁奖晚会上的灾难\N{\rEng}Disaster at the MTV awards.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.36,0:11:04.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,人们都在嘲笑小甜甜\N{\rEng}People are ridiculing Britney Spears.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.99,0:11:06.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她的演出很糟糕\N{\rEng}Her performance was awful   Tom.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.03,0:11:08.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她看起来疲惫  她看起来很胖\N{\rEng}She looked tired   she looked fat
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.52,0:11:09.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她没有脑袋\N{\rEng}she didn't have a head.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.84,0:11:11.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,热线电话全是对她的抱怨\N{\rEng}It was just completely phoned in.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.96,0:11:12.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,毫无疑问  汤姆\N{\rEng}No doubt   Tom  
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.73,0:11:15.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这个女孩有大麻烦了\N{\rEng}that girl has major issues.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.25,0:11:16.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要听他们的  小甜甜\N{\rEng}Don't listen to 'em   Brit!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.55,0:11:18.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们只是在嫉妒你\N{\rEng}They're all just jealous.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.17,0:11:21.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,明天就让你上"减肥有道"\N{\rEng}And we can put you on SlimFast tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.86,0:11:25.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等一会  等一会\N{\rEng}Hang on   hang on  
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.11,0:11:27.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她很快就会出来\N{\rEng}she'll be out in a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.27,0:11:42.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须带她离开这里\N{\rEng}We have to get her away from all this   dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.38,0:11:44.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这些人不会善罢甘休的\N{\rEng}People just aren't gonna let up.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.10,0:11:46.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须把她带到\N{\rEng}We have to take her somewhere
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.27,0:11:48.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没人骚扰的地方\N{\rEng}to just be at peace.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.69,0:11:49.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  世界上哪儿有小甜甜\N{\rEng}Dude   where in the world can Britney
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.84,0:11:53.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,能够不被骚扰的地方\N{\rEng}Spears go where nobody will bother her?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.64,0:11:56.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我知道一个地方\N{\rEng}I know where.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.02,0:12:02.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们要三张去北极的票\N{\rEng}We want three tickets to the North Pole.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.82,0:12:03.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,北极\N{\rEng}The North Pole?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.74,0:12:05.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谁他妈的会去北极啊\N{\rEng}Who the hell goes to the North Pole?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.86,0:12:07.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们会  我  我的朋友  还有他姨妈\N{\rEng}We do. Me   my friend   and his aunt.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.75,0:12:12.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这里是"小甜甜观察"\N{\rEng}It's Britney Watch!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.88,0:12:14.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,神智错乱的\N{\rEng}A distraught Britney Spears
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.56,0:12:15.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜失踪了\N{\rEng}has apparently disappeared
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.08,0:12:18.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,抛弃了所有亲朋好友\N{\rEng}and abandoned all those close to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.57,0:12:20.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一个当地家庭主妇拍到一张\N{\rEng}A local housewife caught a photo of
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.34,0:12:22.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜伪装潜逃的照片\N{\rEng}Britney running away in this disguise!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.87,0:12:24.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她一定对她在MTV颁奖晚会\N{\rEng}Britney is obviously very upse
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.70,0:12:26.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,的演出感到很不安  容\N{\rEng}about her MTV performance   Ron  
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.82,0:12:28.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所以她才变得如此绝望\N{\rEng}and so she's become desperate.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.70,0:12:30.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她最大的麻烦是  她的伪装\N{\rEng}Most troubling for her is the fact
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.40,0:12:33.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有明显的"骆驼趾"\N{\rEng}[译注：骆驼趾是女性阴部的俗称]
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.91,0:12:37.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的天  莱斯利  这"骆驼趾"\N{\rEng}Oh boy   now   Leslie   this seems
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.83,0:12:39.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看起来可真囧\N{\rEng}like a really bad camel toe offense.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.95,0:12:42.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,绝对是很明显的"骆驼趾"  崔西\N{\rEng}Absolutely major camel toe   Tracy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.92,0:12:44.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜看起来忘记了\N{\rEng}Britney just seems oblivious.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.04,0:12:46.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她肯定会被认出来的\N{\rEng}She was bound to get noticed:
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.56,0:12:47.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,带着那样的"骆驼趾"走来走去\N{\rEng}you walk around with that kind of
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.75,0:12:50.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会不引人注目\N{\rEng}cam toe and you're gonna turn heads.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.60,0:12:52.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大卫  知道她的\N{\rEng}David   any idea as to how big
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.36,0:12:53.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,"骆驼趾"到底有多大吗\N{\rEng}the camel toe actually was?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.18,0:12:55.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她从来没有像这样\N{\rEng}She was sporting toe
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.48,0:12:56.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,突出过她的"骆驼趾"  布莱恩\N{\rEng}like never before   Brian.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.80,0:12:57.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道这个\N{\rEng}I don't know what's
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.52,0:12:58.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,女孩是怎么了  但是\N{\rEng}wrong with that girl   but  
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.94,0:13:00.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这可真是给全世界\N{\rEng}it's a slap in the face
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.00,0:13:01.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,的骆驼扇了一记耳光\N{\rEng}to camels all over the planet.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.76,0:13:02.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜的亲友们\N{\rEng}Those close to Britney
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.89,0:13:04.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,表示了他们的担忧\N{\rEng}say they are very worried
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.21,0:13:05.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,并且想把她安全带回家\N{\rEng}and want to bring her home safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.11,0:13:08.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在让我们回到本地新闻\N{\rEng}And now back to the local news.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.18,0:13:09.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,动物管理协会上周\N{\rEng}The giant squirrel which was
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.89,0:13:11.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,抓住的巨大松鼠\N{\rEng}picked up last week by animal control
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.01,0:13:14.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,显然认为它自己是一个人\N{\rEng}apparently now thinks it's a person.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.68,0:13:16.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,科罗拉多州官方已经把这只\N{\rEng}Colorado officials have taken
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.12,0:13:17.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,松鼠送到约翰·霍普金斯大学\N{\rEng}the squirrel to Johns-Hopkins
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.64,0:13:19.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,做精神测试\N{\rEng}for psychiatric evaluation.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.65,0:13:23.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那只松鼠明显是在发疯\N{\rEng}Hm   that squirrel is obviously nuts.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.37,0:13:26.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,4号站台\N{\rEng}Platform 4F
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.40,0:13:28.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一定是在车站另一边\N{\rEng}it must be on the other side of the station.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.52,0:13:30.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她在这儿  小甜甜在这儿\N{\rEng}There she is! It's Britney!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.81,0:13:33.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\rEng}Oh no.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.88,0:13:42.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  他们不会\N{\rEng}Dude   they're never gonna
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.52,0:13:44.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,放我们走的\N{\rEng}let us through.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.44,0:13:46.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们会的   我有主意\N{\rEng}Yes they are! I have an idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.93,0:13:50.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜  她到哪儿去了\N{\rEng}Britney? Where'd she go?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.66,0:13:52.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她在这\N{\rEng}There she is!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.09,0:14:14.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没事了  你很快就能到北极了\N{\rEng}It's okay   you'll be in the North Pole soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.63,0:14:19.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她在这儿  小甜甜  是我\N{\rEng}There she is. Hey Britney   it's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.55,0:14:33.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜  别跑了\N{\rEng}Britney. It's over.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.27,0:14:35.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你到底为什么要跑\N{\rEng}What were you running for anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.93,0:14:37.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等一下\N{\rEng}Hey   wait a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.69,0:14:39.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她的"骆驼趾"到哪儿去了\N{\rEng}Where's her camel toe?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.68,0:14:41.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不是小甜甜  满意了吧\N{\rEng}I'm not Britney Spears   alright?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.13,0:14:44.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,妈的  她一定\N{\rEng}Oh   psych! She must be back
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.21,0:14:45.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还在车站  快走\N{\rEng}at the train station; come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.63,0:14:46.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,站住\N{\rEng}Now   wait a minute!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.94,0:14:48.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都等一下\N{\rEng}Everyone just stop for one minute!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.57,0:14:50.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,听着  你们\N{\rEng}Look   you guys are
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.88,0:14:52.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,会害死她的\N{\rEng}gonna end up killing her.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.60,0:14:54.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们看不出来小甜甜已经\N{\rEng}Can't you see that Britney isn't in any
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.16,0:14:55.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不能再受更多的骚扰了吗\N{\rEng}condition to handle this crap anymore?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.45,0:14:59.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我知道看着名人堕落\N{\rEng}I know watching celebrities
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.71,0:15:00.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,能给你们带来乐趣\N{\rEng}go down can be fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.03,0:15:01.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我和我的朋友们\N{\rEng}Me and my friends are
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.58,0:15:03.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,跟你们一样有过错  但是\N{\rEng}as guilty as all of you   but
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.70,0:15:06.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也许  也许这次\N{\rEng}maybe   just   maybe  
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.59,0:15:08.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这次我们应该停手了\N{\rEng}...it's time to let this one go.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.74,0:15:11.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这一次  让我们在\N{\rEng}Just this one time   let's   let's
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.39,0:15:13.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一切变得太迟之前停手吧\N{\rEng}all stop before it's too late   huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.90,0:15:18.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,孩子  你看起来没有明白\N{\rEng}Son   you don't seem to understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.20,0:15:20.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜  必须死\N{\rEng}Britney Spears... has to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.70,0:15:23.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}Huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.48,0:15:25.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你以为所有这些\N{\rEng}What do you think all
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.56,0:15:27.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,努力都是为了什么\N{\rEng}this effort has been for?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.37,0:15:29.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不可能停手的\N{\rEng}It cannot be stopped.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.06,0:15:32.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们的动机非常崇高\N{\rEng}The purpose is too great.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.43,0:15:34.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她必须  死\N{\rEng}She must... die.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.54,0:15:51.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小斯坦利又累又饿\N{\rEng}Little Stanley was tired and hungry.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.54,0:15:53.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是他知道\N{\rEng}But he knew that for
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.48,0:15:55.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为了小甜甜的安全\N{\rEng}Britney Spears to be safe  
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.50,0:15:58.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他必须把她带到北极\N{\rEng}he had to get her to the North Pole.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.62,0:16:00.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吧  斯皮尔斯小姐\N{\rEng}You doing okay   Ms. Spears?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.38,0:16:05.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是她\N{\rEng}It's her.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.67,0:16:07.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  我确定是小甜甜\N{\rEng}Um no   I'm sure it's Britney Spears;
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.20,0:16:08.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,跟照片一模一样\N{\rEng}it looks just like the picture.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.46,0:16:13.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你要我干  什么\N{\rEng}You want me to   to what?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.06,0:16:15.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我明白\N{\rEng}Yes   I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.73,0:16:26.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你好  我是鲍勃·撒默尔\N{\rEng}Hello   I'm Bob Summers  
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.98,0:16:27.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就是今天吗\N{\rEng}It's today the day?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.33,0:16:29.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么回事\N{\rEng}What is going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.28,0:16:31.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你们都想要小甜甜死\N{\rEng}Why do you want Britney Spears to die?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.30,0:16:33.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没人想要她死  小男孩\N{\rEng}Well nobody wants her to die   little boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.62,0:16:36.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是  需要她死\N{\rEng}We all simply... need her to.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.68,0:16:38.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-你明白嘛  -不\N{\rEng}- Do you understand?  - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.25,0:16:40.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,听着  小孩\N{\rEng}Look   kid  
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.71,0:16:42.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,历史上的任何时代\N{\rEng}throughout history people have
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.03,0:16:44.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,人们都意识到\N{\rEng}found it necessary to engage in...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.65,0:16:46.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,人体祭品的必要性\N{\rEng}human sacrifice.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.48,0:16:48.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在古代  人们总是\N{\rEng}In ancient times   humans would commonly
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.95,0:16:50.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,选出一个可爱的女孩  用珠宝\N{\rEng}pick one lovely girl   adorn her
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.73,0:16:52.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,把她打扮得像女神一样\N{\rEng}with jewels   treat her like a goddess  
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.85,0:16:54.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,然后   看着她去死\N{\rEng}and then... watch her die.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.11,0:16:56.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们总以为自己\N{\rEng}We americans like to think we're
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.74,0:16:58.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在已经文明得多了\N{\rEng}more civilized now  
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.17,0:16:59.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但事实是我们对\N{\rEng}but the truth is our
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.23,0:17:00.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,折磨和死亡的嗜好\N{\rEng}lust for torture and death
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.60,0:17:01.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,跟角斗士时代\N{\rEng}is no different than
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.53,0:17:02.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没有区别\N{\rEng}it was in gladiator times.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.99,0:17:04.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,唯一的区别是\N{\rEng}Only difference is that
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.29,0:17:05.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们喜欢\N{\rEng}now we like to watch people
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.41,0:17:06.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,用杂志和照片\N{\rEng}put to death through
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.53,0:17:07.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来处死人\N{\rEng}magazines and photographs.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.10,0:17:09.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真他妈的可惜\N{\rEng}It's a damn shame too.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.60,0:17:11.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,古代的方式好得多\N{\rEng}Old ways were better.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.42,0:17:12.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,以前是抽签挑出人选\N{\rEng}Used to be we just picked someone
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.99,0:17:14.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,然后用石头把他们砸死\N{\rEng}by lottery and then stoned them to death.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.17,0:17:19.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,美国人不想再用石头砸死人\N{\rEng}No, the american people don't want to stone people to death any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.22,0:17:21.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还是让祭品自杀最好\N{\rEng}Best have the sacrifice kill itself.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.48,0:17:22.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你是说每个人\N{\rEng}You mean everyone has been
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.68,0:17:24.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,都想让小甜甜自杀\N{\rEng}wanting Britney Spears to kill herself?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.44,0:17:26.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小甜甜很早前就被选出来了\N{\rEng}Britney was chosen a long time ago  
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.82,0:17:28.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们捧她  崇拜她\N{\rEng}to be built up and adored  
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.45,0:17:30.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,然后为了丰收  献祭她\N{\rEng}and then sacrificed. For harvest.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.89,0:17:38.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们在哪儿  不太对劲啊\N{\rEng}Hey   where are we? This isn't right.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.76,0:17:44.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\rEng}Oh no!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.61,0:17:46.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快走  小甜甜\N{\rEng}Come on   Britney!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.46,0:17:49.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快  快\N{\rEng}Come on   come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.71,0:18:22.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,妈  爸\N{\rEng}Mom   Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.01,0:18:23.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们要杀她\N{\rEng}They're gonna kill her!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.96,0:18:24.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们要\N{\rEng}They're going to in-
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.78,0:18:26.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,慢着  你们在这里干什么\N{\rEng}Wait   what are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.84,0:18:29.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,全美人民都有参与  凯尔\N{\rEng}It's all of america, Kyle. We're all a part of this together.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.65,0:18:32.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们都知道这一切\N{\rEng}You know all about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.43,0:18:35.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  到底他妈的发生什么事情了\N{\rEng}Kyle   what the fuck is going on now?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.43,0:18:36.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她被捧成明星\N{\rEng}She's been built up
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.29,0:18:37.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是用来做祭品的  斯坦\N{\rEng}to be sacrificed   Stan!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.85,0:18:39.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,祭品  为了什么\N{\rEng}Sacrificed? For what?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.60,0:18:41.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为了丰收  斯坦利\N{\rEng}For harvest   Stanley.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.16,0:18:42.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,永恒不变的动机\N{\rEng}Same reason we've always done it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.14,0:18:44.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,祭祀三月里\N{\rEng}Sacrifice in March  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.94,0:18:46.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,丰收玉米地\N{\rEng}corn have plenty starch.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.52,0:18:48.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,玉米丰收\N{\rEng}Corn harvest!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.98,0:18:50.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们一直没有告诉过你\N{\rEng}We haven't told you about it  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.22,0:18:51.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,斯坦利  因为我们\N{\rEng}Stanley   because we  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.04,0:18:53.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们想等到孩子们\N{\rEng}we like to wait until kids are
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.54,0:18:55.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,长大一些再跟他们\N{\rEng}a little older to talk to them about
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.36,0:18:57.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谈论避孕套和\N{\rEng}things like condoms and ritualistic
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.61,0:18:59.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,丰收人体祭品等话题\N{\rEng}human sacrifice for harvest.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.14,0:19:01.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,够了\N{\rEng}All right   enough already!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.99,0:19:04.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这件事已经持续得太久了\N{\rEng}This has all gone on long enough!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.71,0:19:05.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这个小孩说得对\N{\rEng}The kid is right.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.99,0:19:07.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,已经拖得太久了\N{\rEng}This has gone on too long.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.83,0:19:10.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  她早就应该\N{\rEng}Yeah. She was supposed to
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.16,0:19:11.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,自行了断了\N{\rEng}have killed herself a long time ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.92,0:19:14.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,丰收季节都快到了\N{\rEng}And harvest is coming soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.22,0:19:14.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  大伙\N{\rEng}All right   folks  
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.97,0:19:17.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们快来做个了断\N{\rEng}let's finish this quickly.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.29,0:19:27.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,慢着  住手\N{\rEng}No wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.65,0:19:40.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快  快点\N{\rEng}Come on   hurry up.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.24,0:19:40.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我跑不动\N{\rEng}I can't run.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.99,0:19:42.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们快上  我后排跟进\N{\rEng}You go ahead   I'll catch up with ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.72,0:19:53.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,给  戴维\N{\rEng}Here Davey.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.38,0:20:08.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,停手\N{\rEng}Hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.03,0:20:13.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她死了\N{\rEng}She's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.39,0:20:16.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想  现在是时候\N{\rEng}Well   I think it's time for
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.39,0:20:19.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不再打扰这个可怜的女孩了\N{\rEng}us to leave the poor girl alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.13,0:21:01.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-早  比尔  -早  吉尔\N{\rEng}- Morning   Bill.  - Morning   Gil.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.20,0:21:02.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,漂亮的玉米\N{\rEng}Nice-looking corn.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.45,0:21:11.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,莎朗  兰迪   收成好吧\N{\rEng}Hey Sharon   Randy   great harvest   huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.12,0:21:12.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,难以置信的好收成\N{\rEng}An incredible harvest.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.46,0:21:14.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,多年不见这么好的玉米了\N{\rEng}Some of the best corn I've seen in years.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.92,0:21:16.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-她是个乡村歌手的女儿  -快看\N{\rEng}- She's the daughter of a country singer  - Hey   check it out!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.03,0:21:18.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这个少女\N{\rEng}and the young girl has really
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.38,0:21:20.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,风靡了全国\N{\rEng}taken the country by storm.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.50,0:21:22.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,汉纳.蒙塔纳的主演米莉.塞勒斯\N{\rEng}Hannah Montana's Miley Cyrus
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.85,0:21:24.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,虽然只有15岁\N{\rEng}though only fifteen years old  
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.60,0:21:25.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但已经是冉冉上升的\N{\rEng}is already on her way
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.42,0:21:27.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,明日巨星了\N{\rEng}to being a major superstar.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.60,0:21:30.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看起来下一次的收成\N{\rEng}Looks like next harvest
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.95,0:21:32.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还会更好\N{\rEng}will be even better.
