[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2008-10-23 08:34:58
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayDepth: 0
PlayResX: 1916
PlayResY: 1076
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 2
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H19000000,&H000E0300,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,2,2,134,120,68,1
Style: eng,Microsoft YaHei,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,26,1
Style: Top,微软雅黑,10,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Git,Comic Sans MS,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Chn,微软雅黑,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Eng,Comic Sans MS,60,&H002AF7FF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.20,0:00:11.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm going down to south park\N gonna have myself a time 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.05,0:00:15.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Friendly faces everywhere\N humble folks without temptation 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.33,0:00:18.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Going down to south park\N gonna leave my woes behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.72,0:00:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ample parking day or night\N people shouting howdy neighbor
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.96,0:00:24.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heading on out to south park\N gonna see if I can't unwind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.54,0:00:28.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I like girls with big vaginas\N I like girls with big fat titties
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.61,0:00:31.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.00,0:21:43.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译制作\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}YYeTs人人影视字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.90,0:21:44.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}校译\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}sunflo
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.90,0:21:45.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1c&HFDC282&}后期\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}csbeyond
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.60,0:00:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0150,,{\1c&HFDC282&}南方公园  第12季第3集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.60,0:00:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0100,,大波霸\N{\rEng}"Major Boobage"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.56,0:00:37.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,同学们  今天我们有很严肃的\N{\rEng}Okay  kids  we have something very
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:39.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,事情需要讨论  好嘛\N{\rEng}serious we need to discuss today  m'kay.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.86,0:00:41.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有的学生似乎在\N{\rEng}It appears that some kids in  school
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.54,0:00:44.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,通过窒息自己来寻找刺激\N{\rEng}are getting high by choking themselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.03,0:00:48.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有人把它称做"窒息游戏"  好嘛\N{\rEng}Some kids call it the choking game  m'kay
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.40,0:00:51.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是窒息自己是不好的  好嘛\N{\rEng}but choking  yourself is bad  m'kay.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.00,0:00:54.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要再这样做了  好嘛\N{\rEng}Don't do that  m'kay.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.30,0:00:56.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,可以窒息自己来嗨\N{\rEng}You can get high from choking yourself?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.73,0:00:59.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,同学们总会尝试\N{\rEng}School children are often experimenting
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.59,0:01:01.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,危险的方法来寻找刺激\N{\rEng}with dangerous ways to get high.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.59,0:01:03.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,例如吸胶水  喝止咳糖浆\N{\rEng}M'kay  like sniffing glue  guzzling
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.89,0:01:06.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,嗅油漆  好嘛\N{\rEng}cough medicine   huffing paint  m'kay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.39,0:01:08.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这些都是不好的  好嘛\N{\rEng}But they're all bad.M'kay?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.76,0:01:11.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我佛罗里达的表哥说\N{\rEng}My cousins in florida said kids
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.05,0:01:13.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们那儿都用猫尿来嗨\N{\rEng}in their school get off of cat pee.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.14,0:01:15.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,猫尿\N{\rEng}Cat pee?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.02,0:01:16.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不可能  猫尿\N{\rEng}That's not true.You can't get
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.05,0:01:17.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能让人嗨呢\N{\rEng}high off of cat urine.Can you?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.75,0:01:20.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,其实不是普通的猫尿\N{\rEng}Well  it's not actually cat urine.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.46,0:01:21.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是公猫\N{\rEng}But male cats  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.70,0:01:23.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,标志自己领地时\N{\rEng}when they're marking their territory  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.80,0:01:25.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,它们会撒浓缩尿液\N{\rEng}spray a concentrated urine
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.44,0:01:27.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来驱赶其他公猫\N{\rEng}to fend off other male cats.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.94,0:01:30.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那会让你很嗨的  好嘛\N{\rEng}And that can get you really high.M'kay?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.66,0:01:34.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,非常  非常嗨  好嘛\N{\rEng}Really  really high  m'kay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.03,0:01:37.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也许不应该\N{\rEng}Probably shouldn't have
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.79,0:01:40.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你们的  好嘛\N{\rEng}told you that just now  m'kay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.19,0:01:42.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那也许是不对的\N{\rEng}That was probably bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.59,0:01:45.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  这样能让我的猫\N{\rEng}All right.This should keep my cat
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.61,0:01:47.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在撒尿时不会移动位置\N{\rEng}in place while he sprays the urine.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.56,0:01:49.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,可怜的米图猫咪\N{\rEng}Yes  poor mitew kitty  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.72,0:01:51.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你现在紧张吗\N{\rEng}are you just so upset right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.24,0:01:54.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们在浪费时间\N{\rEng}You guys are wasting your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.64,0:01:56.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  不可能起作用的\N{\rEng}Yeah  it's not gonna work.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.50,0:01:59.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好  准备好了吗  肯尼\N{\rEng}Okay.You ready  kenny?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.14,0:02:00.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-好了   -好\N{\rEng}- All set!  - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.50,0:02:03.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,把另外一只公猫带过来\N{\rEng}Bring out the other male cat.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.41,0:02:25.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有感觉吗\N{\rEng}Do you feel anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.43,0:02:27.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼  爽吗\N{\rEng}Well  kenny?Are you buzzed?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.38,0:03:50.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,酷  快看\N{\rEng}Cool!Check it out!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.31,0:03:55.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我看得出来你被我女儿\N{\rEng}I see that you are enticed by my
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.43,0:03:58.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,波涛汹涌的双乳吸引\N{\rEng}daughter's awesome  rocking tits.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.03,0:03:58.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.89,0:04:00.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,去跟我女儿在\N{\rEng}Then bathe with my daughter
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.38,0:04:02.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,瓦诺什泉里共享鸳鸯浴吧\N{\rEng}in the fountain of varnoth.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.38,0:04:04.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,用肥皂泡涂满其双乳\N{\rEng}Appease the gods by lathering her boobs
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.43,0:04:06.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,以安抚众神\N{\rEng}with soapy suds.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.13,0:04:08.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\rEng}Okay!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.52,0:04:19.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼  肯尼  醒醒\N{\rEng}Kenny.Kenny  wake up.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.73,0:04:21.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,醒醒  肯尼  你没事吧\N{\rEng}Wake up  kenny.You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.74,0:04:23.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼  慢着\N{\rEng}Kenny!Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.65,0:04:24.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她到哪儿去了\N{\rEng}Where'd she go?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.97,0:04:26.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  猫尿真的让你嗨翻了\N{\rEng}Dude  that cat urine really fucked you up!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.83,0:04:28.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你刚才可真是飘飘欲仙啊\N{\rEng}You were seriously tripping balls.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.48,0:04:29.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈的混蛋\N{\rEng}You fuckin' asshole!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.51,0:04:30.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼  住手\N{\rEng}Agh! Kenny! Knock it off!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.54,0:04:31.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你发什么疯\N{\rEng}What's wrong with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.24,0:04:33.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你就不能让我一个人呆着嘛\N{\rEng}Why couldn't you leave me alone!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.05,0:04:33.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计\N{\rEng}Dude!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.79,0:04:35.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  肯尼  冷静一点\N{\rEng}Dude  kenny  calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.50,0:04:39.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就差一点了\N{\rEng}Oh  I was so close!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.43,0:04:42.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们真该看看她的咪咪\N{\rEng}You should have seen her titties.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.32,0:04:43.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么咪咪\N{\rEng}What titties?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.80,0:04:45.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,咪咪\N{\rEng}The titties!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.23,0:04:47.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那个女孩的  简直是人间极品\N{\rEng}On the girl  they were incredible!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.92,0:04:50.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼  猫在你脸上撒尿后\N{\rEng}Kenny  all you did after the cat peed in your face
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.21,0:04:52.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你就绕着圈地欢呼雀跃\N{\rEng}was start  running around in circles cheering.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.01,0:04:53.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,然后你尖叫着在镇上狂奔\N{\rEng}Yeah  then you ran through town screaming
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.23,0:04:55.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还开始撕你自己的衣服\N{\rEng}and started  tearing off all your clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.19,0:04:59.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就差一点就摸到了\N{\rEng}I almost touched them.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.70,0:05:01.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  我想我们\N{\rEng}Dude  I don't think we should be
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.97,0:05:04.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,最好不要再碰那玩意了\N{\rEng}messing around with that crap anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.70,0:05:07.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,Fox新闻台即将播出\N{\rEng}Next on fox news --
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.65,0:05:09.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,最新的毒品风潮\N{\rEng}it's the newest drug craze
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.43,0:05:12.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在威胁你小孩的生命\N{\rEng}and it's killing your kids!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.03,0:05:13.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,威胁我们小孩的生命\N{\rEng}Killing our kids?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.52,0:05:15.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,整个美国  小孩\N{\rEng}All over america kids are
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.18,0:05:17.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,都在用猫尿来寻求刺激\N{\rEng}getting high on cat urine.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.78,0:05:19.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,通过吸入猫尿\N{\rEng}Huffing cat urine apparently
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.14,0:05:20.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来获得极乐状态\N{\rEng}causes a euphoric state
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.94,0:05:23.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也被称为"芝士"\N{\rEng}and is also referred to as "cheesing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.25,0:05:25.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为什么叫"芝士"\N{\rEng}Why cheesing?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.26,0:05:27.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,因为做起来很有意思\N{\rEng}[译注:英文芝士火锅fondue与做起来有意思谐音]
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.55,0:05:29.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这个6年级女生说她已经\N{\rEng}This sixth grade girl says she's been
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.48,0:05:32.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,沉溺于吸猫尿几个月了\N{\rEng}snorting cat piss for several months.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.18,0:05:34.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们有时在课间休息时溜出去\N{\rEng}We sometimes sneak out during recess and
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.11,0:05:37.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友(消音)会把她的猫带来\N{\rEng}our friend named "Beep" goes and gets her cats.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.11,0:05:39.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们会"芝士"一整天\N{\rEng}And we'll just cheese all day long.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.89,0:05:41.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  希拉\N{\rEng}Oh  my god!Sheila!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.40,0:05:42.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快来看\N{\rEng}Come look at this!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.43,0:05:43.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么判断你小孩\N{\rEng}So how can you tell if
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.73,0:05:45.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是否在"芝士"\N{\rEng}your child is cheesing?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.23,0:05:46.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,第一  你小孩看起来\N{\rEng}One  your child seems
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.39,0:05:48.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,神情冷漠  心不在焉\N{\rEng}distant   preoccupied.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.09,0:05:49.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,第二  你小孩的脸\N{\rEng}Two  your child's face
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.54,0:05:51.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,闻起来像猫尿\N{\rEng}smells like cat urine.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.04,0:05:53.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,第三  在动物园看老虎的时候\N{\rEng}Three   when you see tigers at the zoo  
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.23,0:05:55.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你小孩会开始磨牙\N{\rEng}your child starts grinding his or her teeth.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.73,0:05:57.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还需要注意你小孩跟同学\N{\rEng}You might also notice by certain phrases
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.80,0:06:00.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,说话时的一些用语  例如\N{\rEng}your child says to school friends  such as --
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.50,0:06:02.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,"嘿  走去吃芝士"\N{\rEng}"hey   let's go cheese."
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.04,0:06:04.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,或者"想吃芝士吗  伙计"\N{\rEng}Or "do you feel like cheesing   guys?"
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.48,0:06:06.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,又或者"我现在让芝士嗨得\N{\rEng}Or "dude  I'm cheesing my
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.54,0:06:08.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真他妈的爽歪歪了"\N{\rEng}f-ing brains out right now."
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.95,0:06:10.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小孩在干这个\N{\rEng}Kids are doing this?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.58,0:06:13.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小孩能够这样做因为那并不违法\N{\rEng}Kids do it because it's  legal.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.56,0:06:16.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在无可挽救之前你们能做什么\N{\rEng}What can you do before it's too late?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.96,0:06:19.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须保护我们孩子\N{\rEng}We have to protect our
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.95,0:06:22.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不受其侵害  希拉\N{\rEng}children from this  sheila.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.94,0:06:26.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,20% 6到12岁的美国学生承认\N{\rEng}20% of american students aged 6 to 12 say
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.56,0:06:29.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们至少一次尝试过"芝士"\N{\rEng}they have tried cheesing at least once.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.56,0:06:31.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小孩也把其称作\N{\rEng}Kids also refer to it as
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.31,0:06:34.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,"芝士游戏"或"维他命芝士"\N{\rEng}"the cheese game  " or "vitamin cheese  "
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.11,0:06:35.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,或"玛丽·珍\N{\rEng}or "mary jane
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.31,0:06:37.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,脸上撒尿欢乐时光"\N{\rEng}piss in your face fun time."
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.41,0:06:39.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,"芝士"在快速的蔓延\N{\rEng}Cheesing is spreading fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.66,0:06:41.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们是真的被吓着了\N{\rEng}All right.We're all sufficiently scared  
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.14,0:06:42.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,杰拉德  我们该怎么办\N{\rEng}Gerald   but what can we do?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.74,0:06:44.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我起草了一个让养猫\N{\rEng}I have written up a bill that would make
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.81,0:06:48.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在南方公园全市非法化的议案\N{\rEng}having a cat illegal  in the city of south park.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.51,0:06:52.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,杰拉德说得对  我们必须要行动了\N{\rEng}Gerald's right.We all have to face it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.29,0:06:54.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,猫是致命的动物\N{\rEng}Cats are deadly animals.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.22,0:06:55.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果你把鼻子伸到它们的胯部\N{\rEng}If you stick your nose up their crotch
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.71,0:06:58.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吸它们的猫尿  你就死定了\N{\rEng}and snort their piss  they can kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.41,0:07:00.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,以我超级大律师的能力\N{\rEng}With my super lawyer powers
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.11,0:07:01.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以把猫从镇上赶尽杀绝\N{\rEng}we can rid our town of cats
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.91,0:07:03.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们小孩就\N{\rEng}so that our kids can
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.16,0:07:05.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,再也没法嗨了\N{\rEng}never get high again!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.79,0:07:08.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让我们都来支持杰拉德\N{\rEng}Let's hear it for gerald!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.20,0:07:11.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,都来支持杰拉德啊\N{\rEng}Let's hear it for gerald!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.30,0:07:20.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\rEng}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.18,0:07:21.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊\N{\rEng}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.87,0:07:25.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快戒了吧  瘾君子  上帝啊\N{\rEng}Get over it druggie.Jeez!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.09,0:07:28.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,再见  挠挠猫  我们会想你的\N{\rEng}Goodbye  scrambles.We'll miss you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.94,0:07:34.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这儿有两只\N{\rEng}Got two here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.67,0:07:36.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们他妈的要干什么\N{\rEng}Hey  what the fuck are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.37,0:07:37.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  这些猫是不合法的\N{\rEng}Sorry  these are illegal.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.97,0:07:38.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.53,0:07:39.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\rEng}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.28,0:07:40.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们要干什么\N{\rEng}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.20,0:07:43.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  操你妈\N{\rEng}Hey  fuck You!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.67,0:07:46.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我说过了  我是有过猫\N{\rEng}Look  I told you.I had a cat.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.55,0:07:47.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但它太不老实了  所以\N{\rEng}But I had it put to sleep because
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.81,0:07:49.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我把它安乐死了\N{\rEng}it pissed me off.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.58,0:07:54.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,嘘\N{\rEng}Shhh.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.47,0:07:55.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,米图猫咪 你现在\N{\rEng}Mitew kitty  you have to
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.15,0:07:56.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,必须住在阁楼里\N{\rEng}live in the attic for now.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.95,0:07:57.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来\N{\rEng}Here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.74,0:07:59.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,写日记吧\N{\rEng}Write a diary.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.34,0:08:05.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们  看见肯尼了没\N{\rEng}Guys  have you seen kenny?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.66,0:08:07.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没  肯尼好像今天生病了没来\N{\rEng}No  I think kenny's out sick today.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.50,0:08:09.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他昨天也生病了没来\N{\rEng}Yeah  and he was out sick yesterday too.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.08,0:08:14.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们  我猜肯尼之所以没来\N{\rEng}Guys   I think kenny isn't here
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.01,0:08:16.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是因为躲在家里"芝士"\N{\rEng}because he's at home cheesing.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.72,0:08:18.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会\N{\rEng}Aw   come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.73,0:08:21.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼知道"芝士"的危险性\N{\rEng}Kenny knows how dangerous cheesing is.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.24,0:08:22.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  而且他也没有猫\N{\rEng}Yeah  and where's he gonna find cats anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.57,0:08:23.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,猫都被抓走了\N{\rEng}They've been outlawed.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.57,0:08:27.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  谁现在还有猫啊\N{\rEng}Yeah  who has cats these days?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.01,0:08:28.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大麻也是非法的\N{\rEng}Pot's illegal too but
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.13,0:08:29.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还不是能弄到\N{\rEng}people still manage to find it!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.93,0:08:31.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼从第一次"芝士"了后\N{\rEng}Ever since that first time kenny
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.52,0:08:33.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就一直不对劲\N{\rEng}cheesed he hasn't been the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.52,0:08:35.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们都注意到他的变化了吧\N{\rEng}You've all noticed the change in him!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.57,0:08:37.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我敢打赌肯尼一定\N{\rEng}I'll bet kenny is home
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.55,0:08:39.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,正在家"芝士"\N{\rEng}cheesing right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.98,0:09:38.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼\N{\rEng}Kenny?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.45,0:09:40.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼  你在家吗\N{\rEng}Kenny  you home?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.50,0:09:52.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼\N{\rEng}Kenny?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.88,0:09:57.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天  他已经"芝士"疯了\N{\rEng}Oh  boy.He's cheesed out his mind!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.05,0:10:06.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼\N{\rEng}Kenny
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.42,0:10:10.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,给\N{\rEng}There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.49,0:10:12.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,喝点咖啡  肯\N{\rEng}Try some coffee  ken.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.16,0:10:18.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼  我们必须谈谈了\N{\rEng}Kenny  we need to have a serious talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.90,0:10:20.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不想谈\N{\rEng}No  we don't  guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.50,0:10:21.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,必须要\N{\rEng}Yes  we do.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.70,0:10:22.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们是你朋友  伙计\N{\rEng}We're your friends  dude.And we're
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.74,0:10:24.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能看着你毁掉\N{\rEng}not gonna let you ruin your life.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.24,0:10:25.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不会毁掉的\N{\rEng}I'm not ruining my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.89,0:10:28.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们他妈的就不能不管我吗\N{\rEng}Will you guys just back the fuck Off?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.12,0:10:29.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看看你自己\N{\rEng}Look at yourself!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.32,0:10:31.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你不能再"芝士"了\N{\rEng}You've got to lay off the cheese!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.72,0:10:37.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  小兄弟\N{\rEng}Yeah  that's it  little buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.34,0:10:38.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,尽管吐吧\N{\rEng}Just let it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.91,0:10:39.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼  虽然我们\N{\rEng}Kenny  i know we're super
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.85,0:10:40.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是很好的朋友\N{\rEng}cool and everything  
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.85,0:10:42.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但如果我们再发现你"芝士"\N{\rEng}but if we ever catch you cheesing again
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.42,0:10:44.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们只好告发你了\N{\rEng}we're gonna tell on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.02,0:10:45.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  好吧\N{\rEng}Ugh  okay.Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.77,0:10:47.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想睡觉了\N{\rEng}I just want to sleep now.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.06,0:10:48.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  他需要\N{\rEng}Yeah  he needs some sleepy
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.34,0:10:50.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,睡觉觉了\N{\rEng}night-night  doesn't the buddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.88,0:10:54.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须把猫带走\N{\rEng}We gotta keep this away from him.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.61,0:11:05.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,米图猫咪  嘘\N{\rEng}Mitew kitty!Shhhh!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.21,0:11:07.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,该死的\N{\rEng}Dammit!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.33,0:11:11.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,米图猫咪  安静\N{\rEng}Mitew kitty  you have to be quiet
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.25,0:11:13.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不然你会被他们发现的\N{\rEng}or else they're gonna find you!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.96,0:11:16.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.65,0:11:20.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,隔壁的猫\N{\rEng}The neighbor cat.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.76,0:11:22.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还没被抓走\N{\rEng}He hasn't been caught yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.72,0:11:24.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  不行  米图猫咪\N{\rEng}No  no  mitew kitty.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.89,0:11:25.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你喜欢鲁佛斯  但是\N{\rEng}I know you like rufus  but
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.95,0:11:27.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他必须自谋出路\N{\rEng}he  has to fend for himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.56,0:11:30.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不能再藏更多的猫了  米图猫咪\N{\rEng}I can't hide anymore cats  mitew kitty.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.40,0:11:32.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的麻烦已经够多了\N{\rEng}I'm in trouble enough as it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.24,0:11:35.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  好吧  好吧\N{\rEng}All right  all right.Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.95,0:11:41.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  鲁佛斯  轻点\N{\rEng}All right  come on  rufus.Quietly.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.01,0:11:48.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上帝  我没法都收容你们\N{\rEng}Oh  jesus  no!No  I can't hide you all!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.63,0:11:51.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉  你们必须\N{\rEng}I'm sorry.You'll just have
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.54,0:11:53.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,到其他地方\N{\rEng}to find somewhere else to --
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.81,0:11:58.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,算了  我想四只猫和两只猫\N{\rEng}Well  i suppose I'll get in just as
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.66,0:12:00.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,带来的麻烦也没多大的区别\N{\rEng}much trouble for four cats as for two.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.96,0:12:02.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\rEng}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.75,0:12:14.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,啊\N{\rEng}Huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.32,0:12:20.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上帝\N{\rEng}Oh  my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.31,0:12:22.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔\N{\rEng}Kyle?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.60,0:12:23.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  我们能\N{\rEng}Kyle  can we talk to you
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.75,0:12:25.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,跟你谈一谈嘛\N{\rEng}for a minute  please?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.10,0:12:27.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么事\N{\rEng}Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.07,0:12:30.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  你最近有在嗨吗\N{\rEng}Kyle  have you been getting high?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.27,0:12:31.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\rEng}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.17,0:12:32.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么你妈妈在你\N{\rEng}Then why did your mother find
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.77,0:12:35.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,放衣服的抽屉里发现这个\N{\rEng}this in your dressing drawer?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.05,0:12:39.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  听着  这不是我的\N{\rEng}All right.Look  that isn't mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.97,0:12:41.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我只是帮一个朋友保管\N{\rEng}I'm just holding it for a friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.52,0:12:43.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要对我们撒谎  凯尔\N{\rEng}Don't lie to us  kyle!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.16,0:12:45.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你"芝士"有多久了\N{\rEng}How long have you been on the cheese?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.75,0:12:47.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我没有在"芝士"\N{\rEng}I'm not cheesing!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.72,0:12:49.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我一次都没有"芝士"过\N{\rEng}I've never cheesed once in my life!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.43,0:12:51.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,回你的房间呆着去\N{\rEng}Get up to your room right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.18,0:12:52.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,直到你妈妈和我商量\N{\rEng}Until your mother and I figure
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.39,0:12:53.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好怎么处理这件事\N{\rEng}out how to deal with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.59,0:12:54.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,爸  你就不能\N{\rEng}Dad  will you just listen
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.41,0:12:55.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,冷静听我说吗\N{\rEng}to me for a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.21,0:12:56.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在就去  凯尔\N{\rEng}Now  kyle!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.66,0:12:58.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上帝\N{\rEng}God!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.75,0:13:00.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,杰拉德  我们怎么办\N{\rEng}Gerald  what are we gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.48,0:13:02.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们儿子是猫尿瘾君子\N{\rEng}Our son is a cat pee addict!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.22,0:13:04.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们先要把这个处理掉\N{\rEng}First thing is we've got to  dispose of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.74,0:13:05.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你准备怎么做\N{\rEng}What are you going to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.69,0:13:07.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我现在最好先把它\N{\rEng}I better just take it down
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.23,0:13:08.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,关到地下室去\N{\rEng}to the basement for now.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.43,0:13:10.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让凯尔找不到它\N{\rEng}Make sure kyle can't find it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.11,0:13:17.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  我在想什么啊\N{\rEng}No  no.What am i thinking?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.90,0:13:19.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不应该这样做\N{\rEng}I shouldn't don't this.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.53,0:13:23.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我已经有10年没有嗨过了\N{\rEng}I've been clean for ten years.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.08,0:13:25.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我甚至连猫都没有接近过\N{\rEng}I haven't even been near a cat.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.25,0:13:26.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,然后有报道说\N{\rEng}But then that report said
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.42,0:13:28.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们小孩也在这样做\N{\rEng}our  kids were doing it  too.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.02,0:13:29.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道凯尔会染上\N{\rEng}I knew kyle would have the same
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.37,0:13:31.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,跟我曾经一样的病态\N{\rEng}sickness as I used to have.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.37,0:13:33.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们家里有一只猫\N{\rEng}Now a cat is in our home
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.08,0:13:35.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,实在是太有诱惑力了\N{\rEng}and it's too tempting.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.48,0:13:41.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我  我最后再来一次\N{\rEng}I  I'll just do it one more time.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.73,0:13:43.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,最后一次\N{\rEng}One last time.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.78,0:13:45.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,然后我会通知警察\N{\rEng}Then I'll call the police  
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.23,0:13:47.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让他们带走这只猫\N{\rEng}have them pick up the cat.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.43,0:13:49.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我会彻底金盆洗手\N{\rEng}And I'll never do it again.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.60,0:13:54.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在这最后一次之后\N{\rEng}After this one last time.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.97,0:15:02.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我没法拒绝诱惑\N{\rEng}I couldn't stay away.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.91,0:15:06.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,都怪你波涛汹涌的咪咪\N{\rEng}Curse your rockin' tits.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.40,0:15:09.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-谁  -请开门\N{\rEng}- Who is it?  - Please  open the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.08,0:15:13.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有人说你在收容猫\N{\rEng}They say you're hiding cats!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.78,0:15:17.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,收容猫  那可是违法的\N{\rEng}Hiding cats?That would be illegal!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.73,0:15:18.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你没明白\N{\rEng}You don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.97,0:15:20.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的小尼希卡\N{\rEng}My little nishka  
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.25,0:15:22.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她别无所去了\N{\rEng}she has nowhere else to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.45,0:15:24.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  我没法\N{\rEng}Oh  no!No  I cannot possibly
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.32,0:15:25.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,再收容更多了\N{\rEng}take in another.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.32,0:15:26.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话他们会抓走她的\N{\rEng}But they will find her.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.76,0:15:27.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我已经收容了安德森\N{\rEng}I've already taken in the
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.87,0:15:29.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,和沃利斯基的猫了\N{\rEng}anderson's cats  the wolitsky's.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.57,0:15:32.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我真的无能为力\N{\rEng}There is simply nothing else I can --
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.70,0:15:37.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不过  也许我还能腾出\N{\rEng}then again  perhaps I could find
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.10,0:15:39.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,空间再容纳一只\N{\rEng}space for just this one more.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.00,0:15:41.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你在如此黑暗的时代\N{\rEng}Oh  you show such kindness
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.60,0:15:43.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,展现了如此耀眼的光辉\N{\rEng}in such darkest of times.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.23,0:15:53.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我靠\N{\rEng}What the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.02,0:16:01.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼  滚出去\N{\rEng}Kenny  get outta here!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.48,0:16:05.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,靠  肯尼\N{\rEng}Oh  crap!Kenny!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.68,0:16:08.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,坏猫咪\N{\rEng}Bad kitties.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.55,0:16:15.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,爸  有人在按门铃\N{\rEng}Dad!Somebody's at the front door!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.89,0:16:19.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我到底是不是被关禁闭了\N{\rEng}Well  am I grounded or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.60,0:16:22.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我来开门\N{\rEng}Fine!I'll get it!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.49,0:16:26.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  我们有大麻烦了\N{\rEng}Dude  we've got a big problem!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.31,0:16:28.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,卡特曼说肯尼糟透了\N{\rEng}Cartman says kenny is really messed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.37,0:16:31.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他已经"芝士"得神志不清了\N{\rEng}He's cheesing his fucking balls off  dude!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.29,0:16:32.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.42,0:16:34.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他把所有卡特曼藏在阁楼\N{\rEng}He apparently got to all the cats
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.05,0:16:35.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,里的猫都用来嗨了\N{\rEng}cartman's been hiding in his attic.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.84,0:16:36.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你把猫藏在阁楼\N{\rEng}What are you doing with
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.62,0:16:37.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,里干什么  死胖子\N{\rEng}cats in your attic  fat ass?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.82,0:16:39.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们是无辜的受害者  凯尔\N{\rEng}They're innocent victims in this  kyle!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.68,0:16:40.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不把他们藏起来的话\N{\rEng}They have to hide or
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.36,0:16:41.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们会被处死的\N{\rEng}they'll be put to death.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.16,0:16:43.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你不会明白的\N{\rEng}Something you just can't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.95,0:16:45.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快  我们必须在肯尼\N{\rEng}Come on.We gotta find kenny
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.91,0:16:47.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,毁了他自己之前找到他\N{\rEng}before he hurts himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.11,0:16:49.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我走不了  我爸把我关禁闭了\N{\rEng}I can't!My dad grounded me!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.46,0:16:51.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对了\N{\rEng}Wait a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.25,0:16:52.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我爸到哪儿去了\N{\rEng}Where is my dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.68,0:17:02.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大家好\N{\rEng}Hey  everybody!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.62,0:17:04.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,再见到你们真高兴啊\N{\rEng}Good to seeya again!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.18,0:17:16.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,慢着\N{\rEng}Hold!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.54,0:17:18.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你现在还不能抚摸\N{\rEng}You cannot yet caress my
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.57,0:17:20.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我女儿傲人的乳房\N{\rEng}daughter's awesome boobage.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.17,0:17:22.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\rEng}How come?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.91,0:17:27.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还有一个求爱者\N{\rEng}There is another suitor.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.78,0:17:29.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.93,0:17:31.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快滚蛋  小屁孩\N{\rEng}Get outta here  kid!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.46,0:17:33.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  你滚蛋  那个女孩是我的\N{\rEng}Dude  You!That's my girl!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.48,0:17:35.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你还太年轻了\N{\rEng}You're too young for this stuff!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.44,0:17:37.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们必须在乳头山的\N{\rEng}This must be decided in the
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.07,0:17:40.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,乳房殿里一决雌雄\N{\rEng}breastriary in nipopolis!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.50,0:17:54.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上吧  为了"波霸杯"而战\N{\rEng}Now fight!For the locknar trophy!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.12,0:18:36.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,爸\N{\rEng}Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.91,0:18:39.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,爸  你到底在干什么\N{\rEng}Dad!What the hell are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.31,0:18:40.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们这样扭打\N{\rEng}They been going at it
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.33,0:18:42.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,足足有30分钟了\N{\rEng}for a good 30 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.13,0:18:44.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她是我的  你这个小杂碎\N{\rEng}She's mine  you little asshole!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.14,0:18:46.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他妈的快滚开\N{\rEng}Get the fuck off me!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.76,0:18:48.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,杰拉德\N{\rEng}Gerald?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.99,0:18:52.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,禁猫令的主要提议者被控告\N{\rEng}The key proponent of the cat ban has been
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.20,0:18:54.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在公共场所"芝士"\N{\rEng}charged with cheesing in a public park.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.60,0:18:56.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,杰拉德·布罗夫洛夫斯基准备\N{\rEng}Gerald broflovski is prepared
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.05,0:18:58.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,发表一个公众声明\N{\rEng}to give a public statement.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.72,0:19:00.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想就一个私人事件\N{\rEng}I would like to address a
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.02,0:19:01.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,发表声明\N{\rEng}personal matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.22,0:19:03.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我放纵了自己堕落  首先\N{\rEng}I have let myself down and I would first
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.75,0:19:06.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我要向我亲爱的太太道歉\N{\rEng}like to apologize to my lovely wife --
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.00,0:19:07.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要碰我\N{\rEng}Don't touch me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.30,0:19:09.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,向南方公园所有人道歉\N{\rEng}And to the people of south park.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.31,0:19:10.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我错了\N{\rEng}I was wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.55,0:19:11.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不能再让猫\N{\rEng}And I can't let cats
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.78,0:19:13.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来承担所有指责了\N{\rEng}take the fall anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.48,0:19:15.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,错的是我们\N{\rEng}It's our fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.06,0:19:16.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是利用他们\N{\rEng}The people who use cats
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.56,0:19:18.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,美妙尿液的人\N{\rEng}for their sweet urine.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.46,0:19:19.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须懂得\N{\rEng}We have to learn that
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.85,0:19:21.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为了"芝士"这样做并不值得\N{\rEng}cheesing just isn't worth it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.95,0:19:24.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  你能够在乳房殿里战斗\N{\rEng}Sure  you get to fight in the breastriary
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.31,0:19:26.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在瓦诺什泉里和\N{\rEng}and swim in the fountains of varnoth with
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.48,0:19:28.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,熟女山的波霸仙女共泳\N{\rEng}the  ittytitty fairies of mamary mountain.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.78,0:19:30.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他到底在说什么\N{\rEng}What the hell is he talking  about?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.28,0:19:31.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,毫无头绪\N{\rEng}I have no idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.67,0:19:33.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,然后在格撒格斯山洞\N{\rEng}And then you fight the boobgoblin
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.24,0:19:34.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,和乳妖战斗\N{\rEng}in the gazangas cave.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.83,0:19:37.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,然后你可能会赢得女孩的感激\N{\rEng}And then the girl may thank you for it
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.10,0:19:39.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是她  是不真实的\N{\rEng}but she isn't real.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.50,0:19:40.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何  你永远不可能看到\N{\rEng}And you never really get a good
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.63,0:19:43.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她裸露的双乳\N{\rEng}look at her naked boobs anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.49,0:19:45.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,问题在于  那个世界\N{\rEng}Problem is the more you go into that world
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.73,0:19:47.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,会让你越陷越深\N{\rEng}the more you need to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.73,0:19:49.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,直到你失去\N{\rEng}Until you start blowing off all
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.13,0:19:51.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,身边真正关心你的人\N{\rEng}the real people who care about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.83,0:19:54.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  说得对\N{\rEng}Yeah  I guess so.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.63,0:19:56.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,猫不是问题的所在\N{\rEng}Cats aren't the problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.59,0:19:58.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们把猫非法化  但我却\N{\rEng}We made cats illegal and then I
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.39,0:20:00.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,10年来第一次"芝士"\N{\rEng}cheesed for the first time in ten years.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.79,0:20:02.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们总是会\N{\rEng}And kids are always going to
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.13,0:20:03.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,找到新的刺激\N{\rEng}find a new way to get high.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.73,0:20:05.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,例如吸胶水  舔癞蛤蟆\N{\rEng}Like sniffing glue or licking  toads
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.93,0:20:08.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,发酵大便  嗅油漆\N{\rEng}or fermenting feces or  huffing paint.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.33,0:20:08.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还可以\N{\rEng}You can also
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.92,0:20:11.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  够了  杰拉德\N{\rEng}Okay  that's probably good  gerald.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.42,0:20:13.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想说的是我错了\N{\rEng}The point is I was wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.37,0:20:17.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是该合法化猫的时候了\N{\rEng}It's time to legalize cats.Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.52,0:20:18.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伟大的杰拉德\N{\rEng}Hooray for gerald!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.72,0:20:21.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们都来支持杰拉德\N{\rEng}Let's hear it for gerald!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.05,0:20:27.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,挠挠猫\N{\rEng}Scrambles!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.97,0:20:29.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你回来了真好\N{\rEng}So good to have you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.53,0:20:31.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你不会记我们仇吧\N{\rEng}You ain't sore at us  are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.64,0:20:37.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真高兴一切都结束了\N{\rEng}I'm sure glad that's over with.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.16,0:20:38.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N{\rEng}Me too.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.57,0:20:39.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,知道嘛  我们都\N{\rEng}But you know  we've all
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.63,0:20:40.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,应该有所领悟\N{\rEng}learned something  you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.63,0:20:42.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能迫害生命\N{\rEng}We can never persecute living beings and
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.21,0:20:44.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,逼迫他们东躲西藏  这是不对的\N{\rEng}force them into hidinvel it's wrong
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.39,0:20:47.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你难道没发现这跟历史\N{\rEng}And you don't see any  parallel between
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.08,0:20:48.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,中的某些事件很相似吗\N{\rEng}that and  anything else in history?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.02,0:20:50.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\rEng}nope.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.68,0:20:51.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我完全不知道\N{\rEng}I have no idea what
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.71,0:20:52.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么  凯尔\N{\rEng}you're talking about   Kyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.71,0:20:54.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们  快看\N{\rEng}You guys!Check it out!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.56,0:20:56.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼\N{\rEng}It's kenny.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.15,0:20:59.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真是太好了\N{\rEng}Isn't that great?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.26,0:21:01.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他开始真正享受生活了\N{\rEng}he's just getting high on life
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.16,0:21:02.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.42,0:21:09.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他真的是很享受啊\N{\rEng}He's getting really high on life.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.53,0:21:15.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  他已经被废掉了\N{\rEng}Dude  he's getting super wasted on life.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.19,0:21:17.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼\N{\rEng}Kenny!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.53,0:21:20.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这他妈的是什么花\N{\rEng}What the hell kind of flowers are those?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.39,0:21:21.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼\N{\rEng}Kenny?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.39,0:21:22.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼\N{\rEng}Kenny?
