[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2008-10-30 08:43:29
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayDepth: 0
PlayResX: 1916
PlayResY: 1076
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 2
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H19000000,&H000E0300,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,2,2,134,120,68,1
Style: eng,Microsoft YaHei,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,26,1
Style: Top,微软雅黑,10,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Git,Comic Sans MS,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Chn,微软雅黑,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Eng,Comic Sans MS,60,&H002AF7FF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.20,0:00:11.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm going down to south park\N gonna have myself a time 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.05,0:00:15.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Friendly faces everywhere\N humble folks without temptation 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.33,0:00:18.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Going down to south park\N gonna leave my woes behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.72,0:00:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ample parking day or night\N people shouting howdy neighbor
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.96,0:00:24.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heading on out to south park\N gonna see if I can't unwind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.54,0:00:28.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I like girls with big vaginas\N I like girls with big fat titties
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.61,0:00:31.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.00,0:21:46.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译制作\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}YYeTs人人影视字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.00,0:21:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}校译\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Tina sunflo
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.00,0:21:49.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1c&HFDC282&}后期\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}csbeyond
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.00,0:00:31.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0150,,{\1c&HFDC282&}南方公园  第12季第4集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.00,0:00:31.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0100,,加拿大罢工\N{\rEng}Canada on Strike
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.99,0:00:39.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,同学们  请安静点  好吗\N{\rEng}Students   quiet please   m'kay.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.67,0:00:41.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们可能已经知道了\N{\rEng}As you may or may not know  
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.25,0:00:44.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,今天是加拿大感恩节\N{\rEng}Today is Canada Appreciation Day.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.59,0:00:47.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老天  我已经觉得无聊了\N{\rEng}Oh   God   I'm bored already!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.79,0:00:49.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好嘛  全球加拿大办公署\N{\rEng}M'kay   so we've been asked
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.03,0:00:50.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,要求我们\N{\rEng}to show you a video
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.14,0:00:52.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,给你们放一段录像\N{\rEng}From the World Canadian Bureau.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.48,0:00:54.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,请开始吧\N{\rEng}Start the tape   please.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.06,0:00:57.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大家好  我是斯蒂芬·埃布特曼\N{\rEng}Hello   I am Stephen Abootman  
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.02,0:00:59.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,全球加拿大办公署署长\N{\rEng}president of the World Canadian Bureau.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.52,0:01:00.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有想过\N{\rEng}Do you ever stop to think
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.50,0:01:02.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大对全球来说有多重要\N{\rEng}How important Canada is to the world?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.54,0:01:03.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在\N{\rEng}Right now  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.10,0:01:04.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想请本校所有\N{\rEng}I would like all students
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.60,0:01:06.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大籍学生\N{\rEng}Of Canadian descent in this school
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.29,0:01:07.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,起立\N{\rEng}To stand up.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.68,0:01:11.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看看你们学校的\N{\rEng}Just look at all these
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.89,0:01:13.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大精英们\N{\rEng}fine Canadians in your school.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.59,0:01:15.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们是如此多才多艺\N{\rEng}See how diverse they are!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.14,0:01:17.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当你想到加拿大时\N{\rEng}When you think of Canada  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.38,0:01:19.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,脑海里首先浮现的是什么\N{\rEng}What's the one thing that comes to mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.50,0:01:20.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,同性恋\N{\rEng}Gayness!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.18,0:01:25.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  精神\N{\rEng}That's right -- spirit.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.56,0:01:27.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是什么让加拿大如此重要\N{\rEng}What is it that makes Canada so important?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.91,0:01:29.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一无是处\N{\rEng}Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.89,0:01:38.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的加拿大同胞们\N{\rEng}My fellow Canadians.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.44,0:01:39.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,长久以来\N{\rEng}For too long
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.07,0:01:41.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们被欺压奚落\N{\rEng}We have been pushed around and ridiculed.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.47,0:01:43.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,昨天本应是一个\N{\rEng}Yesterday was supposed to be a day of
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.39,0:01:45.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,感恩及理解的日子\N{\rEng}appreciation and understanding.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.29,0:01:46.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,然而\N{\rEng}Instead  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.02,0:01:47.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大感恩节\N{\rEng}Canada Appreciation Day
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.75,0:01:49.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,却被世界嘲弄\N{\rEng}was mocked worldwide!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.60,0:01:54.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没人把我们当回事\N{\rEng}Nobody takes us Canadians seriously!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.57,0:01:56.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们完全不尊重加拿大\N{\rEng}It's like the world don't respect Canada at all!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.98,0:01:57.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.81,0:01:58.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得是时候\N{\rEng}And I think it's time
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.64,0:01:59.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让世界知道\N{\rEng}for Canada to show the world
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.93,0:02:02.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没有加拿大会多么糟糕\N{\rEng}just how bad things would be without it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.01,0:02:03.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起传达一个信息\N{\rEng}Together we can send a message!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.86,0:02:06.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大要罢工\N{\rEng}It's time for Canada to strike!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.73,0:02:10.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你刚刚说罢工吗\N{\rEng}Did you say "strike"?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.23,0:02:11.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对\N{\rEng}Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.06,0:02:12.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所有加拿大人都加入我吧\N{\rEng}Every Canadian join me!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.48,0:02:13.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,团结一致\N{\rEng}Join together.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.39,0:02:15.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大要罢工\N{\rEng}Canada on strike!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.91,0:02:17.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大要罢工\N{\rEng}Canada on strike!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.34,0:02:24.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*加拿大*\N{\rEng}*Canada.*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.04,0:02:25.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*加拿大要罢工*\N{\rEng}*Canada on strike.*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.49,0:02:26.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*加拿大不再沉默*\N{\rEng}*Canada says no more!*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.94,0:02:27.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*拒接轻视*\N{\rEng}*No more neglect.*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.86,0:02:28.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*要求尊重*\N{\rEng}*We want respect.*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.61,0:02:30.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*罢工就为此*\N{\rEng}*That's what we're striking for!*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.19,0:02:31.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*所有官僚与高管*\N{\rEng}*All you bureaucrats and corporate cats*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.74,0:02:33.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*都滚一边去*\N{\rEng}*Can all take a hike!*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.28,0:02:34.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*因为加拿大*\N{\rEng}*It's Canada.*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.74,0:02:36.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*要罢工*\N{\rEng}*On strike!*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.78,0:02:37.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*加拿大要罢工*\N{\rEng}*Canada on strike*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.83,0:02:39.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*从温哥华到圣约翰*\N{\rEng}*From Vancouver to St.John's*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.83,0:02:41.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*竖起中指*\N{\rEng}*We raise our middle fingers*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.31,0:02:42.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*插你屁屁*\N{\rEng}*for you all to sit upon*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.99,0:02:44.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*看你还怎么*\N{\rEng}*and with our fingers up your ass*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.77,0:02:46.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*嚣张盛气*\N{\rEng}*you won't be very psyched*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.07,0:02:49.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*加拿大要罢工*\N{\rEng}*it's Canada on strike*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.13,0:02:50.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我们绝不屈服*\N{\rEng}*and we will not bow or budge*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.92,0:02:52.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我们意志坚定*\N{\rEng}*our resolve is strong*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.66,0:02:53.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们还花了3小时\N{\rEng}we even took three hours
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.97,0:02:55.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*来练习罢工曲*\N{\rEng}*to rehearse this striking song*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.08,0:02:57.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*加拿大要罢工*\N{\rEng}*Canada on strike*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.20,0:02:58.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*不论你在哪*\N{\rEng}*No matter where you are*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.00,0:03:00.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*只要你是加拿大人*\N{\rEng}*if you are Canadian*
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.37,0:03:02.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*就该站出来*\N{\rEng}*then you've got to do your part*
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.30,0:03:03.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*走上大街*\N{\rEng}*March out of the halls*
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.92,0:03:04.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}That's right!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.67,0:03:06.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,舔我的加拿大臭脚丫吧\N{\rEng}Suck my Canadian balls.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.53,0:03:09.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*加拿大要罢工*\N{\rEng}*It's Canada on strike!*
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.73,0:03:12.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*加拿大*\N{\rEng}*It's Canada!*
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.95,0:03:16.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*要罢工*\N{\rEng}*On strike!*
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.48,0:03:20.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你说的\N{\rEng}Uh   when you say :
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.83,0:03:23.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大罢工了\N{\rEng}"Canada is on strike   "
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.05,0:03:25.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么意思\N{\rEng}what exactly do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.26,0:03:26.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你以为是什么意思\N{\rEng}What do you think it means?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.65,0:03:27.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们罢工了  老弟\N{\rEng}We're striking   buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.73,0:03:28.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就这样\N{\rEng}No more!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.14,0:03:29.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,直到我们得到想要的东西\N{\rEng}That's it until we get what we want.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.17,0:03:32.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你以什么身份\N{\rEng}Who exactly are you
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.39,0:03:34.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,批准这次罢工\N{\rEng}to authorize this strike?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.58,0:03:36.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我是斯蒂芬·埃布特曼\N{\rEng}I am stephen abootman  
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.08,0:03:38.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,W.G.A.的头头\N{\rEng}Leader of the W.G.A.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.70,0:03:40.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,W.G.A.\N{\rEng}The W.G.A.?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.48,0:03:41.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.39,0:03:43.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,全球加拿大办公署\N{\rEng}The World Canadian Bureau.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.38,0:03:48.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大究竟想要什么\N{\rEng}What exactly does Canada want?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.65,0:03:51.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们要更多的钱\N{\rEng}We want more money.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.65,0:03:54.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对  更多钱\N{\rEng}Yeah   more money.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.78,0:03:56.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,从哪儿要更多的钱\N{\rEng}More money from where?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.50,0:03:57.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,只要更多钱就行\N{\rEng}Just more money   you know!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.00,0:03:59.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大拿的钱不够多\N{\rEng}Canada doesn't get enough money.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.57,0:04:01.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,其他国家有的是钱\N{\rEng}Other countries have lots of money.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.11,0:04:02.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们要那些钱\N{\rEng}We want some of that money.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.06,0:04:04.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,比如因特网\N{\rEng}How about the internet?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.97,0:04:06.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,因特网能赚很多钱\N{\rEng}The internet makes lots of money.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.34,0:04:07.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,给我们点那些钱\N{\rEng}Give us some of that money.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.92,0:04:09.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对  给我们因特网的钱\N{\rEng}Yeah! Give us internet money!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.79,0:04:11.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,埃布特曼先生\N{\rEng}Mr.Abootman  
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.11,0:04:13.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你似乎不太了解\N{\rEng}you seem to not understand
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.10,0:04:15.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,全球经济是怎么运作的  我想\N{\rEng}how global economics works.I think that...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.11,0:04:17.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,少跟我嚼嘴皮子\N{\rEng}Don't give me that fat cat fancy lip wiggling!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.83,0:04:18.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们到底给不给\N{\rEng}Are you going to give Canada
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.85,0:04:20.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大更多的钱\N{\rEng}more money or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.50,0:04:23.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕不行\N{\rEng}I'm afraid we can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.25,0:04:25.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那加拿大就别无选择了\N{\rEng}Then you leave Canada no choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.27,0:04:28.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,罢工会继续的\N{\rEng}The strike shall continue!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.12,0:04:36.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,支持加拿大请鸣笛\N{\rEng}Honk if you support Canada.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.77,0:04:48.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,支持加拿大请鸣笛\N{\rEng}Honk if you support Canada.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.25,0:04:49.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  瞧着\N{\rEng}Hey   honey   watch this.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.63,0:04:53.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们在支持工会\N{\rEng}We're supporting Unions!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.84,0:04:54.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.34,0:04:55.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们是进步的夫妇\N{\rEng}We're a very progressive couple!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.82,0:04:57.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,说得对\N{\rEng}Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.13,0:04:59.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真好玩\N{\rEng}Oh   that's fun!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.87,0:05:00.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们完成了\N{\rEng}Well   we've done our
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.61,0:05:02.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,本周的行善\N{\rEng}good deed for the week.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.15,0:05:04.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想现在就算我对你肛交\N{\rEng}I think now i can make love to your anus
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.24,0:05:05.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也不会激怒上帝了\N{\rEng}Without making god angry.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.79,0:05:06.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\rEng}Oh   really?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.70,0:05:07.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\rEng}Goodie!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.20,0:05:16.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们\N{\rEng}Guys  
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.37,0:05:18.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我很担心我弟弟\N{\rEng}I'm really worried about my brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.01,0:05:20.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不在乎\N{\rEng}We don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.26,0:05:22.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你应该在乎\N{\rEng}You should care!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.28,0:05:23.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这次罢工会影响每个人  死胖子\N{\rEng}This strike affects everybody   fat ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.38,0:05:25.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,开始了\N{\rEng}It's on!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.17,0:05:26.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\rEng}Yippie!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.17,0:05:28.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,泰伦斯和菲利普秀\N{\rEng}It's the Terrance and Phillip show.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.03,0:05:29.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,今天播放\N{\rEng}Today's episode
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.16,0:05:30.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,"我放天然屁"\N{\rEng}"I fart huckabees".
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.52,0:05:32.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么又播这个\N{\rEng}Aw   this one again?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.92,0:05:33.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老天  他们重播这个\N{\rEng}God   they've replayed this one
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.94,0:05:35.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,都快80次了\N{\rEng}like eighty times now!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.56,0:05:35.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,菲利普\N{\rEng}Say Phillip  
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.99,0:05:38.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我刚买了部新的混合动力车\N{\rEng}I just bought this new hybrid car.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.35,0:05:40.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是用电力的吗\N{\rEng}Oh   does it run on electricity?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.31,0:05:42.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  用天然气的\N{\rEng}No   it uses natural gas.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.41,0:05:48.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看了那么多遍\N{\rEng}Huh   it somehow loses its punch
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.74,0:05:50.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,都没意思了\N{\rEng}After multiple viewings.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.35,0:05:51.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,该死  他们什么时候播\N{\rEng}Goddammit   when are we gonna air
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.31,0:05:52.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,新的泰伦斯和菲利普秀\N{\rEng}new Terrance and Phillip shows?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.93,0:05:54.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不会有新节目了\N{\rEng}There aren't going to be new shows.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.07,0:05:54.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们还没明白吗\N{\rEng}Don't you get it?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.00,0:05:56.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,泰伦斯和菲利普都是加拿大人\N{\rEng}Terrance and Phillip are Canadian!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.68,0:05:58.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们得让加拿大停止罢工\N{\rEng}We have to get Canada to end this strike!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.22,0:06:00.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没什么大不了的\N{\rEng}It's not a big deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.04,0:06:01.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以看美国喜剧\N{\rEng}We can just American comedy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.67,0:06:04.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你以为那很糟吗\N{\rEng}You think that's bad?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.73,0:06:06.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还记得那次我给\N{\rEng}Remember the time I sang
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.29,0:06:08.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,保罗·麦卡尼唱"蟑螂"吗\N{\rEng}"la cucaracha" for Paul McCartney.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.90,0:06:09.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\rEng}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.59,0:06:13.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能沦落到看这个\N{\rEng}We are not resorting to that!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.47,0:06:20.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,1  2  3  4\N{\rEng}One   two   three   four  
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.63,0:06:22.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大应得更多\N{\rEng}Canada deserves more!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.13,0:06:22.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,钱\N{\rEng}Money!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.94,0:06:24.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,1  2  3  4\N{\rEng}One   two   three   four  
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.31,0:06:25.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大应得更多\N{\rEng}Canada deserves more!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.54,0:06:26.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,钱\N{\rEng}Money!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.87,0:06:27.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,喂  老兄\N{\rEng}Look  buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.75,0:06:29.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我和菲利普要回家一段时间\N{\rEng}Me and Phillip need to go home for a bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.50,0:06:30.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,回家\N{\rEng}Go home?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.35,0:06:31.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们不能离开战线\N{\rEng}You can't leave the picket line!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.28,0:06:33.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但这个拖太长时间了\N{\rEng}But this is taking too long  
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.27,0:06:34.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,菲利普又有糖尿病\N{\rEng}and Phillip is diabetic.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.04,0:06:36.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  我们要坚守阵地\N{\rEng}Look   guy   we all have to stay strong.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.86,0:06:38.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们要是不和加拿大同胞携手并肩\N{\rEng}If you don't stand with your fellow Canadians  
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.25,0:06:39.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们就是叛徒\N{\rEng}Then you are a rat.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.69,0:06:41.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别叫我叛徒  老兄\N{\rEng}Don't call me a ramit buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.48,0:06:43.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不是你老兄  朋友\N{\rEng}I'm not your buddy   friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.35,0:06:44.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他不是你朋友  伙计\N{\rEng}He's not your friend   guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.61,0:06:46.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不是你伙计  老兄\N{\rEng}I'm not your guy   buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.16,0:06:47.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他不是你老兄  朋友\N{\rEng}He's not your buddy  friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.75,0:06:49.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不是你朋友  伙计\N{\rEng}I'm not your friend   guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.35,0:06:53.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩还不明白吗\N{\rEng}Don't you two understand anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.04,0:06:54.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们以为罢工是笑话吗\N{\rEng}You think striking is a joke?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.84,0:06:56.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们以为是开玩笑吗\N{\rEng}You think it's something to ridicule?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.15,0:06:58.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对  你们以为很好玩吗\N{\rEng}Yeah   you think this is funny'?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.71,0:07:01.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们还不明白我们必须要团结\N{\rEng}Don't you see that we have to stand together
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.41,0:07:02.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,否则就会一无是处\N{\rEng}or else we are nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.87,0:07:03.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,斯蒂芬\N{\rEng}Stephen!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.92,0:07:05.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,美国打来的电话\N{\rEng}A call came in from the United States.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.37,0:07:05.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们想跟你谈\N{\rEng}They want to talk to you
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.96,0:07:07.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,结束罢工的事\N{\rEng}about ending the strike!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.22,0:07:08.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我说过吧\N{\rEng}What did I tell you!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.49,0:07:10.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我说过他们迟早会让步的\N{\rEng}I told you we'd get to them sooner or later!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.03,0:07:15.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  安静  各位\N{\rEng}All right   shh! Quiet   everyone!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.51,0:07:16.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让我来处理\N{\rEng}Let me handle this.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.73,0:07:19.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\rEng}Yes?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.44,0:07:20.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我是斯蒂芬·埃布特曼\N{\rEng}This is Stephen Abootman  
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.36,0:07:22.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,W.G.A.的头头\N{\rEng}head of the W.G.A..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.98,0:07:24.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\rEng}Ah   hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.20,0:07:25.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们希望你们停止罢工\N{\rEng}We want you to end the strike.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.12,0:07:27.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们希望了  是吧\N{\rEng}Oh   you do   huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.06,0:07:28.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们受不了了\N{\rEng}They had enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.87,0:07:30.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,要我们停止罢工\N{\rEng}They want us to end the strike.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.37,0:07:37.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,安静  让我来处理\N{\rEng}Quiet.Let me deal with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.66,0:07:39.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们可以停止罢工\N{\rEng}All right  we're prepared to end the strike.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.99,0:07:41.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但你们必须同意\N{\rEng}if you are agreeing that
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.19,0:07:43.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们该拿更多钱\N{\rEng}We should have more money.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.73,0:07:45.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们完全同意\N{\rEng}We totally think
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.45,0:07:46.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们应该拿更多钱\N{\rEng}you should have more money.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.36,0:07:48.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们让步了\N{\rEng}We got 'em!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.45,0:07:49.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们成功了\N{\rEng}We did it!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.76,0:07:50.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,结束了\N{\rEng}It's over!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.95,0:07:51.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,罢工结束了\N{\rEng}The strike is over!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.50,0:07:54.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\rEng}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.41,0:07:55.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们准备给我们多少钱\N{\rEng}How much are you gonna give us?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.64,0:07:59.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们其实没多少钱\N{\rEng}Well   we don't really have that much money.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.85,0:08:01.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还玩谈判手段  是吧\N{\rEng}Oh   negotiating hard ball   are we?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.00,0:08:03.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那些因特网的钱呢\N{\rEng}What about all that internet money?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.71,0:08:05.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,因特网\N{\rEng}The internet?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.73,0:08:06.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你给我听好  朋友\N{\rEng}You listen to me  friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.26,0:08:08.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们最好想办法\N{\rEng}You better figure out a way
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.21,0:08:09.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,搞够钱给我们\N{\rEng}to get us our fair amount of money.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.58,0:08:10.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,下次带够钱\N{\rEng}And until you come back
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.54,0:08:11.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,再来找我\N{\rEng}with a solid fair number  
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.65,0:08:12.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,否则没的谈\N{\rEng}I'm finished talking to you  
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.98,0:08:15.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你这个官僚白痴\N{\rEng}you slimy corporate dickhead!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.85,0:08:18.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别担心\N{\rEng}Don't worry!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.81,0:08:20.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谈判就是这样的\N{\rEng}This is how negotiating works.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.16,0:08:21.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,情况大好\N{\rEng}This is good.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.01,0:08:22.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们把他们镇住了\N{\rEng}We've got 'em by the balls.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.31,0:08:28.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们说什么\N{\rEng}What they say?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.97,0:08:30.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们要我们从因特网\N{\rEng}They said we have to give them money
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.63,0:08:31.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,弄钱给他们\N{\rEng}that we make on the internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.08,0:08:33.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们要怎么从\N{\rEng}How are we supposed to
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.95,0:08:35.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,因特网赚钱\N{\rEng}make money on the internet?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.72,0:08:38.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,其他人是怎么从\N{\rEng}Well   how do other people
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.45,0:08:40.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,因特网赚钱的\N{\rEng}make money on the internet?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.98,0:08:43.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们要搞些吸引人的东西\N{\rEng}We have to put something up on the internet
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.09,0:08:45.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,放到因特网上去\N{\rEng}that everyone would find fascinating.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.16,0:08:47.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等等  我有办法了\N{\rEng}Wait   I've got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.44,0:09:03.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我说来肛交吧*\N{\rEng}*I said what what in the butt.*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.67,0:09:09.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*你想跟我肛交吗*\N{\rEng}*You want to do it in my butt  in my butt.*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.78,0:09:11.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我们来肛交吧*\N{\rEng}*Let's do it in the butt  okay.*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.65,0:09:13.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*没关系*\N{\rEng}*It's okay*  
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.47,0:09:15.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*就算你一柱擎天*\N{\rEng}*If you had it over thigh.*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.53,0:09:17.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*别担心*\N{\rEng}*Don't you worry * 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.24,0:09:19.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我不会咬你*\N{\rEng}*I won't bite.*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.26,0:09:20.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*别太用力*\N{\rEng}*Not that hard.*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.51,0:09:21.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*如果想要*\N{\rEng}*If you want it * 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.19,0:09:23.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我给你鼓劲*\N{\rEng}*I'll give you power.*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.54,0:09:25.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*温柔点*\N{\rEng}*Just be gentle * 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.70,0:09:27.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我如花般娇滴*\N{\rEng}*I'm delicate like a flower.*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.51,0:09:31.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*想要就来吧*\N{\rEng}*Give it to me  if you please.*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.47,0:09:32.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,偶滴神啊\N{\rEng}Oh   my.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.42,0:09:33.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*来肛交吧*\N{\rEng}*What what in the butt.*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.47,0:09:39.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我说来肛交吧*\N{\rEng}*I said what what in the butt.*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.67,0:09:45.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*你想跟我肛交吗*\N{\rEng}*You want to do it in my butt  in my butt.*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.67,0:09:48.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我们来肛交吧*\N{\rEng}*Let's do it in the butt   okay*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.70,0:09:50.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,越来越多人看了\N{\rEng}There's more people diong it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.23,0:09:51.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\rEng}This is going great!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.78,0:09:53.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  艾克\N{\rEng}Don't worry   Ike.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.77,0:09:55.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,罢工很快就会结束了\N{\rEng}This strike will be over soon!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.98,0:10:09.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,下一条国际新闻\N{\rEng}And in other world news  
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.50,0:10:10.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,日本首相\N{\rEng}the leader of Japan
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.36,0:10:12.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,今天要求增加\N{\rEng}today is calling for an increase
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.17,0:10:14.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,军费开支\N{\rEng}in military spending.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.14,0:10:15.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们怎么都\N{\rEng}How come they haven't mentioned
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.23,0:10:16.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不提我们\N{\rEng}anything about us?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.25,0:10:17.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候播罢工新闻\N{\rEng}When are they gonna get to the strike?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.78,0:10:19.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  罢工是大新闻\N{\rEng}Don't worry.The strike is big news.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.74,0:10:21.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我确定会是头条\N{\rEng}I'm sure it would be one of the top stories.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.63,0:10:22.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,今晚的其他新闻\N{\rEng}In other news tonight  
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.65,0:10:24.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,因特网上一盘\N{\rEng}It's the internet video
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.05,0:10:27.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,点击率超过1千万的录像\N{\rEng}That has already seen over 10 million views.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.05,0:10:28.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一位年轻  表情疑惑的男孩\N{\rEng}A young   confused-looking boy
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.76,0:10:30.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,边跳边唱一首\N{\rEng}dancing and singing a song called
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.83,0:10:33.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肛交歌\N{\rEng}"what what in my asshole".
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.46,0:10:34.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,汤姆  仅仅一周\N{\rEng}Tom   in just one week.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.55,0:10:35.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,此录像已成为\N{\rEng}The video has become
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.33,0:10:37.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,全美最热门焦点\N{\rEng}The most watched thing in all of America.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.91,0:10:39.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,录像里的小男孩\N{\rEng}The boy in the video  
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.21,0:10:40.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,更多地被称为\N{\rEng}Referred to by most as
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.53,0:10:41.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,"小基男"\N{\rEng}"that little gay kid"
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.65,0:10:43.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,已被邀请参加\N{\rEng}has already been asked to appear on
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.64,0:10:45.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吉米·金迈尔和"今日秀"节目\N{\rEng}Jimmy Kimmel and the "today show".
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.01,0:10:49.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,该死  那根本不算新闻\N{\rEng}Goddammit!That's not news.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.03,0:10:50.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们呢\N{\rEng}What about us?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.44,0:10:51.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,斯蒂芬\N{\rEng}Look  uh  Stephen  
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.90,0:10:54.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,泰伦斯和我谈过了\N{\rEng}Terrance and I were talking  and well  
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.77,0:10:55.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看起来似乎\N{\rEng}It's starting to look like maybe
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.83,0:10:57.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不会赢  懂吗\N{\rEng}We're not gonna win this thing   you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.12,0:11:00.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们能赢  我们要乐观点\N{\rEng}We'll win.we just have to stay resilient!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.70,0:11:01.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对  但是\N{\rEng}Well   yeah   but
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.46,0:11:03.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大家都快饿死了\N{\rEng}Everyone is dying of starvation.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.50,0:11:05.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对  我们放弃吧  伙计\N{\rEng}Yeah   let's give it up   guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.25,0:11:06.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别叫我伙计\N{\rEng}Don't call me your guy!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.69,0:11:08.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不是你伙计  朋友\N{\rEng}I'm not your guy  friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.35,0:11:10.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不是你朋友  老兄\N{\rEng}I'm not your friend   buddy!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.30,0:11:12.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不是你老兄  伙计\N{\rEng}I'm not your buddy   guy!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.22,0:11:13.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等等  开始了\N{\rEng}Wait! Here it is!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.44,0:11:14.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大声点  我们上电视了\N{\rEng}Turn it up   we're on.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.26,0:11:16.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,今晚最后的新闻\N{\rEng}And finally tonight  
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.16,0:11:18.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大罢工出现新局面\N{\rEng}A new development in the "Canada Strike".
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.95,0:11:20.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,提醒那些不记得\N{\rEng}For those of you who don't remember  
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.41,0:11:21.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,或不关心的人\N{\rEng}or don't care  
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.04,0:11:23.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大为争得更多钱而罢工\N{\rEng}Canada has been striking for more money.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.36,0:11:24.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\rEng}Yeah   All right!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.98,0:11:28.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我说过的  听着  听着\N{\rEng}I told you  now listen.Just listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.12,0:11:30.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,事件出现惊人局面\N{\rEng}In a shocking turn of events  
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.60,0:11:31.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如今\N{\rEng}It now appears that
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.27,0:11:33.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,成千上万丹麦人\N{\rEng}thousands of people from Denmark
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.53,0:11:35.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,涌入美国\N{\rEng}are flooding into the United States
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.10,0:11:36.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,希望填补罢工的\N{\rEng}with hopes of taking the place
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.70,0:11:38.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大人的空缺\N{\rEng}of the striking Canadians.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.43,0:11:40.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.21,0:11:40.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你真的认为\N{\rEng}Do you really think
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.99,0:11:42.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,丹麦人能取代加拿大人吗\N{\rEng}You Danish can replace the Canadians?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.42,0:11:44.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们那里\N{\rEng}Well   where we come from
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.91,0:11:46.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也很冷\N{\rEng}It's pretty cold too   yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.42,0:11:47.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们喜欢冰球\N{\rEng}We like hockey and
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.24,0:11:49.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也没人注意我们\N{\rEng}Nobody really pays any attention to us.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.59,0:11:51.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没人知道丹麦在哪\N{\rEng}Nobody knows where Denmark is.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.20,0:11:51.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.99,0:11:52.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所以你们仔细想想\N{\rEng}So when you think about it
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.88,0:11:54.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们就是欧洲的加拿大人\N{\rEng}We're the Canadians of Europe.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.81,0:11:56.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋\N{\rEng}Scabs!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.00,0:11:58.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能这样\N{\rEng}How could you?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.76,0:12:05.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们在网上搞了个很成功的\N{\rEng}We made a really successful thing
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.84,0:12:06.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,东东\N{\rEng}On the internet  
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.55,0:12:08.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们想来领钱\N{\rEng}And we like to collect our money.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.43,0:12:10.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,取号然后跟其他人一起等\N{\rEng}Take a number and wait with everyone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.30,0:12:12.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,夫人  你可能没认出\N{\rEng}Ma'am  perhaps you don't recognize
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.48,0:12:13.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,轰动因特网\N{\rEng}The internet sensation
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.62,0:12:15.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,YOUTUBE上的小基男\N{\rEng}"little gay kid" from youtube.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.05,0:12:18.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,取号然后跟其他人一起等\N{\rEng}Take a number and wait with everyone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.44,0:12:28.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巧克力雨\N{\rEng}Chocolate rain!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.68,0:12:31.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我认得你\N{\rEng}Hey  I know you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.05,0:12:32.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你是那个屁眼交小孩\N{\rEng}You're the "what what my asshole kid".
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.95,0:12:34.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是肛交  先生\N{\rEng}"What what in the butt"  sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.56,0:12:35.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是真空男\N{\rEng}It's tron guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.62,0:12:36.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我在YOUTO看过他\N{\rEng}I saw him on youto.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.60,0:12:37.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当然\N{\rEng}Yeah   sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.63,0:12:39.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所有因特网明星都在这\N{\rEng}All the biggest internet stars are here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.85,0:12:41.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定记得"扭吧扭吧"\N{\rEng}You remember of course numa numa?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.34,0:12:51.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还有星战小鬼\N{\rEng}and starwar's kid..
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.32,0:12:55.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还有轰动因特网的\N{\rEng}And the internet sensation  
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.81,0:12:57.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,可爱喷嚏熊猫\N{\rEng}Cute sneezing panda.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.84,0:13:02.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还有剽悍地鼠\N{\rEng}And there is dramatic look gopher!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.46,0:13:08.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我在网上都看过你们\N{\rEng}I've seen all you guys on the internet?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.23,0:13:09.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有多少人\N{\rEng}So how many people
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.79,0:13:12.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看了你的录像\N{\rEng}have seen your internet video?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.09,0:13:14.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,几十万吧\N{\rEng}Ugh   a few hundred thousand.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.30,0:13:16.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就那么点\N{\rEng}Mere peanuts!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.00,0:13:19.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巧克力雨可是横扫因特网\N{\rEng}Chocolate Rain has done gangbusters.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.25,0:13:20.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,理论上说\N{\rEng}Theoretically
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.96,0:13:23.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我是百万富翁\N{\rEng}I'm a millionaire.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.10,0:13:23.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  去你的\N{\rEng}Dude   screw you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.89,0:13:25.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你的已经是去年的事了\N{\rEng}Your internet thing is so last year.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.93,0:13:28.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别烦巧克力雨男\N{\rEng}Leave Chocolate Rain guy alone!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.80,0:13:30.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别烦他\N{\rEng}Leave him alone!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.59,0:13:32.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我说真的\N{\rEng}I'm serious!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.92,0:13:36.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,失陪\N{\rEng}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.93,0:13:38.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\rEng}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.73,0:13:41.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你这个贪婪的官僚蛀虫\N{\rEng}You greedy  corporate fat cat.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.84,0:13:43.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你说过会给我们钱的\N{\rEng}You said you would get us money.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.12,0:13:45.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们在努力\N{\rEng}We're working on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.61,0:13:46.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你在故意拖延\N{\rEng}You're stalling
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.43,0:13:48.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我会放弃\N{\rEng}Because you think I'll give up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.26,0:13:48.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你知道\N{\rEng}You know that
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.72,0:13:49.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大部分加拿大人已在\N{\rEng}Most Canadians are talking about
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.99,0:13:51.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,讨论放弃罢工\N{\rEng}giving up the strike already.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.63,0:13:54.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你把我逼得走投无路了\N{\rEng}You've got me over a barrel and you know it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.44,0:13:55.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,阁下\N{\rEng}Sir!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.21,0:13:56.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们正竭尽全力\N{\rEng}We're doing everything we can.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.57,0:13:57.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还要我再说一遍吗\N{\rEng}You want me to say it again?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.23,0:13:59.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你把我逼得走投无路了\N{\rEng}You've got me over a barrel.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.44,0:14:00.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,高兴了吧\N{\rEng}There   you happy?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.56,0:14:00.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你把我逼得\N{\rEng}You've got me bent over
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.87,0:14:02.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,露出我娇嫩的屁股\N{\rEng}A barrel with my tender ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.57,0:14:03.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等着被你的\N{\rEng}just waiting to be pulverized
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.77,0:14:05.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,男性雄风蹂躏\N{\rEng}by your thrusting manhood.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.40,0:14:09.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果我发起又取消罢工\N{\rEng}Do you realize how stupid I'm going to look
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.29,0:14:11.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我会多糗吗\N{\rEng}if I call off the strike after starting all this?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.76,0:14:12.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不会这么做的\N{\rEng}I won't do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.64,0:14:13.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,听清了吗  伙计\N{\rEng}You hear me   guy?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.64,0:14:14.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你错了\N{\rEng}You're wrong  
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.43,0:14:15.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不管发生什么\N{\rEng}No matter what happens  
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.68,0:14:17.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我绝不停止罢工\N{\rEng}I will never call off this strike.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.85,0:14:20.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就算我们都翘辫子\N{\rEng}Even if it means we all die.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.03,0:14:22.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不想让你们死\N{\rEng}We don't want you to die!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.72,0:14:24.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那你最好赶快\N{\rEng}Then you better hurry.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.55,0:14:26.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们时日不多了\N{\rEng}We don't have much longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.29,0:14:28.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不然你就是罪魁祸首\N{\rEng}The blood will be on your hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.95,0:14:35.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们得快点\N{\rEng}We have to speed this up.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.22,0:14:36.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们能不能跳到\N{\rEng}Can we collect our internet money
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.39,0:14:37.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们前面领钱\N{\rEng}in front of you   please?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.59,0:14:39.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\rEng}I don't think so!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.41,0:14:43.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没什么比巧克力雨更重要\N{\rEng}Nothing takes priority over Chocolate Rain
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.11,0:14:45.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他又来自大的一套了\N{\rEng}Oh   here he goes with the ego again.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.08,0:14:47.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谁封你是最红因特网明星的\N{\rEng}Who crowned you the top internet star?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.82,0:14:48.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我封的\N{\rEng}I did  
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.71,0:14:52.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我比你们都红的时候封的\N{\rEng}When I became bigger than all you bitches.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.91,0:14:53.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧\N{\rEng}Oh   please!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.68,0:14:55.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,憨笑宝贝的点击率\N{\rEng}Laughing baby had four times
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.09,0:14:56.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,都比你高4倍\N{\rEng}as many views as you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.65,0:15:02.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈的最好给我闭嘴\N{\rEng}You better shut your fucking mouth  
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.41,0:15:03.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,憨笑宝贝\N{\rEng}laughing baby!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.75,0:15:05.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们都把卷毛忍者忘啦\N{\rEng}Did you all forget about afro ninja?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.71,0:15:06.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的点击率\N{\rEng}My internet thing
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.46,0:15:07.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,比谁都高\N{\rEng}was bigger than anybody's.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.70,0:15:08.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,理论上\N{\rEng}I made you over
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.52,0:15:10.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我赚了超过1亿美元的\N{\rEng}A hundred million theoretical dollars.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.71,0:15:11.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,喷嚏熊猫\N{\rEng}Sneezing panda
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.76,0:15:13.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,理论上值几十亿呢\N{\rEng}is theoretically worth billions.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.00,0:15:16.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们他妈的都想死吗\N{\rEng}You all want to motherfucking die?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.93,0:15:18.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\rEng}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.17,0:15:33.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,算了\N{\rEng}Hey   forget it!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.30,0:15:34.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们等就是了\N{\rEng}We'll wait our turn!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.85,0:15:45.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别烦真空男\N{\rEng}leave tron guy alone!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.58,0:15:47.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别烦他\N{\rEng}leave him alone!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.72,0:15:52.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,准备吃巧克力子弹吧  臭婊子\N{\rEng}Get ready for some chocolate bean   bitch!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.59,0:15:58.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别烦熊猫\N{\rEng}Leave the panda alone!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.70,0:15:59.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别烦她\N{\rEng}Leave her alone!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.97,0:16:01.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我说真的\N{\rEng}I'm serious.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.55,0:16:15.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,以为我会放过你吗  地鼠\N{\rEng}Thought I forgot about you   gopher?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.17,0:16:24.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的大脑\N{\rEng}My brain
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.21,0:16:34.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,爽  我们不用等了\N{\rEng}Sweet   I think we're next in line now!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.80,0:16:56.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,斯蒂芬  他们来了\N{\rEng}Stephen  they are here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.14,0:16:57.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们来谈判了\N{\rEng}They come to negotiate.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.17,0:16:59.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么  真的吗\N{\rEng}What  you mean it?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.68,0:17:01.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  我们拿到钱了\N{\rEng}Okay  we get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.66,0:17:03.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们到底是谁\N{\rEng}Who the hell are you
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.84,0:17:04.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们就是告诉你\N{\rEng}We are the ones that told you
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.70,0:17:05.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,会从因特网赚钱给你们的人\N{\rEng}We go get internet money.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.77,0:17:08.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,给  我们赚了1千万虚拟货币\N{\rEng}Here  we made ten million theoratical dollars
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.22,0:17:09.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,全给你们\N{\rEng}It's all for you
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.81,0:17:13.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,虚拟货币\N{\rEng}Theoratical dollars
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.03,0:17:14.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我要这个干嘛\N{\rEng}What am i suppose to do with that
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.43,0:17:16.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们浪费了我的时间\N{\rEng}You litter time waster
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.19,0:17:17.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们很辛苦才赚到\N{\rEng}Hey  we work really hard to
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.05,0:17:18.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这些虚拟货币的\N{\rEng}get this theoratical money
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.25,0:17:20.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对  大家都以为我是同性恋\N{\rEng}yeah everyone think I am a homo now
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.12,0:17:22.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你就是同性恋  巴特斯\N{\rEng}You are homo  Butters
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.55,0:17:24.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  现在就结束  行吗\N{\rEng}Dude will you just end this thing now
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.09,0:17:25.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我弟弟快死了\N{\rEng}my little brother is gonna die
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.85,0:17:28.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不要做傻子\N{\rEng}No I am not gonna look like a idiot
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.54,0:17:30.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,即使会被罢工的人耻笑\N{\rEng}If I was gonna laughed at everyone on strike
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.42,0:17:32.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我也绝不承认\N{\rEng}The last thing I gonna do is to admit it
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.39,0:17:36.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,喂  我是W.G.A.的头头\N{\rEng}Yes?This is the head of W.G.A.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.39,0:17:38.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,全球加拿大办公署\N{\rEng}The World Canadian bureau
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.71,0:17:40.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,埃布特曼先生\N{\rEng}Oh Mr. Abootman
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.00,0:17:42.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我是全球峰会的头头\N{\rEng}It's the Global Summit Leaders
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.99,0:17:45.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们想跟你谈罢工的事\N{\rEng}We want to talk to you about the strike
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.01,0:17:47.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\rEng}You do?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.27,0:17:48.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们想要谈判吗\N{\rEng}You want a negotiate?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.93,0:17:51.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  其实我们是想问\N{\rEng}No actually.we were just wondering
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.10,0:17:52.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们都死了\N{\rEng}If when you all dead
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.36,0:17:53.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们能不能用纽芬兰\N{\rEng}We can use Newfoundland
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.59,0:17:55.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来建新的环球主题公园\N{\rEng}for a new global theme park
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.99,0:18:03.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\rEng}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.74,0:18:05.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们随便给他点东西  好吗\N{\rEng}Will you just give this guy something   please?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.29,0:18:07.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}Excuse me?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.29,0:18:08.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他只是不想看起来像个傻子\N{\rEng}He just doesn't want to look like an idiot  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.69,0:18:09.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所以他想让大家\N{\rEng}so he needs everyone to think
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.23,0:18:10.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,以为罢工很成功\N{\rEng}the strike was for something.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.14,0:18:12.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,随便给他点东西\N{\rEng}Just give him anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.51,0:18:15.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以给加拿大\N{\rEng}Well   we could give Canada
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.21,0:18:18.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一点小安慰奖品\N{\rEng}Some small consolation prize.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.97,0:18:19.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们给你点小东西\N{\rEng}If they give you something small  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.83,0:18:21.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你能停止罢工吗\N{\rEng}will you end the strike?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.05,0:18:23.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们能不能\N{\rEng}Will they
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.48,0:18:25.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,假装给了加拿大很多\N{\rEng}act like they're giving Canada a lot
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.77,0:18:27.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这样大家才觉得我做得很好\N{\rEng}So everyone thinks I did a good job?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.61,0:18:29.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们能不能假装给了他很多\N{\rEng}Can you act like you're giving him a lot?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.41,0:18:31.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当然  何乐而不为\N{\rEng}Sure   why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.47,0:18:37.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们赢了\N{\rEng}We have won!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.90,0:18:42.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们赢得了多少\N{\rEng}So how much did we get?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.48,0:18:43.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们\N{\rEng}Well   we  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.42,0:18:45.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们没有完全得到想要的\N{\rEng}we didn't get everything that we wanted  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.42,0:18:48.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但经过艰苦的谈判\N{\rEng}But we negotiated hard
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.07,0:18:51.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们得到这些"笨尼肯"的优惠券\N{\rEng}And we got these coupons to Bennigans
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.46,0:18:55.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,和给每个加拿大人的免费泡泡糖\N{\rEng}and free bubble gum for every canadian!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.32,0:19:02.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这些优惠券\N{\rEng}These coupons
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.35,0:19:03.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让每位加拿大人均可\N{\rEng}entitle every canadian
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.76,0:19:05.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,免费在"笨尼肯"享受一顿饭\N{\rEng}to a free meal at bennigans!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.05,0:19:07.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当然必须同时消费\N{\rEng}With the purchase of a meal at
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.00,0:19:08.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等值或更贵的食物\N{\rEng}equal or greater value   of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.74,0:19:11.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们成功了\N{\rEng}We did it!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.35,0:19:16.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,朋友们\N{\rEng}My friends  
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.91,0:19:18.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是加拿大历史上\N{\rEng}this is the greatest victory
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.70,0:19:20.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,最伟大的胜利\N{\rEng}in Canadian history!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.04,0:19:23.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大取得罢工胜利\N{\rEng}Canada wins the strike!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.27,0:19:26.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,罢工结束  加拿大赢了\N{\rEng}Strike over! Canada Victorious!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.97,0:19:29.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,罢工庆功宴  下周举行\N{\rEng}Strike victory party set for next week
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.50,0:19:37.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾克\N{\rEng}Ike.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.77,0:19:38.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,艾克\N{\rEng}Ike!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.82,0:19:40.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,罢工结束了\N{\rEng}It's over.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.79,0:19:41.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,结束了吗\N{\rEng}It's over?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.90,0:19:43.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对  给你\N{\rEng}Yeah   here you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.14,0:19:52.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我真高兴罢工终于结束了\N{\rEng}Boy   I'm sure glad that's over with.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.32,0:19:53.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N{\rEng}Me too!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.67,0:19:54.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对  但是\N{\rEng}Yeah   but you know  
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.45,0:19:55.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我今天有所领悟\N{\rEng}I learned something today.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.27,0:19:57.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们都以为能\N{\rEng}We thought we could
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.00,0:19:58.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,利用因特网赚钱\N{\rEng}make money on the internet  
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.17,0:19:59.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但因特网虽然\N{\rEng}but while the internet
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.19,0:20:01.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对创新的人来说很新奇刺激\N{\rEng}is new and exciting for creative people  
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.47,0:20:02.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但它作为一个分配机制\N{\rEng}it hasn't matured as a
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.49,0:20:04.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还未成熟到能够让人\N{\rEng}distribution mechanism to the extent
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.12,0:20:04.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,牺牲现实的\N{\rEng}that one should trade real
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.91,0:20:06.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,或眼前的利益来换取\N{\rEng}or immediate opportunities for income
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.04,0:20:07.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,未来网络收入的前景\N{\rEng}for the promise of future online revenue.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.90,0:20:09.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还需要很多年\N{\rEng}It will be a few years before
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.09,0:20:10.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,网络媒介的数字化分配\N{\rEng}digital distribution of media on the internet
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.78,0:20:11.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,才能成熟地货币化\N{\rEng}can be monetized to an extent
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.70,0:20:13.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,从而使得内容生产商必须放弃\N{\rEng}that necessitates content producers to forgo
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.77,0:20:15.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们在传统媒介中的公允价值\N{\rEng}their fair value in more traditional media.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.78,0:20:18.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.85,0:20:25.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,庆功宴\N{\rEng}Victory Party
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.80,0:20:30.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们成功了\N{\rEng}We did it!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.98,0:20:32.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,庆祝一下吧  各位\N{\rEng}Celebrate   everyone!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.80,0:20:37.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们在罢工中献出生命\N{\rEng}They gave their lives for the strike
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.38,0:20:39.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,暂停\N{\rEng}Hold on a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.44,0:20:40.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,停一下\N{\rEng}Wait just a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.52,0:20:43.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚做了统计\N{\rEng}We just did some calculating.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.32,0:20:44.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,由于罢工期间息业\N{\rEng}By not working during the strike  
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.71,0:20:47.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大损失了1千零40万美元\N{\rEng}Canadians lost $10.4 million dollars.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.50,0:20:48.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,而"笨尼肯"的优惠券\N{\rEng}And our bennigan's coupons
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.97,0:20:50.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,和泡泡糖只价值\N{\rEng}and bubble gum is worth roughly
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.31,0:20:52.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,3千零8美元\N{\rEng}3  008 dollars.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.14,0:20:53.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别管那个\N{\rEng}Don't look at that.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.54,0:20:55.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  朋友们  跳舞吧\N{\rEng}Come on   friends   let's dance.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.50,0:20:57.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不知道自己干了什么\N{\rEng}You had no idea what you were doing
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.72,0:20:58.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在还装得像个\N{\rEng}and now you're trying to make it
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.79,0:20:59.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,胜利者好让\N{\rEng}look like you won so that
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.40,0:21:00.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不会流放你\N{\rEng}we won't set you a drift!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.77,0:21:02.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,该死  朋友  你们还不明白吗\N{\rEng}Dammit   friends   don't you see?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.65,0:21:04.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,胜利是为了加拿大的下一代  伙计\N{\rEng}We won for future Canadians   guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.98,0:21:06.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好让他们\N{\rEng}So the little guy
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.11,0:21:07.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,再不会任人摆布\N{\rEng}doesn't get pushed around anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.77,0:21:10.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是加拿大尊严的胜利\N{\rEng}This was a victory for Canada's respect.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.28,0:21:18.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们这是干嘛\N{\rEng}What do you think you're doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.45,0:21:19.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,流放你们  白痴\N{\rEng}We're setting you adrift   idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.57,0:21:23.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也许你们能去跟丹麦人生活\N{\rEng}Maybe you can go live with the Danish!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.02,0:21:26.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你会后悔的  朋友\N{\rEng}You'll regret this day   friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.20,0:21:29.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不是你朋友  老兄\N{\rEng}I'm not your friend   buddy!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.12,0:21:32.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不是你老兄  伙计\N{\rEng}I'm not your buddy   guy!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.41,0:21:34.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他不是你伙计  朋友\N{\rEng}He's not your guy   friend!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.54,0:21:37.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不是你朋友  老兄\N{\rEng}I'm not your friend   buddy!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.98,0:21:40.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是你老兄  伙计\N{\rEng}We're not your buddies   guy!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.32,0:21:45.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不是你们的伙计  朋友\N{\rEng}I'm not your guy   friends!
