[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2008-10-30 08:43:29
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayDepth: 0
PlayResX: 1916
PlayResY: 1076
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 2
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H19000000,&H000E0300,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,2,2,134,120,68,1
Style: eng,Microsoft YaHei,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,26,1
Style: Top,微软雅黑,10,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Git,Comic Sans MS,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Chn,微软雅黑,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Eng,Comic Sans MS,60,&H002AF7FF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1
[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.20,0:00:11.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm going down to south park\N gonna have myself a time 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.05,0:00:15.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Friendly faces everywhere\N humble folks without temptation 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.33,0:00:18.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Going down to south park\N gonna leave my woes behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.72,0:00:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ample parking day or night\N people shouting howdy neighbor
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.96,0:00:24.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heading on out to south park\N gonna see if I can't unwind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.54,0:00:28.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I like girls with big vaginas\N I like girls with big fat titties
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.61,0:00:31.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.90,0:21:45.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译制作\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}YYeTs人人影视字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.90,0:21:47.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}校译\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}sunflo
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.90,0:21:48.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1c&HFDC282&}后期\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}csbeyond
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.60,0:00:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0150,,{\1c&HFDC282&}南方公园  第12季第5集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.60,0:00:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0100,,咦唷  小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}Eek A Penis!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.70,0:00:38.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看起来 我的整个人生\N{\rEng}It's like my whole life has just
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.83,0:00:41.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就是一团糟  你们知道嘛\N{\rEng}been one big screw up   you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.24,0:00:44.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我承认  我以前对性很困惑\N{\rEng}I admit it   I was sexually lost.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.83,0:00:47.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,后来我看到了奥普拉秀上的这个人\N{\rEng}And then I see this person on Oprah.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.20,0:00:48.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一个女人  但是她做了变性\N{\rEng}She's a woman   but then she got
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.49,0:00:49.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,手术成为了一个男人\N{\rEng}a sex change and became a man  
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.70,0:00:51.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是她却怀孕还生了小孩\N{\rEng}but then she got pregnant and is having a baby
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.62,0:00:54.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,说明她骨子里依然是个女人\N{\rEng}which means she was still a woman all along.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.44,0:00:56.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所以我依然还是个男人\N{\rEng}That means I'm really still a man!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.95,0:00:59.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我仍然感觉自己是个男人\N{\rEng}I still feel like a man.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.17,0:01:02.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这些会在考试中出现吗\N{\rEng}Are we gonna get tested on this?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.18,0:01:05.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的变性是个大错特错\N{\rEng}This sex change was a big mistake. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.65,0:01:08.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当时我吃了很多止痛药\N{\rEng}I was on a lot of pain killers at the time  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.63,0:01:10.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为这是我想要的\N{\rEng}and I thought it was what I wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.64,0:01:12.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  想做点数学题嘛\N{\rEng}Dude   you wanna do some math problems?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.67,0:01:15.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,然后我去了医院\N{\rEng}And then I go to the doctor   right?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.07,0:01:16.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我说  医生  我想恢复\N{\rEng}And I say doctor   I want to go
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.14,0:01:18.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的男儿身  他说\N{\rEng}back to being a man and he says  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.15,0:01:19.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你的器官已经严重受损\N{\rEng}"well   there's been too much damage"
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.66,0:01:21.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你回不去男儿身了\N{\rEng}"you can't go back."
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.37,0:01:23.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你到哪儿再去找个小鸡鸡呢\N{\rEng}Where are you going to find a penis?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.54,0:01:26.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我居然需要去再找个小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}What do you mean where am i gonna find a penis!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.24,0:01:27.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我是个男人\N{\rEng}I'm a man!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.74,0:01:30.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我他妈理所当然应该有小鸡鸡的\N{\rEng}I deserve a God dammed penis!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.53,0:01:36.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加里森  加里森老师\N{\rEng}Uh   Mister --Mister Garrison!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.66,0:01:39.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,能跟你谈一下嘛\N{\rEng}Could we speak with you   please?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.95,0:01:42.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们想干什么  我在上课\N{\rEng}What do you want? I'm trying to teach.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.18,0:01:44.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们觉得你最好先把你的\N{\rEng}Uh   we think it's best you not teach until
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.57,0:01:46.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,个人生活理顺再来上课  好嘛\N{\rEng}you get your personal life in order   m'kay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.99,0:01:49.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你说起来容易  麦基\N{\rEng}Oh   it's so easy for you   Mackey
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.67,0:01:51.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,又不是你没有小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}you have a penis!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.68,0:01:54.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  同学们  看起来\N{\rEng}Okay   students   uh   obviously we've had
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.55,0:01:56.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们老师出了点状况\N{\rEng}a little emergency with your teacher.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.57,0:01:59.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所以  在我们处理问题的时候需要\N{\rEng}So   uh   while we deal with this we need one of you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.00,0:02:02.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一个人来带领大家为明天的测试做准备\N{\rEng}to lead the class and review for tomorrow's quiz.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.70,0:02:04.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我  我   我   我\N{\rEng}Me   me! Me!Me!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.94,0:02:06.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,选我  选我\N{\rEng}Right here! Right here!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.39,0:02:09.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还有其他人想当一天的老师吗\N{\rEng}who else would like to be teacher for the day?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.27,0:02:11.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还有其他人吗\N{\rEng}Anybody else?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.52,0:02:15.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,维多利亚校长  选我\N{\rEng}Principal Victoria! Over here!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.32,0:02:18.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还有其他的自愿者吗\N{\rEng}Any other volunteers perhaps?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.75,0:02:21.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,维多利亚校长\N{\rEng}Principal Victoria!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.50,0:02:22.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  好吧  很好\N{\rEng}Alright   alright   fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.66,0:02:24.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  你来带领全班\N{\rEng}Eric   you lead the class.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.17,0:02:25.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\rEng}Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.25,0:02:26.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,带着大家把加里森老师\N{\rEng}Now just lead a review over whatever
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.76,0:02:27.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所教的都复习一遍\N{\rEng}Mr. Garrison's been teaching you
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.97,0:02:31.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我很快就会回来检查你的工作\N{\rEng}and I'll be back to check on your shortly.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.62,0:02:36.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,哼  哼  哼\N{\rEng}Well   well   well...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.12,0:02:38.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在谁是老师了\N{\rEng}who's teacher now?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.07,0:02:41.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,耶  谁是老师\N{\rEng}Yeah... who's teacher?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.53,0:02:43.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你又不是老师  死胖子\N{\rEng}You're not the teacher   fat ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.43,0:02:45.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在要叫我卡特曼先生  凯尔\N{\rEng}That's Mister Cartman now   Kyle!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.29,0:02:46.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,聪明的话就不要打断我\N{\rEng}And you will be wise to not interrupt
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.81,0:02:49.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,除非你想被停课\N{\rEng}my class unless you want to be suspended!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.87,0:02:54.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,耶  听明白了嘛\N{\rEng}Yeah. You like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.46,0:02:58.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  克莱德  你是第一个  上来\N{\rEng}Alright   Clyde   you're first. Get up here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.86,0:03:01.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,耶  你会体验到的  克莱德\N{\rEng}Yeah   you're gonna take it   Clyde.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.68,0:03:09.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看起来本地农民的市场\N{\rEng}So it appears that the local farmer's market
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.13,0:03:12.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很快就会完全被关闭\N{\rEng}could be soon facing complete closure.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.54,0:03:14.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,另外一条消息  南方公园一间\N{\rEng}In other news tonight   a South Park
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.51,0:03:16.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,生物医学公司因为\N{\rEng}bio company is coming under fire
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.52,0:03:18.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,用遗传工程把人体器官移植\N{\rEng}for genetically engineering body parts
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.62,0:03:20.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,到小白鼠身上而备受指责\N{\rEng}onto laboratory mice.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.85,0:03:22.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这张被移植了一只人类\N{\rEng}This picture of a mouse genetically
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.91,0:03:24.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,耳朵的小白鼠照片\N{\rEng}altered to grow a human ear
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.92,0:03:27.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,已经招惹了广泛的抗议\N{\rEng}has already sparked waves of protest.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.95,0:03:29.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.25,0:03:30.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是科学家称  通过这种方法\N{\rEng}But the scientists say the process
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.97,0:03:32.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,可以使成千上万\N{\rEng}could help thousands of people
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.48,0:03:36.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,被毁容的人得到需要的耳朵或鼻子\N{\rEng}who have become disfigured and need ears or noses.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.30,0:03:38.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,偶滴神啊\N{\rEng}Holy freakin' Jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.70,0:03:41.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,研究小组实验室\N{\rEng}RESERCH GROUP LABORTORIES
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.05,0:03:42.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,利用普通的基因技术\N{\rEng}Using common genetics
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.63,0:03:43.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,和软骨支架技术\N{\rEng}and cartilage scaffolding  
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.64,0:03:45.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以把几乎所有人体器官\N{\rEng}we can graft almost any body part
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.41,0:03:47.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,移植到小白鼠身上来生长\N{\rEng}onto a mouse and allow it to develop.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.42,0:03:49.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是你在电视上看过的小白鼠\N{\rEng}Here's the mouse you saw on television.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.74,0:03:51.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一旦耳朵完全成型了\N{\rEng}Once the ear fully forms   it can
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.18,0:03:53.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就可以移植到人体上\N{\rEng}be transplanted onto a person.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.49,0:03:56.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,医生  小鸡鸡呢\N{\rEng}Doctor   what about a penis?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.42,0:03:58.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小鸡鸡是男性用来插入\N{\rEng}Well   a penis is something a
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.05,0:04:00.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,女性阴道的器官\N{\rEng}man puts into a woman's vagina.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.37,0:04:01.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  不\N{\rEng}No   no.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.17,0:04:03.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我是说如果我给你我的DNA  你能\N{\rEng}If I gave you some of my DNA   could
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.09,0:04:05.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在小白鼠身上培养一个小鸡鸡给我吗\N{\rEng}you grow a penis on a mouse for me?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.10,0:04:07.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你没明白  这个实验非常昂贵\N{\rEng}You don't understand   doing this stuff is very expensive
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.92,0:04:09.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,而且我们从来没试过小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}and we've never tried a penis before.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.73,0:04:11.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不敢保证一定能行\N{\rEng}There's no guarantee it would work!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.42,0:04:12.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我可以给你我所有的钱\N{\rEng}I will give you all the money
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.62,0:04:15.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,只求一试  求求你\N{\rEng}I have to just try. Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.03,0:04:17.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,医生  我是个困在女性身体里的男人\N{\rEng}Doctor   I'm a man trapped in a woman's body.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.59,0:04:19.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我需要一个小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}I need a penis.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.04,0:04:22.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  好吧  让我们来试试吧\N{\rEng}Alright   alright   let's see what we can do.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.03,0:04:25.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  我们叫你来是表扬你\N{\rEng}Eric   we've called you in to commend you
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.03,0:04:27.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,作为代理老师的表现\N{\rEng}for your role as student teacher.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.87,0:04:28.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要表扬我\N{\rEng}Don't commend me  
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.94,0:04:31.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是那些学生自己太笨了\N{\rEng}it's the students fault for being so stupid!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.15,0:04:32.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,表扬  的意思是你\N{\rEng}Commend means you've done
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.27,0:04:34.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,干得不错  埃里克  好嘛\N{\rEng}a great job   Eric   mkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.18,0:04:36.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,通过带领他们复习\N{\rEng}After leading your class through review  
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.09,0:04:37.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你的同学们取得了他们\N{\rEng}your schoolmates scored higher
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.50,0:04:39.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,从未得到过的高分\N{\rEng}than they ever have on their tests!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.71,0:04:42.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不论你是怎么做的  那的确有效\N{\rEng}Whatever you did really worked on them!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.44,0:04:43.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\rEng}Oh well   thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.88,0:04:45.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我相信严格的纪律和同情心\N{\rEng}I believe strict discipline along with compassion
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.87,0:04:48.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是促进学生学习的催化剂\N{\rEng}for my students is catamite to their learning.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.12,0:04:50.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这些来自丹佛县学校董事会\N{\rEng}These gentlemen from the Denver County School Board
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.11,0:04:52.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,的先生们想跟你谈谈\N{\rEng}have something they want to ask you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.12,0:04:54.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,年轻人  你作为代理教师的成功\N{\rEng}Young man   word of your success as a student
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.24,0:04:56.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让我们整个董事会都在思考\N{\rEng}teacher has started the whole board thinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.29,0:04:57.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们想让你把你的方法用在\N{\rEng}We would like you to try your methods
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.64,0:04:59.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们一个市内学校的班级上\N{\rEng}on one of our inner city school classes.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.96,0:05:02.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那些小孩根本就不听成人老师的\N{\rEng}These kids just won't listen to any adult teachers  
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.51,0:05:05.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,既然你在你的班级上取得了成功\N{\rEng}and since you handled your class so well  
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.25,0:05:07.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有兴趣来试试吗\N{\rEng}how'd you like to give it a shot?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.26,0:05:08.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那听起来是个拯救\N{\rEng}That sounds like a chance to really make
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.78,0:05:10.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那些学生于水深火热的机会\N{\rEng}an impact on some students who need it most.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.99,0:05:13.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们打算付我多少钱\N{\rEng}How much will you pay me?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.76,0:05:16.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,三百美元\N{\rEng}Three hundred bucks!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.07,0:05:17.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们听到我的说的了吗\N{\rEng}Did you hear what I said you guys!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.59,0:05:18.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我出色的教学技巧\N{\rEng}My awesome teaching skills is
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.74,0:05:20.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,会让我赚三百美元\N{\rEng}gonna earn me three hundred bucks!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.95,0:05:22.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你才不是出色的老师呢\N{\rEng}You're not an awesome teacher!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.75,0:05:23.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何  整个班都\N{\rEng}Whatever   the whole class
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.87,0:05:25.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在测验中考了高分\N{\rEng}scored super high on the tests.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.88,0:05:27.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们得高分唯一的原因是\N{\rEng}The only reason we scored high was
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.24,0:05:28.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们从加里森的抽屉里把\N{\rEng}because we took the answers out of
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.45,0:05:30.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,答案偷了出来  你自己最清楚\N{\rEng}Garrison's desk   and you know it!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.17,0:05:31.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  但从加里森的抽屉\N{\rEng}Yes   but whose idea was it to take
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.98,0:05:33.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,里偷答案是谁的主意呢\N{\rEng}the answers out of Garrison's desk?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.60,0:05:34.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼的\N{\rEng}Kenny's!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.83,0:05:36.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  那是我的主意\N{\rEng}Yeah   that was my idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.17,0:05:36.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,噢  对\N{\rEng}Oh   yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.88,0:05:38.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么样  我就要去教\N{\rEng}But whatever   I'm gonna go teach those
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.38,0:05:39.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那些市区的底层学生了\N{\rEng}underprivileged inner city students
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.59,0:05:41.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让他们的生活翻天覆地\N{\rEng}and really turn their lives around.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.68,0:05:43.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那些小孩会怎么对你吗\N{\rEng}Do you know what those kids are going to do to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.89,0:05:45.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一个中产阶级的白人小孩\N{\rEng}A little middle class white
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.02,0:05:46.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对他们指手画脚\N{\rEng}boy telling them what to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.43,0:05:49.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们会他妈的杀了你的\N{\rEng}They are going to fucking murder you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.71,0:05:54.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也许他是对的\N{\rEng}Maybe he's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.94,0:05:57.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我必须小心我的样子\N{\rEng}I better be careful how I look.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.48,0:06:27.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,同学们  请安静  请安静\N{\rEng}Students   quiet! Quiet   please!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.29,0:06:31.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,都把注意力放在我身上\N{\rEng}Give me your attention.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.22,0:06:32.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我可以整夜都把注意力\N{\rEng}I'll give you my attention
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.66,0:06:35.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,放到你身上  米勒太太\N{\rEng}all night long   Mrs. Miller!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.59,0:06:38.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你是在玩火  罗德里格斯\N{\rEng}You're on thin ice   Rodriguez!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.62,0:06:39.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,听着\N{\rEng}Now listen up.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.73,0:06:41.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,丹佛县学校董事会派来了\N{\rEng}The Denver County School Board has
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.19,0:06:44.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一位特别的客串老师\N{\rEng}sent over a special guest teacher.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.05,0:06:47.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们要想从高中毕业的话\N{\rEng}This may be your last shot at
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.65,0:06:49.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这也许是你们最后的机会了\N{\rEng}graduating from high school at all!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.66,0:06:53.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,请欢迎  埃里克·卡特曼内兹\N{\rEng}I want you to welcome -- Eric Cartmanez.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.59,0:06:57.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们好  同学们\N{\rEng}Hello   students.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.89,0:07:02.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我是埃里克·卡特曼内兹  你们的新老师\N{\rEng}I am Eric Cartmanez   your new teacher.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.96,0:07:05.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他到底是什么玩艺\N{\rEng}What the hell is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.42,0:07:09.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我是来教你们微积分的\N{\rEng}I am here to teach you Calculus.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.76,0:07:14.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想你对于现在的进展\N{\rEng}I think you're going to be very
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.10,0:07:15.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,会非常高兴的  加里森小姐\N{\rEng}pleased with the progress   Ms. Garrison.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.91,0:07:17.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加里森先生\N{\rEng}Mister Garrison!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.26,0:07:19.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  加里森先生\N{\rEng}Sorry   'Mister' Garrison.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.22,0:07:21.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你的DNA在小白鼠身上\N{\rEng}Your DNA has replicated and grafted
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.66,0:07:23.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,复制和移植得非常成功\N{\rEng}very successfully with the mouse.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.67,0:07:28.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你的小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}And so here's your penis.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.23,0:07:31.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,哇  我的小鸡鸡看起来真不错\N{\rEng}Wow   my penis looks great!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.63,0:07:33.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  真是个很棒的小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}Yes   it's a fantastic penis.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.75,0:07:35.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜你\N{\rEng}Congratulations.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.42,0:07:37.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还要多久才能长好\N{\rEng}How long before it's ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.06,0:07:38.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,它还需要一段时间来\N{\rEng}Well   it still has some
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.33,0:07:40.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,成形  但不会太久了\N{\rEng}forming to do   but fairly soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.44,0:07:42.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让我试试握在手里的感觉\N{\rEng}Lemme see if it feels right in my hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.58,0:07:44.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别  不要打开\N{\rEng}No! Don't open the --
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.60,0:07:46.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,噢  不\N{\rEng}Oh   no!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.12,0:07:50.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要让它跑出实验室\N{\rEng}Don't let it get out the lab.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.04,0:07:54.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}My penis!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.96,0:08:00.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,站住  小鸡鸡  快回来\N{\rEng}Stop penis! Come back here!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.50,0:08:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  每个人都拿一份silly bus\N{\rEng}Okey, everyone take a silly bus.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.50,0:08:02.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[译注：silly bus是一个教育机构]
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.64,0:08:05.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,然后传给你身后的朋友\N{\rEng}and pass it to the amigo behind you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.15,0:08:07.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,朋友  你到底想干什么\N{\rEng}Hey man   what the hell do you think you're doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.23,0:08:08.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\rEng}Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.64,0:08:09.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,卡特曼内兹先生到这来是\N{\rEng}Mr. Cartmanez is here to make
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.75,0:08:11.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为了保证你们都能上大学\N{\rEng}sure you all get into college.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.76,0:08:12.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上大学\N{\rEng}Get into college?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.71,0:08:13.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,朋友  我们可\N{\rEng}Man   we aren't getting
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.40,0:08:15.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上不了大学  去你妈的\N{\rEng}into no college? Fuck you!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.11,0:08:16.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,- 没错  -  说得对\N{\rEng}- Yeah   man!  - That's right!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.46,0:08:19.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,- 这到底是什么  - 这是垃圾\N{\rEng}- What is this   anyway?  - Man   this is crap!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.42,0:08:23.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么改变这些小孩\N{\rEng}How do I reeech these keeeds?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.97,0:08:26.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们之所以认为自己进不了大学\N{\rEng}The reason that you think you can't get into college
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.31,0:08:28.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是因为你们没有学过\N{\rEng}is because you haven't been taught --
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.32,0:08:30.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如何正确的作弊\N{\rEng}how to cheat properly.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.14,0:08:32.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们以为白人为什么总是有优势\N{\rEng}How do you think white people always get ahead?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.81,0:08:34.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们总是作弊\N{\rEng}Because we cheat all the time --
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.42,0:08:38.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我是说因为他们总是作弊\N{\rEng}I mean because they cheat all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.91,0:08:41.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是比尔·比利奇克\N{\rEng}This is Bill Beeelichick.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.15,0:08:42.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,新英格兰爱国者队的教练\N{\rEng}Coach of the New England Patriots.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.94,0:08:45.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他已经赢得了三次超级杯了  怎么赢的\N{\rEng}He's won three superbowls. How?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.33,0:08:47.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,靠作弊\N{\rEng}He cheated.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.12,0:08:50.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他甚至作弊被抓了现行  但没人在乎\N{\rEng}He even got caught cheating. And nobody cared.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.15,0:08:51.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,比尔·比利奇克证明了\N{\rEng}Bill Beelicheck proved that
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.46,0:08:53.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在美国作弊是可行的\N{\rEng}in America it's ok to cheat  
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.17,0:08:56.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,只能你能通过作弊达到巅峰\N{\rEng}as long as you cheat your way to the top.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.01,0:08:58.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  我可不想被人称做骗子\N{\rEng}Hey   I don't want to be called a cheater.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.27,0:09:00.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不会  如果你作弊后还是失败了\N{\rEng}No   no   if you cheat and fail  
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.64,0:09:01.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你才是个骗子\N{\rEng}you're a cheater.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.85,0:09:03.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果你通过作弊成功了\N{\rEng}If you cheat and succeed
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.64,0:09:05.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你就是王道\N{\rEng}you're savvyyyy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.55,0:09:07.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,胡说八道\N{\rEng}This is bullshit!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.03,0:09:09.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想浪费时间来学作弊\N{\rEng}I don't want to waste my time learning to cheat!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.72,0:09:10.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  门就在那儿\N{\rEng}Go ahead   the door's right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.74,0:09:14.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,再见  好自为之  我们会想你的\N{\rEng}Bye   bye   have fun   we will miss you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.70,0:09:19.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么改变这些小孩\N{\rEng}How do I reach these kids?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.12,0:09:24.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们\N{\rEng}Boys!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.40,0:09:27.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们  看见我的小鸡鸡了吗\N{\rEng}Boys   have you seen my penis?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.88,0:09:29.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.78,0:09:31.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的小鸡鸡跑了\N{\rEng}My penis is on the loose!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.46,0:09:32.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们看见了\N{\rEng}If you see it   just try to
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.57,0:09:34.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就用奶酪来诱捕它\N{\rEng}catch it with some cheese!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.61,0:09:39.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的大脑要崩溃了\N{\rEng}Ow   that hurt my brains.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.28,0:09:53.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好身材  朋友\N{\rEng}Nice form   compadre.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.18,0:09:55.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我跷了你的课  老师\N{\rEng}Hey I walked out of your class   teacher.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.77,0:09:56.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我不想跟你争辩\N{\rEng}Look   I don't want to argue with
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.67,0:09:58.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,作弊的好处\N{\rEng}you about the merits of cheating.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.48,0:10:00.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这么好的天气谁想争辩啊\N{\rEng}Who wants to argue on a nice day like theeees.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.58,0:10:02.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来单挑怎么样\N{\rEng}How about a little pickup game?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.01,0:10:04.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  皮塔诺\N{\rEng}Hey   Petano!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.42,0:10:05.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,能帮我们计分吗\N{\rEng}Can you keep score for us?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.81,0:10:08.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没问题  卡先生\N{\rEng}Sure thing   Mr. C.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.42,0:10:10.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你先防守  朋友\N{\rEng}Okay   you start on defense   amigo.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.95,0:10:20.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,1比0了  朋友\N{\rEng}Oho   that's one to nothing   amigo.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.21,0:10:21.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你作弊\N{\rEng}You cheated!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.52,0:10:23.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,比分是多少\N{\rEng}What's the score   Effe?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.04,0:10:25.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  再来  该你进攻了\N{\rEng}Okay   let's go. Your turn.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.28,0:10:33.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,2比0了  朋友\N{\rEng}That's two to noteeeng   amigo.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.29,0:10:35.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,去你妈的  你不能那样做\N{\rEng}Fuck you   man! You can't do that!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.62,0:10:38.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看看比分牌吧  朋友\N{\rEng}Look at the scoreboard   amigo.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.51,0:10:41.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,无论你说多少次我作弊\N{\rEng}No matter how many times you say I cheated  
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.06,0:10:44.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,比分牌始终是2比0\N{\rEng}the scoreboard says 2-0.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.37,0:10:45.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你想说什么\N{\rEng}I know what you're trying to say  
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.74,0:10:48.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但我还是不会赞同的\N{\rEng}but I still don't agree with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.56,0:10:51.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,2比0了\N{\rEng}Two to nothing   essa.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.41,0:10:53.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,2比0\N{\rEng}Two to nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.70,0:10:57.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么改变这些小孩\N{\rEng}Hoh   how do I reach these keedz?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.55,0:11:05.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么\N{\rEng}What is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.27,0:11:17.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,斯蒂芬  斯蒂芬  快来\N{\rEng}Stephen! Stephen   come quick!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.41,0:11:18.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  亲爱的\N{\rEng}What is it   dear?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.61,0:11:21.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有一个小鸡鸡跑到我们厨房来了\N{\rEng}A penis is loose in our kitchen!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.22,0:11:22.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}A penis?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.15,0:11:24.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  刚刚从地板上穿过去\N{\rEng}Yes   it just ran across the floor!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.59,0:11:26.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  冷静一点\N{\rEng}Now darling   calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.56,0:11:27.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,冷静什么  我可不想\N{\rEng}Calm down nothing   I don't want
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.95,0:11:30.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那个小鸡鸡在我家里乱跑\N{\rEng}that penis running through my house!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.26,0:11:33.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,女人  总是害怕小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}Ah   women   always afraid of penises.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.25,0:11:38.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在那儿  看到了吧\N{\rEng}There! There you see it!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.27,0:11:40.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,只是一个很小的小鸡鸡  亲爱的\N{\rEng}Oh   it's just a little penis   darling.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.56,0:11:44.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不管  它可能带有很多病毒\N{\rEng}I don't care   it's probably got all kinds of diseases.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.96,0:11:47.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,慢着  我想那是我们老师的小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}Hey   wait! I think that's teacher's penis!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.13,0:11:48.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们老师的小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}Your teacher's penis?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.36,0:11:49.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  一定是他的\N{\rEng}Yeah   that must be his!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.91,0:11:51.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  你怎么知道你们\N{\rEng}Butters   how do you know what
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.87,0:11:53.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老师的小鸡鸡长什么样子\N{\rEng}your teacher's penis looks like?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.31,0:11:57.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,今天要讲的是作弊\N{\rEng}Today   we will discuss one of the
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.51,0:11:59.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,最基础的方法之一\N{\rEng}fundamental ways to cheat --
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.12,0:12:01.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在考试前把考试内容搞到手\N{\rEng}getting test material ahead of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.36,0:12:02.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,比尔·比利奇克是怎么\N{\rEng}When Bill Belichick cheated for
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.69,0:12:04.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,替爱国者队作弊的\N{\rEng}the Patriots   what did he do?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.30,0:12:07.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他录下了对手的防守\N{\rEng}He videotaped the opposing team's defense.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.42,0:12:09.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,把防守看成是你们的考试\N{\rEng}Think of the defense as your test.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.70,0:12:13.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们同样需要录下它的防守\N{\rEng}When taking a test you must also videotape the defense.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.76,0:12:15.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在正式开考之前先知道\N{\rEng}Learn what's on the test before they
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.54,0:12:18.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,考试的内容  那么你们就能\N{\rEng}give it to you   and that way you can --
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.92,0:12:24.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想  也许我可以尝试一下作弊\N{\rEng}I thought that   well   maybe I could give cheating a try.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.18,0:12:26.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,请坐吧  朋友\N{\rEng}Have a seat   amigo.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.68,0:12:29.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴你回来\N{\rEng}Good to have you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.04,0:12:29.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\rEng}Alright.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.71,0:12:31.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当比尔·比利奇克连同摄像机\N{\rEng}Now   when Bill Belichick got caught
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.35,0:12:33.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一起被抓现行时  他没有慌张\N{\rEng}with his camera   he did not panic.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.66,0:12:34.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他只是说了每一个优秀白人\N{\rEng}He simply said what every good
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.95,0:12:36.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,作弊者被抓住时说的话\N{\rEng}white cheater says when caught:
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.36,0:12:39.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我理解错了规则\N{\rEng}I misinterpreted the rules.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.31,0:12:40.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们如果作弊被抓住了\N{\rEng}It's what you must also say
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.26,0:12:41.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也必须这么说\N{\rEng}when caught cheating.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.27,0:12:43.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我理解错了规则\N{\rEng}"I misinterpreted the rules."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.19,0:12:45.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,跟着我说  我理解错了规则\N{\rEng}Say it with me "i misinterpreted the rules."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.86,0:12:46.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很好  再来一遍\N{\rEng}Good! Again!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.77,0:12:49.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我理解错了规则  再来一遍\N{\rEng}I misinterpreted the rules! Again!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.37,0:12:51.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我理解错了规则\N{\rEng}I misinterpreted the rules!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.62,0:12:53.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在你们听起来像是白人了\N{\rEng}Now you sound like white people!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.13,0:12:55.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我理解错了规则\N{\rEng}I misinterpreted the rules!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.00,0:12:57.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么叫你把\N{\rEng}What the hell do you mean
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.80,0:13:00.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的小弟弟放在门外\N{\rEng}you just put my penis outside?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.21,0:13:01.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不通知我\N{\rEng}Why didn't you call me?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.56,0:13:03.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,听着  加里森  我太太不想家里有\N{\rEng}Look   Garrison   my wife didn't want a
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.27,0:13:05.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小鸡鸡  我不得不把它弄出去\N{\rEng}penis in the house   I had to get it out!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.48,0:13:07.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那我现在到哪儿去找它\N{\rEng}Well now how am I supposed to find it?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.34,0:13:09.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,它可能在任何地方\N{\rEng}It could be anywhere!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.71,0:13:13.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\rEng}Holy crap!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.72,0:13:17.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,卡罗尔  快下来\N{\rEng}Carol   get down from there!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.43,0:13:20.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  你刚刚没看到那个小鸡鸡吗\N{\rEng}No! Didn't you see that penis just now?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.22,0:13:22.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我相信那个小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}I'm sure that penis is way more
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.90,0:13:25.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,比你怕它更害怕你\N{\rEng}scared of you than you are of it!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.41,0:13:27.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你看见了一个小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}You saw a penis?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.12,0:13:32.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很大很恶心\N{\rEng}It's so big and disgusting!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.35,0:13:40.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快回来  小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}Come back here   penis!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.96,0:13:44.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在这儿  抓住你了\N{\rEng}There you are! Got you!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.98,0:13:49.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  你可不是我的小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}Hey you are not my penis
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.81,0:13:55.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在这儿  站住\N{\rEng}There it goes. Stop   you!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.82,0:13:59.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,第27题的答案是5\N{\rEng}The answer to number 27 is five.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.53,0:14:02.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,第27题的答案是5\N{\rEng}The answer to number 27 is five.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.65,0:14:05.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,第28题的答案是14\N{\rEng}The answer to number 28 is fourteen.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.48,0:14:08.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,第28题的答案是14\N{\rEng}The answer to number 28 is fourteen.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.41,0:14:10.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  这有意义吗\N{\rEng}Man   what's the point?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.29,0:14:12.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这一切都有意义吗\N{\rEng}What's the point of any of this?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.23,0:14:17.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  所有人复习播音员\N{\rEng}Alright   everyone review the section on
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.17,0:14:18.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,原谅爱国者队作弊\N{\rEng}sportscasters forgiving the Patriots for cheating
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.68,0:14:19.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,并且不以为然的片段\N{\rEng}and saying it was no big deal
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.64,0:14:21.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我很快就回来\N{\rEng}I'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.39,0:14:25.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,马丽塔  马丽塔  等等\N{\rEng}Malita! Malita   hold on!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.79,0:14:27.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你不能现在放弃\N{\rEng}You can't quit now?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.04,0:14:28.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了\N{\rEng}Come on   what's wrong with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.67,0:14:31.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这一切都毫无意义\N{\rEng}There isn't any point to all this.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.01,0:14:33.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不会上大学的\N{\rEng}I won't be going to college.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.24,0:14:35.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我怀孕了  行了吧\N{\rEng}I'm pregnant   alright?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.86,0:14:37.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我刚刚发现\N{\rEng}I just found out.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.07,0:14:38.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,而且爱德华多不会帮我\N{\rEng}And Eduardo isn't gonna
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.22,0:14:39.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来抚养小孩的\N{\rEng}help me raise it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.55,0:14:44.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么改变这些小孩\N{\rEng}How do I reach these keeeds?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.17,0:14:46.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我带你去堕胎\N{\rEng}Alright   let's go get you an abortion.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.24,0:14:47.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  我是天主教徒\N{\rEng}No   I'm Catholic.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.83,0:14:50.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我认为堕胎是错误的\N{\rEng}I think abortion is wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.16,0:14:51.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,堕胎不是错误的\N{\rEng}Abortion isn't wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.56,0:14:54.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在教你们什么\N{\rEng}What's the one thing I've been teaching you?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.35,0:14:56.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,作弊是正确的\N{\rEng}That cheating is good.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.06,0:14:57.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.03,0:14:59.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,堕胎是作弊的终极形式\N{\rEng}And abortion is the ultimate form of cheating.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.28,0:15:01.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是在欺骗生理本质\N{\rEng}You're cheating nature itself!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.21,0:15:02.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为什么富家白人女孩\N{\rEng}Why do rich white
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.94,0:15:04.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在生活中总是领先\N{\rEng}girls get ahead in life?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.33,0:15:05.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,因为她们在年轻的\N{\rEng}Because they get abortions
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.37,0:15:06.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,时候就堕过胎了\N{\rEng}when they're young.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.68,0:15:08.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果她们怀孕了  但是仍然想进入\N{\rEng}They get pregnant   but they still want to
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.34,0:15:10.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大学  那么她们就作弊\N{\rEng}go to college so whatever   they just cheat.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.65,0:15:12.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,她们通过作弊夺走\N{\rEng}They cheat that little critter in their
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.15,0:15:14.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肚子里小家伙获得生命的机会\N{\rEng}belly right out of a chance at life.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.95,0:15:16.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  卡先生\N{\rEng}I don't know   Mr. C.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.81,0:15:18.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,墨西哥人都被教导说不能作弊\N{\rEng}Mexicans are told not to cheat.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.60,0:15:20.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不作弊  怀孕了那\N{\rEng}Don't cheat   you got pregnant
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.02,0:15:21.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你只能抚养这个孩子\N{\rEng}you have to raise the child  
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.53,0:15:22.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当你抚养这个孩子的时候\N{\rEng}so then you have to raise a child while
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.99,0:15:24.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,白人女孩都去上大学了\N{\rEng}the white girls get to go to college
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.10,0:15:27.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,并且也许还会继续堕胎\N{\rEng}and probably have a bunch more abortions.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.67,0:15:29.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,越是在困难的时候\N{\rEng}It is at our most challenging times
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.25,0:15:33.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,越是需要我们更努力地作弊\N{\rEng}that we must cheat our very hardest.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.26,0:15:37.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你上一次见到你的\N{\rEng}And the last time you saw
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.37,0:15:39.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小鸡鸡是两天前\N{\rEng}your penis was two days ago?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.68,0:15:40.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.88,0:15:42.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,长毛还是短毛\N{\rEng}Long whiskers or short?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.60,0:15:44.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,短的  还有一对毛茸茸的小耳朵\N{\rEng}Short. And little fluffy ears.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.70,0:15:46.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,毛茸茸的耳朵  好的\N{\rEng}Fluffy ears   ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.69,0:15:47.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,画出来了吗  米奇\N{\rEng}Think you got it   Mitch?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.70,0:15:49.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,画出来了  长官\N{\rEng}I think so   sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.04,0:15:51.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这个像吗\N{\rEng}Is this pretty close?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.00,0:15:56.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不是那样的\N{\rEng}No   no! Not like that!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.08,0:15:57.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那很愚蠢\N{\rEng}That's just silly.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.78,0:15:59.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,长官  我们也许需要派一队人\N{\rEng}Sir   we might want to get a unit down
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.39,0:16:01.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,到肯特纳大街的意大利餐馆去\N{\rEng}to the Italian restaurant on Kentner.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.20,0:16:01.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,出什么事了\N{\rEng}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.96,0:16:03.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,刚接到电话\N{\rEng}Call just came through.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.03,0:16:05.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,说有一个小鸡鸡冲进去抢奶酪吃\N{\rEng}Seems a penis broke in and try to eat their cheese.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.41,0:16:07.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快走\N{\rEng}Well   come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.10,0:16:17.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\rEng}What's the matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.20,0:16:18.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有一个小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}A penis!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.00,0:16:20.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小鸡鸡  在哪儿\N{\rEng}A penis? Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.57,0:16:22.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在这儿\N{\rEng}There it is!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.57,0:16:29.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在哪儿\N{\rEng}Where is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.59,0:16:31.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在那儿\N{\rEng}Look there!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.16,0:16:34.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快\N{\rEng}Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.12,0:16:35.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的厨房里\N{\rEng}What's that a penis
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.38,0:16:37.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会有个小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}doing in a my kitchen?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.30,0:16:41.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你敢干掉我的小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}Don't you dare kill my penis!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.16,0:16:44.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,靠  我们从后面绕过去\N{\rEng}Crap! We gotta go back around!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.39,0:17:00.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*某人  在某地*\N{\rEng}*Someone  somewhere*
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.17,0:17:04.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*在今晚爱着我*\N{\rEng}*is loving me tonight*
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.11,0:17:07.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*遥望着一样的月亮*\N{\rEng}*Looking at the same moon*
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.30,0:17:11.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*看着它是如此的明亮*\N{\rEng}*and seeing it so bright*
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.01,0:17:14.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*某人  在某地*\N{\rEng}*Someone   somewhere*
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.25,0:17:17.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*感受到我的绝望*\N{\rEng}*is feeling my despair*
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.21,0:17:19.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*这相同的月亮*\N{\rEng}*and this same moon is*
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.72,0:17:21.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*让他们联想*\N{\rEng}*making them think  of that*
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.43,0:17:23.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在这儿\N{\rEng}There it is!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.23,0:17:29.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  不\N{\rEng}No! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.61,0:17:32.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  不\N{\rEng}Nooo! Nooooo!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.66,0:17:34.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在没有机会了\N{\rEng}There's not a chance now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.50,0:17:36.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  我们还能找到它\N{\rEng}No! We can find it!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.39,0:17:39.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  加里森  你的小鸡鸡完蛋了\N{\rEng}Sorry  Garrison  your penis is gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.78,0:17:41.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我恐怕我们帮不了什么忙了\N{\rEng}I'm afraid there's nothing more we can do.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.01,0:17:44.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你安心做你的女人吧\N{\rEng}You'll just have to live with being a woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.70,0:17:47.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一个超级丑女  我们走\N{\rEng}A very ugly one. Come on  men.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.82,0:17:51.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,同学们  我想恭喜你们\N{\rEng}Students  I want to congratulate
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.63,0:17:53.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,取得令人惊异的好成绩\N{\rEng}you on your amazing test scores.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.64,0:17:55.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,学校董事会对你们的\N{\rEng}The school board is so
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.01,0:17:56.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,进步非常欣慰\N{\rEng}impressed with your progress  
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.74,0:17:59.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所以他们准备让你们参加能\N{\rEng}that they are going to let you take the standardized
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.70,0:18:02.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,换取大学学分的AP测验\N{\rEng}Advanced Placement test for college credit!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.71,0:18:04.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-太好了  -酷\N{\rEng}-Alright!  -Cool  man.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.46,0:18:06.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这个测验被安排在考试中心的\N{\rEng}The test is going to be heavily monitored
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.53,0:18:08.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,独立房间内  并且受到严格监考\N{\rEng}in a private room at their location
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.54,0:18:12.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,以杜绝作弊\N{\rEng}to assure that there can be absolutely no cheating.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.03,0:18:13.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}Uh what?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.95,0:18:15.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,测验将会安排在明天\N{\rEng}The test will be tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.32,0:18:17.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别让我们失望\N{\rEng}Make us proud.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.22,0:18:21.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在独立房间里对我们监考\N{\rEng}Monitor us in a private room?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.50,0:18:22.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们会发现我们\N{\rEng}Now they're gonna know we've
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.60,0:18:24.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一直是在作弊的\N{\rEng}been cheating all along!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.01,0:18:25.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道\N{\rEng}I knew it  man!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.38,0:18:26.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你让我们相信你的方法\N{\rEng}You made us believe in your way  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.77,0:18:28.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,到头来还是一场空\N{\rEng}and now it's all for nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.58,0:18:29.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不会一场空\N{\rEng}It's not for nothing!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.42,0:18:30.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们足够厉害  你们\N{\rEng}If you're good enough you can
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.56,0:18:31.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,可以当着他们的面作弊\N{\rEng}cheat right in front of them!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.58,0:18:34.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴  朋友  你彻底地毁了我们\N{\rEng}Shut up man  you royally screwed us all!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.11,0:18:38.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么改变这些小孩\N{\rEng}How do I reeeeech these keeeeeds!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.37,0:18:42.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就在最后那次超级杯开始前\N{\rEng}Just before the last Superbowl  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.36,0:18:44.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,比尔·比利奇克集合了他的队员\N{\rEng}Bill Belichick gathered his football players
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.38,0:18:47.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对他们说  让我们真正地赢一次\N{\rEng}and said "let's win this one for real.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.19,0:18:50.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这一次  我们不作弊\N{\rEng}Just this one time  let's not cheat."
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.42,0:18:53.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们知道结果怎么样  他们输了\N{\rEng}You know what happened? They losT.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.45,0:18:57.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,即使你感觉到所有人都在注视你\N{\rEng}Even if you feel all eyes are upon you  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.60,0:19:00.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你也不能放弃作弊\N{\rEng}you cannot give on cheating
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.11,0:19:01.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,否则你可能会输掉\N{\rEng}or else you can lose the
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.18,0:19:04.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一生中最重要的比赛\N{\rEng}biggest game of your lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.09,0:19:07.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我们能行  伙计们\N{\rEng}Yeah  come on  we can do this  guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.24,0:19:08.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们是真正的梦想家\N{\rEng}You are the true dreamers.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.78,0:19:10.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,明天你们会证明自己的\N{\rEng}Tomorrow you will prove it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.39,0:19:11.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们从如何把小纸条打印\N{\rEng}We will begin by reviewing how to print out
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.86,0:19:14.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,成瓶装水的标签开始复习\N{\rEng}cheat sheets as labels for your bottled water.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.28,0:19:24.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你是自作自受  加里森\N{\rEng}You did this to yourself  Garrison.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.43,0:19:25.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让一个愚蠢的基因实验\N{\rEng}Get your hopes up with a
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.68,0:19:27.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,燃起你的希望\N{\rEng}stupid genetic experiment
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.19,0:19:30.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在钱和小鸡鸡都没了\N{\rEng}and now all your money's gone along with your penis.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.36,0:19:39.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么\N{\rEng}What the --
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.17,0:19:46.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  是我的小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}why -- it's my penis.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.19,0:19:50.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的小鸡鸡回来了  怎么会呢\N{\rEng}My penis came bacK. But why?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.55,0:19:57.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想那是对的\N{\rEng}I guess it's true.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.16,0:19:59.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那个俗语怎么说来着\N{\rEng}What's that old saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.69,0:20:03.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果你爱你的小鸡鸡  放开它吧\N{\rEng}If you love your penis  let it go?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.80,0:20:08.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,标准化AP测验\N{\rEng}The standardized Advanced Placement test
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.11,0:20:10.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,被认为是全国最难的\N{\rEng}is considered one of the most difficult
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.12,0:20:13.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,和监考最严格的考试之一\N{\rEng}and carefully monitored tests in the country.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.18,0:20:15.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们有24位学生参加了测验\N{\rEng}Twenty four of our students took the test
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.50,0:20:20.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所有24人都得了满分\N{\rEng}and all twenty four scored one hundred percent!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.93,0:20:24.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们能说几句吗\N{\rEng}Uh  can we say something?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.58,0:20:25.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当然\N{\rEng}Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.73,0:20:27.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们想把这个荣誉框送给教会了\N{\rEng}We would like to present this plaque to the person
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.83,0:20:31.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们白人方法的卡特曼内兹先生\N{\rEng}who taught us the white people method  Mr.Cartmanez.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.02,0:20:48.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我改变了这些小孩\N{\rEng}I reeeeched these keeeeeeeds.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.87,0:20:53.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,同学们  老师们  请鼓掌\N{\rEng}Students and faculty  please put your hands together
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.61,0:20:58.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,同我一起欢迎加里森老师的归来\N{\rEng}and help me in welcoming back Mister Garrison.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.72,0:21:05.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢大家\N{\rEng}Thanks  everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.14,0:21:07.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真高兴回来\N{\rEng}It's great to be bacK.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.06,0:21:08.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我又是一个男人了\N{\rEng}I'm a man again.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.73,0:21:12.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了我的特殊新朋友\N{\rEng}Thanks to my very special new friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.96,0:21:15.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我懂得了其实\N{\rEng}But you know  I've learned that
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.99,0:21:18.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我一直是个男人\N{\rEng}I've really been a dude all along.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.97,0:21:20.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,因为男人和女人最主要的\N{\rEng}Because the key difference between men
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.88,0:21:24.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,区别  是女人可以生小孩\N{\rEng}and women  is that women can have babies.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.49,0:21:26.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不能生小孩\N{\rEng}If you can't have babies  
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.21,0:21:28.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那你就是个男人\N{\rEng}then you're a man.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.09,0:21:30.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,慢着  等一下\N{\rEng}Woa  uh  wait. Hang on a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.95,0:21:32.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我太太得过卵巢癌\N{\rEng}My wife had ovarian cancer  
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.63,0:21:35.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所以她生不了小孩\N{\rEng}so she can't have babies.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.67,0:21:37.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那快去做个艾滋检查  汤普森\N{\rEng}Well  then get an AIDS test  Thompson
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.29,0:21:40.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,因为你老婆是个男人  死基佬\N{\rEng}cuz your wife's a dude  faggot.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.93,0:21:44.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,耶  我回来了\N{\rEng}Yeah! I'm back!
