[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2008-10-30 08:43:29
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayDepth: 0
PlayResX: 1916
PlayResY: 1076
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 2
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H19000000,&H000E0300,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,2,2,134,120,68,1
Style: eng,Microsoft YaHei,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,26,1
Style: Top,微软雅黑,10,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Git,Comic Sans MS,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Chn,微软雅黑,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Eng,Comic Sans MS,60,&H002AF7FF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.20,0:00:11.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm going down to south park\N gonna have myself a time 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.05,0:00:15.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Friendly faces everywhere\N humble folks without temptation 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.33,0:00:18.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Going down to south park\N gonna leave my woes behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.72,0:00:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ample parking day or night\N people shouting howdy neighbor
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.96,0:00:24.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heading on out to south park\N gonna see if I can't unwind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.54,0:00:28.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I like girls with big vaginas\N I like girls with big fat titties
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.61,0:00:31.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.40,0:21:45.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译制作\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}YYeTs人人影视字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.40,0:21:47.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}校译\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}荨香 sunflo
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.40,0:21:48.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1c&HFDC282&}后期\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}csbeyond
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.60,0:00:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0150,,{\1c&HFDC282&}南方公园  第12季第6集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.60,0:00:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0100,,超负荷\N{\rEng}Over Logging
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.53,0:00:39.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,下线  斯坦  该睡觉了\N{\rEng}Get off the internet   Stanley. It's time for bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.95,0:00:41.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  我还有一点事要做\N{\rEng}Mom   I just got to do a couple more things.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.80,0:00:43.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不行  斯坦利  明早再弄\N{\rEng}Now   Stanley! The internet will be
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.54,0:00:44.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,互联网又不会跑掉\N{\rEng}waiting for you in the morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.85,0:00:46.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,关了\N{\rEng}Off!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.11,0:00:48.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌\N{\rEng}Aw   man!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.65,0:00:52.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谢莉  下线  该睡觉了\N{\rEng}Shelley   off the internet. It's bedtime.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.54,0:00:56.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,妈  我在跟我蒙大拿的男朋友聊天呢\N{\rEng}Mom   I'm I-chatting with my boyfriend in Montana.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.03,0:00:58.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快点  谢莉\N{\rEng}Now   Shelley!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.16,0:01:01.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛找我麻烦\N{\rEng}Why do you hate me?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.24,0:01:02.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  下线\N{\rEng}Randy   off the internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.92,0:01:05.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  拜托  别管我\N{\rEng}No! No   come on! Leave me alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.50,0:01:07.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不行  要睡觉觉了\N{\rEng}No   mister. It's time for night-night.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.49,0:01:09.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是  莎朗  我还有事情要做\N{\rEng}But Sharon   I got stuff to do!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.46,0:01:10.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我要查看我的信用评分\N{\rEng}I got to see my credit rating
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.49,0:01:11.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,要给内尔森发邮件\N{\rEng}and I got to send an e-mail Nelson
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.90,0:01:14.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还要看看佛力的旅游照片\N{\rEng}and check out Foley's vacation photos --
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.19,0:01:15.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,又没必要都现在做\N{\rEng}You don't have to do all that now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.96,0:01:19.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那就让你在睡前  再干一件事吧\N{\rEng}You can do one more thing and then it's bedtime.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.25,0:01:23.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,再干一件事?\N{\rEng}One more thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.93,0:01:43.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有没有搞错\N{\rEng}What the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.45,0:01:44.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,斯坦\N{\rEng}Stan!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.10,0:01:46.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-斯坦  我要用你的电脑  -什么\N{\rEng}- Stan   i got to use your computer. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.11,0:01:48.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我上不了网  借用一下你的\N{\rEng}My internet's not working. I got to use yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.22,0:01:50.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,给爸爸一点私人时间  好吗\N{\rEng}And give daddy some private time   will yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.33,0:01:52.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-我也上不了网啊  -不会吧\N{\rEng}- My internet's not working either. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.81,0:01:55.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  上不了网了\N{\rEng}Dad   the internet's not working!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.89,0:01:57.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\rEng}I know that   okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.30,0:01:58.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我必须在上学前  和我\N{\rEng}I have to get online with my
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.68,0:02:01.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的埃米尔在网上碰面\N{\rEng}darling Amir before school starts.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.89,0:02:04.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  我邮箱打不开\N{\rEng}Randy   i can't get my e-mail to open.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.32,0:02:07.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大家都冷静点  冷静  好吗\N{\rEng}Everyone just calm down. Calm down   all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.53,0:02:09.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,会好起来的\N{\rEng}It's going to be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.10,0:02:12.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要恐慌\N{\rEng}We just can't panic.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.26,0:02:15.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,杰拉德  请帮帮我们\N{\rEng}Gerald   please help us.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.99,0:02:18.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  怎么了\N{\rEng}Randy! What's happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.09,0:02:21.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们家  上不了网\N{\rEng}Our house. It has no internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.39,0:02:22.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天哪\N{\rEng}Oh   my god.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.01,0:02:24.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,完全没有信号\N{\rEng}We've got nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.70,0:02:26.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,网络消失了\N{\rEng}It's just gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.37,0:02:28.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,进来吧  在你们的网络修好之前\N{\rEng}Come in. You can use our internet
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.41,0:02:30.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,先用我们家的吧\N{\rEng}until you figure out what to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.22,0:02:31.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  杰拉德\N{\rEng}Thank you   Gerald.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.67,0:02:33.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我第一个上\N{\rEng}I'm getting on it first.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.16,0:02:35.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不行  不行\N{\rEng}Oh   no   you're not!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.51,0:02:36.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  能用你的电脑上一下网吗\N{\rEng}Kyle   can I use your internet?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.76,0:02:38.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-上不了  －不会吧\N{\rEng}- It's not working. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.37,0:02:41.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我拔了网线重新再插上也没用\N{\rEng}I've even unplugged it and plugged it back in.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.23,0:02:43.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  互联网不能坏啊\N{\rEng}No   no. Our internet can't be broken.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.85,0:02:46.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我必须去收拉里昨晚发给我的附件\N{\rEng}I've got to get an attachment Larry sent me last night!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.67,0:02:48.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上不了  杰拉德\N{\rEng}It's not working   Gerald.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.01,0:02:49.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但必须得上啊  也许我该...\N{\rEng}But it has to work. Maybe if I --
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.49,0:02:52.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们的网坏了  杰拉德  面对事实吧\N{\rEng}Your internet's not working   Gerald. Face it!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.21,0:02:53.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,去上学前我必须得上网\N{\rEng}I have to get online before school.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.83,0:02:55.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,星巴克呢  他们有免费的互联网\N{\rEng}What about starbucks? They have free internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.68,0:02:56.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对  星巴克\N{\rEng}Right! Starbucks!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.90,0:02:59.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,带上你们的东西  乘我的车去\N{\rEng}Everyone get your stuff. We can take my car.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.29,0:03:03.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们能上网吗\N{\rEng}Hey   is your guys' internet working?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.28,0:03:05.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不行  都上不了\N{\rEng}No. Nobody's is.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.22,0:03:07.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事\N{\rEng}What's happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.56,0:03:10.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  现在大家都得去星巴克了\N{\rEng}Jesus   everyone's gonna have to go to starbucks now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.05,0:03:13.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,全都上车  我们得比他们先赶过去\N{\rEng}Everyone in the car! We have to beat them there!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.68,0:03:20.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  这一片的人都被影响到了\N{\rEng}God   the whole neighborhood's affected.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.15,0:03:23.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,滚开  彼得森\N{\rEng}Get out of the way   Peterson!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.84,0:03:27.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,市民们  这里也不能上网\N{\rEng}Folks   there's no internet here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.91,0:03:29.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这里不能上网\N{\rEng}It's not working   I tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.37,0:03:30.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这儿也不能上网吗\N{\rEng}It's not working here?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.77,0:03:31.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们  回车里去\N{\rEng}Kids   get back in the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.73,0:03:33.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以去苹果专卖店\N{\rEng}We can go to the Mac store.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.04,0:03:34.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别去了  浪费时间\N{\rEng}No   don't! You're wasting your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.90,0:03:35.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道的\N{\rEng}How do you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.94,0:03:37.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们刚刚从那边过来\N{\rEng}Because we just came from there.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.94,0:03:39.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那儿也不行\N{\rEng}There was nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.01,0:03:41.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一点儿网络的影子都没有\N{\rEng}Not one scrap of internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.88,0:03:43.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能到处都上不了网\N{\rEng}How can there be no internet anywhere?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.68,0:03:44.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊\N{\rEng}What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.79,0:03:46.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谁有黑莓手机\N{\rEng}Anybody got a blackberry?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.03,0:03:47.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,百度一下\N{\rEng}Check drudge report.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.43,0:03:48.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好主意  不  等一下\N{\rEng}Good idea! No   wait!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.85,0:03:51.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们百度不了啊  根本上不了网\N{\rEng}We can't check drudge report. There's no internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.30,0:03:53.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯定还有别的办法来弄清到底怎么了\N{\rEng}There has to be a way to find out what's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.50,0:03:55.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没有  你们还不明白吗\N{\rEng}We can't! Don't you get it?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.27,0:03:57.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,根本无法上网来了解为什么无法上网\N{\rEng}There's no internet to find out why there's no internet!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.93,0:03:59.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,以前没有互联网的时候\N{\rEng}What did we use to get the news
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.39,0:04:02.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们是怎么获得新闻的\N{\rEng}before the internet?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.65,0:04:05.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,电视\N{\rEng}A television!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.65,0:04:17.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉  我们不能为您报道新闻了\N{\rEng}Once again   we apologize but we cannot bring you the news.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.02,0:04:22.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看起来我们第四新闻台无法上网\N{\rEng}It appears that we have no internet here at News 4.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.81,0:04:24.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一旦可以上网\N{\rEng}We'll be happy to bring you up on current events.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.94,0:04:27.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们就会向大家即时播报新闻的\N{\rEng}Just as soon as our internet is back.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.74,0:04:29.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  全州都上不了\N{\rEng}Jesus   it's statewide.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.60,0:04:31.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有可能全国都上不了\N{\rEng}It could be nationwide.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.49,0:04:34.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你们能上网吗\N{\rEng}Hello? Do you have internet?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.64,0:04:37.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这儿是第四频道新闻\N{\rEng}It's channel four news.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.41,0:04:40.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们也上不了\N{\rEng}No   we don't have internet either.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.75,0:04:45.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,到处都没有互联网\N{\rEng}No internet anywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.41,0:04:49.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  我们与世隔绝了\N{\rEng}Jesus   we're all alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.74,0:05:00.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正综艺简体}{\fs12}{\b0}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\3c&H2F2F2F&}{\4c&H000000&}星期一
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.43,0:05:04.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正综艺简体}{\fs12}{\b0}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\3c&H2F2F2F&}{\4c&H000000&}不能上网第八天
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.12,0:05:12.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了\N{\rEng}What's the matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.10,0:05:13.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不知道\N{\rEng}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.46,0:05:15.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我得上网查一下为什么\N{\rEng}I need to get on web and see why
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.31,0:05:17.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我会咳嗽  但是不行\N{\rEng}I have this cough   but I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.92,0:05:21.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,要是我的甜心在网上找我可怎么办\N{\rEng}What if my sweetheart is online looking for me?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.02,0:05:23.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他会奇怪为什么我没有上网见他\N{\rEng}He could be wondering why I don't get online with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.93,0:05:26.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也许他以为我死了\N{\rEng}Maybe he thinks I'm dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.56,0:05:28.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果我亲爱的埃米尔在网上交了\N{\rEng}If my darling Amir gets another internet
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.46,0:05:30.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,另一个女朋友的话  我就杀了他\N{\rEng}girlfriend   I'm going to kill him.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.49,0:05:32.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还有你\N{\rEng}And you!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.11,0:05:35.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谢莉  谢莉  住手  住手\N{\rEng}Shelley! Shelley   woa   stop! Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.37,0:05:37.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,爸  你得想想办法  她已经发狂了\N{\rEng}Dad   you got to do something! She's out of control.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.98,0:05:42.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你说的没错  我们不能坐以待毙\N{\rEng}You're right. We can't just sit here any longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.24,0:05:48.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  你们要去哪儿啊\N{\rEng}Randy   where will you go?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.33,0:05:49.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们要向西走\N{\rEng}We're gonna head west.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.66,0:05:50.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有人说  那里可能\N{\rEng}There's a rumor going around that
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.71,0:05:53.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,会有互联网\N{\rEng}there might be some internet out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.14,0:05:55.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们向着加州前进\N{\rEng}So we're heading out California way.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.05,0:05:57.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你又不知道加州是不是真的能上网\N{\rEng}You don't know if there's any internet in California!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.27,0:05:59.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但这里是肯定不能上网的\N{\rEng}Well   there certainly ain't none here!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.05,0:06:01.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也许你们都该面对现实了\N{\rEng}Look   maybe it's time you all face reality.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.56,0:06:03.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这儿的互联网已经干涸了\N{\rEng}The internet here is dried up.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.34,0:06:04.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,会回来的\N{\rEng}It could come back.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.55,0:06:06.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  也有可能不会\N{\rEng}Yeah   and maybe it won't.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.90,0:06:08.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在这个时候  我的家人\N{\rEng}In the meantime   I got a family
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.01,0:06:10.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,马上就得用上互联网\N{\rEng}who needs internet right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.03,0:06:12.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们要向着加州前进\N{\rEng}We'll head out California way and  
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.53,0:06:14.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看看能找到什么\N{\rEng}and see what we can find.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.86,0:06:17.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  我们走\N{\rEng}Come on. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.69,0:06:20.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,听着  要是你们真的找到互联网了\N{\rEng}Look   if you do find internet  
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.27,0:06:22.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我们  好吗\N{\rEng}let us know   will you?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.08,0:06:26.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么告诉你们  你们又没有互联网\N{\rEng}How? You won't have internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.41,0:06:42.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,加州需要互联网\N{\rEng}California NEED internet
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.46,0:06:48.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  已经住满了\N{\rEng}Sorry   folks. We're full up.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.12,0:06:49.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还有别的什么地方可以住吗\N{\rEng}Know anywhere else we can stay?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.39,0:06:51.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们在去加州的路上\N{\rEng}We're heading out California way.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.49,0:06:52.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,寻找互联网\N{\rEng}Looking for some internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.83,0:06:54.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大家都一样\N{\rEng}You and everyone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.30,0:06:56.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们去住临时营地吧\N{\rEng}You'll have to stay out at the transient camp
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.68,0:06:57.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那的人也都是去加州的\N{\rEng}with all the others heading to California.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.91,0:07:00.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,沿着这条路走一英里就到了\N{\rEng}It's about a mile down the road.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.75,0:07:10.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我一路走来心酸苦楚*\N{\rEng}* I'm going down the road feeling bad *
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.46,0:07:16.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我一路走来心酸苦楚*\N{\rEng}* I'm going down the road feeling bad *
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.05,0:07:19.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我一路走来心酸苦楚*\N{\rEng}* I'm going down the road feeling bad *
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.67,0:07:24.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*天哪  我的互联网消失了*\N{\rEng}* oh   lordy my internet done up and went away *
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.84,0:07:31.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你从哪儿来  老头子\N{\rEng}Where are you from   old-timer?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.60,0:07:33.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,堪萨斯城\N{\rEng}Kansas City.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.05,0:07:37.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我在那儿开了家店  电脑配件店\N{\rEng}Had me a store there   a kind of computer supply store
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.67,0:07:40.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,互联网消失了  我的店也随之完了\N{\rEng}When the internet went   the stores went too.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.72,0:07:43.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等我们到了加州事情就会好起来的\N{\rEng}Things will be different when we get to California.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.52,0:07:46.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等我们有了互联网就能放松休息了\N{\rEng}Soon as we get us some internet we can all rest easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.61,0:07:48.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么那么肯定  硅谷\N{\rEng}Why sure. Silicon Valley.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.76,0:07:50.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们那儿的互联网乱成一团糟\N{\rEng}They got a whole mess of Internet up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.14,0:07:54.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,据说人在里面会被缠住\N{\rEng}Say a man can practically roll around in it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.05,0:07:55.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等我能上网了\N{\rEng}When I get to that Internet
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.27,0:07:58.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我要把能看见的内容都点一遍\N{\rEng}I'm gonna click on just about everything in sight.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.28,0:08:01.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕是弹出广告\N{\rEng}Might even click on a pop-up ad just for the heck of it
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.37,0:08:03.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我要坐在网络前\N{\rEng}Oh   I'm gonna sit down at that internet
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.57,0:08:05.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,狂发电子邮件\N{\rEng}and just start e-mailing.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.60,0:08:10.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,狂发电子邮件直到手骨头酸痛了\N{\rEng}Just keep on e-mailing 'til my fingers are sore to the bone
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.29,0:08:12.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那真不错\N{\rEng}Sure will be nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.66,0:08:15.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们全都是去硅谷的吗\N{\rEng}You folks all heading to Silicon Valley?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.51,0:08:17.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我们得上网\N{\rEng}That's right. We need to get online.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.34,0:08:20.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上网  他说\N{\rEng}Get online   he says.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.22,0:08:21.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这有什么好笑的\N{\rEng}What's so funny about that?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.56,0:08:22.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,想想看吧\N{\rEng}Think about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.76,0:08:25.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有多少人来加州了\N{\rEng}How many folks heading out to California?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.24,0:08:27.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一百万  更多\N{\rEng}A million? More?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.24,0:08:31.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得他们那儿能有多少互联网呢\N{\rEng}How much internet you think they got out there?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.10,0:08:32.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是有一点的  没错\N{\rEng}Might be some internet   sure  
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.84,0:08:35.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但一旦每个人都开始用\N{\rEng}but with everyone trying to use it at once  
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.45,0:08:37.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就会变得很慢很慢\N{\rEng}it's gonna go real slow like.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.74,0:08:40.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  因为我见过\N{\rEng}I knows because I seen it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.20,0:08:43.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我的两个孩子  他们打开一个网页\N{\rEng}My two children   they tried to load a webpage.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.61,0:08:45.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等了三天多\N{\rEng}Took them over three days.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.73,0:08:47.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们坐在那儿等啊等\N{\rEng}They sat there waiting  
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.89,0:08:52.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,进度条才打开一半  他们就死了\N{\rEng}by the time the loading bar was only half full they was dead
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.45,0:08:54.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,活活饿死的\N{\rEng}Starved on the internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.59,0:08:58.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们的肚子都像猪膀胱一样突出来了\N{\rEng}With their bellies stuck out like a pig bladder.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.76,0:09:05.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  斯坦  睡觉去吧\N{\rEng}Come on   Stan. Let's get us some rest.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.15,0:09:15.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,埃米尔  我太想你了\N{\rEng}Amir   I miss you so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.99,0:09:20.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别哭了  谢莉\N{\rEng}Don't cry   Shelley.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.70,0:09:23.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等我们到加州  你就能上网了\N{\rEng}You'll be able to get online when we get to California
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.80,0:09:39.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大家都醒醒  我们到了\N{\rEng}Everyone   wake up   we're here!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.15,0:09:42.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,硅谷  加州\N{\rEng}Silicon Valley   California!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.45,0:09:54.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,姓名\N{\rEng}Name.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.53,0:09:56.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这儿能上网吗\N{\rEng}Do they have internet here?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.13,0:09:57.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,姓名\N{\rEng}Name.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.33,0:09:58.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,马什\N{\rEng}Marsh.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.32,0:09:59.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,服务提供商\N{\rEng}Service provider.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.63,0:10:00.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,零网络公司\N{\rEng}Net Zero.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.48,0:10:02.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  进去排队\N{\rEng}All right. Stay in line once you're inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.52,0:10:05.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,红十字会志愿者会带你们去营地\N{\rEng}Red Cross volunteers will direct you to your campsite
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.19,0:10:06.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这儿能上网吗\N{\rEng}So   is there internet here?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.99,0:10:10.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,排队去营地\N{\rEng}Stay in line and get to your campsite.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.01,0:10:22.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我们在找互联网\N{\rEng}Excuse me. We're looking for some internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.21,0:10:23.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  这儿有\N{\rEng}Yeah   they got it here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.62,0:10:24.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\rEng}All right!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.54,0:10:26.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但没有那么多可分配的\N{\rEng}Bud there ain't enough to go around.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.41,0:10:28.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,只有一点点\N{\rEng}All they got is a little internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.54,0:10:30.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大概一格信号那么多\N{\rEng}Barely a bar a signal.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.65,0:10:33.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所以他们只能严格定量配给\N{\rEng}So they have to ration it out carefully.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.10,0:10:34.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,到那儿签名\N{\rEng}You sign up over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.67,0:10:36.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等他们叫到你  你就可以用一会儿\N{\rEng}And use your time when they call your name.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.71,0:10:39.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,每个家庭一天有40秒的时间来上网\N{\rEng}Each family gets 40 seconds of internet per day.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.58,0:10:41.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,40秒\N{\rEng}40 seconds?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.06,0:10:43.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,连查维基百科都不够\N{\rEng}That ain't even long enough to check wikipedia!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.59,0:10:45.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没办法  只能这样了\N{\rEng}Well   it's all we got so we got to make do.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.94,0:10:48.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我在亚马逊订了几本书\N{\rEng}Look   honey. I ordered us some books on amazon!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.52,0:10:49.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  时间到了\N{\rEng}All right. Time's up.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.59,0:10:52.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  我还没有输入运单信息呢\N{\rEng}No   wait! I haven't entered the shipping information.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.75,0:10:54.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  不\N{\rEng}No! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.74,0:10:57.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,下一个  约翰·格雷\N{\rEng}Next! Grady   John H.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.29,0:11:00.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那样子可怎么上网看毛片呢\N{\rEng}Aw   how am I supposed to see internet porn that way?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.70,0:11:02.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你刚刚说什么\N{\rEng}What did you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.11,0:11:03.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们继续排吧  莎朗\N{\rEng}Uh   you go on ahead   Sharon  
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.73,0:11:05.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,跟孩子们分着用一下网络\N{\rEng}divide some internet amongst the children.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.39,0:11:08.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我去找个管事的人谈谈\N{\rEng}I got to go talk to somebody.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.43,0:11:14.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们就知道这些\N{\rEng}And that's about all we know.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.66,0:11:17.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在加州和佛罗里达某些地方\N{\rEng}There might be some internet still in California  
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.10,0:11:18.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,可能会有一点儿互联网\N{\rEng}and parts of Florida.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.81,0:11:22.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是  在这里还是一点儿也没有\N{\rEng}Though   we certainly still don't have any here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.03,0:11:24.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,传真  有传真\N{\rEng}A fax! A fax is coming through!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.76,0:11:28.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-我们收到传真了  -耶  传真\N{\rEng}- We got a fax! - Yeah   a fax!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.50,0:11:32.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上面说  政府派了\N{\rEng}It says the government has sent
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.57,0:11:34.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,最牛的人去互联网了\N{\rEng}their best people to the internet
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.58,0:11:37.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,以便修好它\N{\rEng}in order to repair it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.58,0:11:41.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们得特派一个记者到现场去\N{\rEng}We got to get a reporter out to the internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.62,0:11:45.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,互联网在哪儿\N{\rEng}Where is the internet?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.82,0:11:58.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,先生们  至今上不了网\N{\rEng}Gentlemen   President is very angry that
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.12,0:12:00.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,总统很生气\N{\rEng}his internet still isn't working.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.14,0:12:01.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们想尽办法了  先生\N{\rEng}We've tried everything   sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.75,0:12:03.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,互联网慢得像蜗牛\N{\rEng}But the internet has slowed to a trickle
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.75,0:12:05.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们没办法让它正常运转\N{\rEng}and we can't get it working correctly.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.17,0:12:06.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,带我下去\N{\rEng}Take me down below.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.55,0:12:10.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想亲自见见互联网\N{\rEng}I want to see the internet for myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.77,0:12:17.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,将军  这就是互联网\N{\rEng}Here it is   general. The internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.98,0:12:25.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,它出了什么问题\N{\rEng}So what's wrong with it?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.66,0:12:28.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看见中间那个一闪一闪的黄灯了吗\N{\rEng}See that flashing orange light in the mid?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.57,0:12:31.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,应该是一直亮着的绿灯\N{\rEng}It's supposed to be solid green.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.82,0:12:36.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天哪\N{\rEng}My god.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.89,0:12:42.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,跳舞的kitty猫  这是什么啊\N{\rEng}Thedancingkitty.Com. I wonder what that is?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.77,0:12:45.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,点击跳舞的kitty猫  就可能获得奖品\N{\rEng}Click on the dancing kitty and you could win a prize.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.93,0:12:46.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  时间到了\N{\rEng}All right   time's up.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.96,0:12:50.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  我刚点了kitty猫  还没得奖呢\N{\rEng}No wait. I just clicked on the kitty. I got it!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.21,0:12:52.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还没到时间呢  不\N{\rEng}No! It wasn't long enough! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.99,0:12:55.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,下一个  彼得·内尔森\N{\rEng}Next. Nelson   Peter T.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.58,0:12:56.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思\N{\rEng}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.61,0:12:59.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我需要  一点私人互联网时间\N{\rEng}I need to uh   have some private internet time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.76,0:13:01.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们也正竭尽所能\N{\rEng}Look   we're just trying to get by here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.38,0:13:04.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但不能对你一人特殊\N{\rEng}Everyone's got to take what they can get.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.94,0:13:08.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我已经两个多星期没有打飞机了\N{\rEng}I haven't jacked off in over two weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.95,0:13:10.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那你打啊\N{\rEng}So jack off.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.31,0:13:11.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你没明白\N{\rEng}You don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.25,0:13:14.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我要上网打飞机\N{\rEng}I need the internet to jack off.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.01,0:13:16.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我习惯了点一下鼠标\N{\rEng}I got used to being able to see anything
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.57,0:13:18.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就能看见任何东西  你懂吗\N{\rEng}at the click of a button you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.63,0:13:20.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你一旦对着日本女优\N{\rEng}Once you jack off to Japanese girls
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.04,0:13:21.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,互相往嘴里呕吐打过飞机\N{\rEng}puking in each other's mouth  
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.35,0:13:23.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你就不可能再回到花花公子了\N{\rEng}you can't exactly go back to "playboy."
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.56,0:13:24.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那你想要怎样\N{\rEng}What do you want us to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.70,0:13:26.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,把电脑搬进房间十分钟\N{\rEng}Pick up the whole computer and put it inside
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.20,0:13:27.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就为了你一个人?\N{\rEng}for ten minutes just for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.93,0:13:30.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-三分钟就够了  －给我滚\N{\rEng}- Three minutes would be plenty. - Get lost.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.43,0:13:36.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  拿好你们的号码牌\N{\rEng}All right. Each of you take a ticket.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.08,0:13:38.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等他们叫你们的名字  就可以去上网了\N{\rEng}When they call your name   you can use the internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.48,0:13:40.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你多少号  臭大粪\N{\rEng}What number are you   turd?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.29,0:13:41.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,851号\N{\rEng}Eight fifty-one
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.96,0:13:43.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在你是923号了\N{\rEng}You're 923 now.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.80,0:13:45.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈\N{\rEng}Hey   mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.48,0:13:47.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谢莉  把号码牌还给你弟弟\N{\rEng}Shelley   give your brother his ticket back.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.58,0:13:49.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们难道都无视我的痛苦吗\N{\rEng}Can't you all see I'm in pain?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.63,0:13:51.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没人理解我纯洁的爱情\N{\rEng}Nobody understands pure love.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.97,0:13:55.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我跟埃米尔比和你们几个傻逼都要亲近\N{\rEng}Amir and I are closer than anybody in this stupid family
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.81,0:14:04.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,过来\N{\rEng}Over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.80,0:14:07.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是在找网络毛片看\N{\rEng}You. Happen to be looking for internet porn?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.52,0:14:09.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  你怎么知道的\N{\rEng}Yeah. How'd you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.21,0:14:12.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很多人都为了那个原因来这儿\N{\rEng}Lots of us fellas came here for that reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.04,0:14:13.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当我们看惯了互联网上\N{\rEng}We all got used to seeing lots of
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.90,0:14:15.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,非常变态的东西后\N{\rEng}really perverted stuff on the internet  
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.91,0:14:18.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在怎么可能回去看花花公子呢\N{\rEng}so now we can't go back to "playboy."
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.14,0:14:19.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,说的没错\N{\rEng}I know! Right?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.68,0:14:22.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,总之  我们有个模拟程序\N{\rEng}Anyway   we got us a simulator.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.12,0:14:26.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,说出你想看到的东西  然后说点击\N{\rEng}You just call out what you want to see and then say click
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.90,0:14:28.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,互联网毛片模拟程序\N{\rEng}Internet porn stimulator.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.69,0:14:30.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,去试试吧\N{\rEng}Give it a try.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.67,0:14:36.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,点一下鼠标就会出现你想看的任何东西\N{\rEng}Anything you wanted to see with the click of a button
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.15,0:14:40.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,日本女优交换体液  点击\N{\rEng}Uh   Japanese girls exchanging bodily fluids. Click.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.36,0:14:48.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,太操蛋了  对着这个怎么打飞机\N{\rEng}Oh   this sucks! I can't jack off to this!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.90,0:14:52.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼\N{\rEng}Dammit.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.20,0:14:56.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那么  群交  点击\N{\rEng}Uh   let's see. Gang bang. Click.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.98,0:15:01.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,人妖  试试人妖  点击\N{\rEng}She-males. Let's try she-males. Click.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.78,0:15:06.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,兽交  点击\N{\rEng}Bestialty. Click on that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.12,0:15:11.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴西放屁仪式毛片  点击\N{\rEng}Brazilian fart fetish porn? Click. Click.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.24,0:15:18.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  这不行\N{\rEng}Nope. This isn't gonna work.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.33,0:15:21.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,完全没感觉\N{\rEng}It's just not the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.52,0:15:22.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\rEng}Well   sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.80,0:15:25.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们要从你信用卡上划走49美元\N{\rEng}That'll be $49 on your credit card.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.71,0:15:28.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这倒跟互联网很像嘛\N{\rEng}Well   at least that part's like the internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.37,0:15:30.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有一位记者已经到达现场了\N{\rEng}We now have a reporter on the scene.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.73,0:15:32.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来看现场报道\N{\rEng}Let's go live!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.70,0:15:34.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,汤姆  我在互联网现场\N{\rEng}Tom   I am at the internet
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.84,0:15:36.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,政府官员正在尽最大的努力\N{\rEng}government officials are doing their best
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.89,0:15:39.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,试图让互联网重新运转\N{\rEng}to get it running again.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.98,0:15:41.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  互联网\N{\rEng}All right   internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.50,0:15:44.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你到底想要我们怎样\N{\rEng}What do you want from us?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.74,0:15:51.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们让你生气了的话  请告诉我们\N{\rEng}If we've angered you somehow   let us know.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.34,0:15:54.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,用数字方式与之对话\N{\rEng}Try to communicate with it digitally again.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.44,0:16:21.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我受够了  开枪警告\N{\rEng}I've had it with this thing. Fire a warning shot at it
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.37,0:16:29.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等一下\N{\rEng}Hey   wait a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.37,0:16:32.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是否有可能...\N{\rEng}Is it possible that --
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.51,0:16:34.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  凯尔\N{\rEng}What is it   Kyle?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.82,0:16:39.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我想我知道问题出在哪里了\N{\rEng}I think I know what's wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.01,0:16:48.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这样太费时间了\N{\rEng}This is taking too long.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.82,0:16:51.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候才轮得上我啊\N{\rEng}When do I get to use the internet?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.54,0:16:53.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,马上就轮到我们了\N{\rEng}It's got to be our turn soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.06,0:16:54.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  市民们  该睡觉了\N{\rEng}All right   folks. It's bedtime.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.44,0:16:56.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,今天的网络到此为止\N{\rEng}No more internet for today
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.08,0:17:00.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,再来一小会儿啊\N{\rEng}Just a little longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.51,0:17:02.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  我们要把电脑锁起来了\N{\rEng}No   no. We're locking it away'til tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.42,0:17:04.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大家都回去睡吧\N{\rEng}Everyone get to bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.29,0:17:36.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,终于  我又能上网了  太好了\N{\rEng}Finally! I'm online again! Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.72,0:17:42.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,日本女优互相往嘴里呕吐\N{\rEng}Japanese girls puke in each other's mouths.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.33,0:17:49.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\rEng}Oh   nice!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.16,0:17:58.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,再来看看兽交\N{\rEng}Now let's see some bestialty.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.23,0:18:08.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,爽\N{\rEng}Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.53,0:18:13.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴西放屁仪式毛片\N{\rEng}Let's get some brazilian fart porn in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.11,0:18:19.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了\N{\rEng}That's got it!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.48,0:18:24.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么声音\N{\rEng}What is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.41,0:18:27.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,貌似有人在被老虎攻击\N{\rEng}Sounds like somebody's being attacked by a tiger.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.30,0:18:32.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,把钥匙拿出来  快进去\N{\rEng}Get the keys. We got to get in there!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.01,0:18:42.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我靠\N{\rEng}What the --
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.62,0:18:44.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-老爸?  -兰迪\N{\rEng}- Dad? - Randy!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.70,0:18:48.39,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,噢  刚刚有只  鬼\N{\rEng}Oh   uh   there was a   a ghost!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.40,0:18:50.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是鬼的黏液\N{\rEng}This is ectoplasm!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.57,0:18:51.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们看见鬼了吗\N{\rEng}Did you see the ghost?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.90,0:18:54.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,它穿过房间  和我擦身而过\N{\rEng}It ran through here and slimed me!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.30,0:18:55.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你这个狗日的\N{\rEng}You son of a bitch!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.81,0:18:59.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不是我干的  是鬼干的\N{\rEng}No   it wasn't me. It was the spooky ghost!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.57,0:19:02.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们最后的机会\N{\rEng}This is our last chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.60,0:19:03.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,政府束手无策\N{\rEng}With nowhere else to turn
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.95,0:19:07.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,只能允许一个勇敢的9岁男孩\N{\rEng}the government is going to allow one brave 9-year-old boy
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.26,0:19:11.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来用他自己的方法使互联网恢复运作\N{\rEng}to attempt his method to get the internet running again
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.20,0:19:12.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,成败在此一举\N{\rEng}It all comes down to this.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.92,0:19:16.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这个犹太小男孩能搞定互联网吗\N{\rEng}Can the little Jewish boy reason with the internet
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.42,0:19:18.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,抑或互联网将永久消失呢\N{\rEng}or will it be gone forever?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.13,0:19:20.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,准备好了\N{\rEng}All clear for procedure.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.33,0:19:23.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好  去吧\N{\rEng}All right. Let's do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.15,0:19:45.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看啊  一闪一闪的黄灯\N{\rEng}Look! The flashing yellow light
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.95,0:19:47.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在一直是绿灯了\N{\rEng}is steady green now!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.56,0:19:48.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他成功了\N{\rEng}He did it!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.87,0:19:50.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-我能上网了  -我也是\N{\rEng}- I've got internet! - Me too!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.78,0:19:53.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所有区域的互联网都通畅了\N{\rEng}Internet activity in all sectors   sir!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.78,0:20:00.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-我能上网了  -我也是\N{\rEng}- I've got internet. - Me too.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.39,0:20:01.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,互联网回来了\N{\rEng}It's back!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.78,0:20:06.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,回来了?  回来了\N{\rEng}It's back? It's back!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.96,0:20:08.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,可以上网了\N{\rEng}It's working!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.13,0:20:11.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我现在可以和我亲爱的埃米尔聊天了\N{\rEng}I can I-chat with my darling Amir now!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.88,0:20:15.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谢莉  谢莉·马什\N{\rEng}Shelley? Shelley Marsh?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.51,0:20:16.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.19,0:20:18.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我是埃米尔啊\N{\rEng}It's me. Amir.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.46,0:20:24.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们家也来了哈\N{\rEng}Your family came here too  
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.43,0:20:27.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\rEng}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.30,0:20:32.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,呃  我还是回家后给你发邮件吧\N{\rEng}So  I guess I'll e-mail you as soon as we get back home
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.57,0:20:33.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  好  不错\N{\rEng}Yeah   okay   sounds good.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.99,0:20:36.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好  再会\N{\rEng}Okay   c'ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.86,0:20:40.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们和好如初  我们和好如初\N{\rEng}We're back together! We're back together!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.17,0:20:49.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,从这次磨难中我们学到了什么呢\N{\rEng}And so what have we learned through this ordeal?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.36,0:20:52.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,互联网消失了  又回来了\N{\rEng}The internet went away   it came back.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.82,0:20:55.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但是还能持续多久  我们都不知道\N{\rEng}But for how long we do not know.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.92,0:20:59.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能再理所当然地使用网络了\N{\rEng}We cannot take the internet for granted any longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.37,0:21:02.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,整个国家必须停止超负荷使用网络\N{\rEng}We as a country must stop over logging-on.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.02,0:21:06.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,应该只在需要的时候再用\N{\rEng}We must use the internet only when we need it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.58,0:21:08.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是很简单地认为\N{\rEng}It's easy for us to think we can just
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.31,0:21:10.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以随意地使用网络\N{\rEng}use up all the internet we want  
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.73,0:21:14.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但如果我们不对互联网给于\N{\rEng}but if we don't treat the internet with the respect
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.30,0:21:18.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,它应得的敬意\N{\rEng}that it deserves  
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.53,0:21:21.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,它终有一天会彻底消失\N{\rEng}it could one day be gone forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.46,0:21:23.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们得学着和互联网一起生活\N{\rEng}And so let us learn to live with the internet  
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.56,0:21:25.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,而不是为了它而活\N{\rEng}not for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.08,0:21:26.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要再漫无目的地浏览网页\N{\rEng}No more browsing for no apparent reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.91,0:21:28.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要再一边看电视\N{\rEng}No more mindlessly surfing on our laptops
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.70,0:21:30.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一边心不在焉地用笔记本上网\N{\rEng}while watching television.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.92,0:21:33.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,最后  我们必须学会\N{\rEng}And finally   we must learn to
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.27,0:21:37.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一天只看2次互联网毛片\N{\rEng}only the internet for porn twice a day.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.58,0:21:39.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,最多\N{\rEng}Max.
