[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2008-10-30 08:43:29
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayDepth: 0
PlayResX: 1916
PlayResY: 1076
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 2
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H19000000,&H000E0300,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,2,2,134,120,68,1
Style: eng,Microsoft YaHei,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,26,1
Style: Top,微软雅黑,10,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Git,Comic Sans MS,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Chn,微软雅黑,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Eng,Comic Sans MS,60,&H002AF7FF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.20,0:00:11.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm going down to south park\N gonna have myself a time 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.05,0:00:15.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Friendly faces everywhere\N humble folks without temptation 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.33,0:00:18.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Going down to south park\N gonna leave my woes behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.72,0:00:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ample parking day or night\N people shouting howdy neighbor
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.96,0:00:24.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heading on out to south park\N gonna see if I can't unwind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.54,0:00:28.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I like girls with big vaginas\N I like girls with big fat titties
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.61,0:00:31.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.50,0:21:45.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译制作\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}YYeTs人人影视字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.60,0:21:46.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}校译\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}荨香 sunflo
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.60,0:21:47.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1c&HFDC282&}后期\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}csbeyond
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.60,0:00:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0150,,{\1c&HFDC282&}南方公园  第12季第7集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.60,0:00:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0100,,超级欢乐时光\N{\rEng}Super Fun Time
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.39,0:00:39.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,同学们  都过来\N{\rEng}Kids   everyone together.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.24,0:00:41.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到先祖谷\N{\rEng}Welcome to Pioneer Village.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.51,0:00:44.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这里是对早期科罗拉多的重现\N{\rEng}This is a re-creation of early Colorado days.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.52,0:00:47.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来认识一下先祖保罗\N{\rEng}I want you all to meet Pioneer Paul.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.01,0:00:49.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,同学们好  欢迎到此一游\N{\rEng}Hi   kids   and welcome to my village.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.33,0:00:53.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾与父母于1864年到此定居\N{\rEng}I settled here in 1864 with my maw and paw.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.60,0:00:55.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,诚然  吾未曾见过\N{\rEng}Sure thing   I ain't never seen
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.77,0:00:58.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,汝等那样奇怪的衣着\N{\rEng}strange clothes like you all are wearing.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.40,0:01:00.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,汝等刚刚乘的那辆\N{\rEng}And what's that fancy yellow
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.00,0:01:03.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,华丽黄色车辆又为何物\N{\rEng}horse carriage you got out there?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.66,0:01:04.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真装逼\N{\rEng}This is gonna suck.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.75,0:01:07.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,汝等一切就绪  尽可入内参观\N{\rEng}When y'all are ready   just head up to the village.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.49,0:01:10.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾镇百姓将解开汝等所有的疑问\N{\rEng}All the townsfolk are there to answer your questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.61,0:01:15.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到1864年  出发咯\N{\rEng}And welcome to 1864. Sit 'em up!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.28,0:01:16.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  先祖保罗\N{\rEng}Thank you   Pioneer Paul.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.77,0:01:18.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,同学们  这个地方很大\N{\rEng}All right   kids   this is a big place
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.53,0:01:22.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所以我要你们每人找个搭档  拉着手\N{\rEng}So I want everyone to pick a partner to hold hands with.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.61,0:01:24.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们来搭档吧  肯尼\N{\rEng}Let's be partners   Kenny.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.78,0:01:26.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不行  我已经和克雷格搭挡了\N{\rEng}No   I'm partners with Craig.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.54,0:01:28.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\rEng}Oh   okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.28,0:01:29.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,斯坦  我们来搭档吧\N{\rEng}Stan   let's be partners   dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.88,0:01:31.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不行  我已经和温蒂搭档了\N{\rEng}No   I'm with Wendy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.44,0:01:34.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你居然想跟一个女孩牵手  同性恋\N{\rEng}You wanna hold hands with a girl? Gaywad.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.29,0:01:38.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们来搭档吧  凯尔\N{\rEng}All right   let's be partners   Kyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.42,0:01:39.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我恨你  记得吗\N{\rEng}I hate you   remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.99,0:01:41.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,想跟我搭档吗  吉米\N{\rEng}You wanna be partners   Jimmy?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.48,0:01:43.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上帝  我又怎么招你了\N{\rEng}Jesus   what have I ever done to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.58,0:01:45.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格  托肯\N{\rEng}Craig? Token?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.07,0:01:47.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谁  还有谁要搭档的\N{\rEng}Who   who else needs a partner?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.69,0:01:57.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还有谁要搭档的\N{\rEng}Who else needs a partner?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.05,0:01:58.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  你和巴特斯搭档吧\N{\rEng}Eric   partner with Butters.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.49,0:02:00.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\rEng}God dammit!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.07,0:02:01.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,拉着他的手  埃里克\N{\rEng}Hold butters' hand   Eric.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.76,0:02:03.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这完全没有必要\N{\rEng}That isn't necessary.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.09,0:02:05.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  等你们俩都回到校车上\N{\rEng}Butters   you are not to let go of Eric's hand
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.03,0:02:07.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,才可以放开埃里克的手\N{\rEng}Until you are both back on that bus.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.06,0:02:08.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,明白吗\N{\rEng}Do you understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.29,0:02:09.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,明白\N{\rEng}I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.58,0:02:12.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,进去吧\N{\rEng}All right   let's head in.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.09,0:02:13.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,可以放手了  巴特斯\N{\rEng}You can let go now   Butters.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.74,0:02:14.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\rEng}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.55,0:02:15.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  巴特斯\N{\rEng}Butters   come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.70,0:02:17.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\rEng}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.47,0:02:18.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  同学们  去拜访那些\N{\rEng}All right   kids. Go ahead and visit
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.85,0:02:21.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有趣的村民吧  学点东西\N{\rEng}the charming villagers and learn stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.16,0:02:24.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,照看好你们的搭档\N{\rEng}Keep track of your partner.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.88,0:02:27.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,各位贵安  我是镇铁匠\N{\rEng}Why   howdy   partners. I'm the town blacksmith.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.91,0:02:30.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,各位是移居到此呢  还是\N{\rEng}Are you folks settlers or are you just
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.04,0:02:32.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,云游路过呢\N{\rEng}trappers passing through?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.35,0:02:34.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们能别玩角色扮演了吗\N{\rEng}look   can we just drop the role-playing thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.73,0:02:36.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是想玩  可我女朋友在这儿\N{\rEng}I would play along   but my girlfriend's here and
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.37,0:02:38.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想在她面前表现得像个傻逼\N{\rEng}I don't wanna look like a dork in front of her.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.38,0:02:39.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  斯坦\N{\rEng}Thanks   Stan.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.42,0:02:41.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,此些人等实乃奇怪也  史密夫\N{\rEng}Those folk sure are strange   Smithy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.73,0:02:43.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾等在此时从未见过\N{\rEng}We ain't never seen them kind of
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.34,0:02:46.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那样华丽的帽子  是吧\N{\rEng}fancy hats in our time   have we?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.95,0:02:49.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那个人还戴着电子表呢\N{\rEng}That guy's wearing a digital watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.75,0:02:51.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天哪\N{\rEng}Oh   jeez.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.83,0:02:54.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-要死啊你  查德  －对不起\N{\rEng}- Dammit   Chad. - I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.65,0:02:58.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,各位贵安  我是兵器铺老板\N{\rEng}Howdy   partners. I'm the town gunsmith.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.17,0:03:00.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在吾等时代  此乃十分之暴力\N{\rEng}You see   in our time   it's pretty violent.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.83,0:03:02.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看见墙上的洞了吗\N{\rEng}See them holes in the walls?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.79,0:03:04.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,印地安人来时  吾等便将来福枪\N{\rEng}That's so we can put a rifle through
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.69,0:03:06.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,从洞中伸出  保卫家园\N{\rEng}to protect us from Indians.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.71,0:03:08.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我要打印地安人\N{\rEng}I wanna shoot an Indian!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.30,0:03:09.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,汝等也许该去\N{\rEng}Now some of you might want to meet
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.63,0:03:11.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,蜡烛坊看看阿比吉尔\N{\rEng}Abigail at the candle making house.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.55,0:03:14.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,亦或去杂货铺逛逛\N{\rEng}Or you can head over the general store.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.20,0:03:18.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看见印地安人了吗\N{\rEng}You see any Indians?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.58,0:03:20.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没有  只是街道还有\N{\rEng}Nah   it's just the city and a --
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.56,0:03:24.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天哪额滴神啊\N{\rEng}oh   my Jesus Christ monkey balls.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.42,0:03:27.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,超级欢乐时光\N{\rEng}Super fun time.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.93,0:03:29.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,哥们儿  快看\N{\rEng}Dude   check it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.91,0:03:31.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,离咱们就两个街区远\N{\rEng}We're only two blocks from a super fun time!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.82,0:03:33.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有电动  飞车  什么都有\N{\rEng}They got video games and rides and everything!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.74,0:03:35.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很酷  走吧  埃里克\N{\rEng}Oh   that's cool. Come on   Eric  
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.16,0:03:36.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们得赶上大部队\N{\rEng}we need to catch up with everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.57,0:03:37.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,哥们儿  去他妈的先祖谷\N{\rEng}Dude   screw this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.67,0:03:38.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们去超级欢乐时光吧\N{\rEng}We gotta go to super fun time!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.98,0:03:40.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不行  我才不要溜走\N{\rEng}Oh   no. I'm not sneaking out.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.93,0:03:42.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,会惹祸上身的\N{\rEng}I'll get in trouble.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.14,0:03:43.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,随便你  放开我的手\N{\rEng}Fine. Then let go of my hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.25,0:03:45.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老师说上车之前  不能放手\N{\rEng}Teacher said I can't let go until we're back on the bus.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.85,0:03:47.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,两条路任你选  巴特斯\N{\rEng}Well   which is it gonna be   Butters?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.09,0:03:48.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,要么跟我一起溜出去\N{\rEng}Are you gonna ditch out with me or
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.05,0:03:50.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,要么违反老师的傻逼规定\N{\rEng}are you gonna disobey the teacher's stupid rule?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.09,0:03:51.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不会放手的\N{\rEng}I'm not letting go.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.63,0:03:52.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,随便  那你就得跟我走\N{\rEng}Fine. Then you're coming with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.96,0:03:53.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不行  埃里克\N{\rEng}No   Eric!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.91,0:03:55.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  放手  去死\N{\rEng}Butters   let go   god dammit!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.01,0:03:59.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不行  老师  老师\N{\rEng}No! Teacher! Teacher!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.86,0:04:02.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,此处便是杂货铺\N{\rEng}This here is our general store.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.56,0:04:05.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾可在此购入所需之物\N{\rEng}It's where I buy all my supplies and such.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.46,0:04:09.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,各位贵安  吾乃杂货铺老板\N{\rEng}Howdy   partners. I own this here general store.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.47,0:04:11.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看  斯坦  这还有那时候的牛肉干\N{\rEng}Look   Stan   they had beef jerky back then.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.83,0:04:13.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,汝言"那时候"为何意\N{\rEng}What do you mean back then?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.03,0:04:17.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,勿忘  如今便是1864年\N{\rEng}Don't forget it's 1864!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.41,0:04:19.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  可惜现在真的不是\N{\rEng}Right. Except for it really isn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.18,0:04:22.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当然是啊  环顾四周吧\N{\rEng}Sure it is. Just look around you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.71,0:04:26.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,什么声音  像是警笛\N{\rEng}What's that? It sounds like police sirens.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.92,0:04:28.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,何为警笛\N{\rEng}What's a siren?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.49,0:04:33.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾等在1864年从未听闻警笛为何物\N{\rEng}We ain't never heard of no siren in 1864.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.69,0:04:39.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,甩掉了  甩掉了\N{\rEng}We lost 'em! We lost 'em!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.93,0:04:43.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,傻逼警察猪一样  关门\N{\rEng}Damn pig cops. Close that gate!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.08,0:04:47.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么回事  -不知道啊\N{\rEng}- What's going on? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.12,0:04:49.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所有人趴到地上  马上\N{\rEng}Everyone down on the ground. Now!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.67,0:04:52.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,哇塞  吾乃警长"警犬麦克"\N{\rEng}Whoa now! I'm sheriff McLawdog.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.82,0:04:56.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾1850年便移居至此...\N{\rEng}I settled here back in 1850 --
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.80,0:04:59.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天哪\N{\rEng}Jesus christ!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.01,0:05:01.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快报警  你们的电话呢\N{\rEng}We got to call the police! Where's your phone?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.39,0:05:03.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,电话  何为电话\N{\rEng}A phone? Why   what's a phone?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.87,0:05:06.11,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾等从未听说此物\N{\rEng}We ain't never heard of such a thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.13,0:05:08.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -拜托  这不是开玩笑\N{\rEng}-What? -Come on   this is serious!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.28,0:05:12.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老板  汝曾听闻过电话否\N{\rEng}Store hand   you ever heard of this fancy smancy phone?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.24,0:05:16.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,从未  此时吾等尚未有电话\N{\rEng}Uh   no. We ain't got a phone in our time.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.27,0:05:18.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,哥们儿  他们刚刚爆了那家伙的头\N{\rEng}Dude   they just shot a guy in the face.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.58,0:05:19.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们得报警\N{\rEng}We got to call the cops.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.92,0:05:21.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,若汝意指执法者\N{\rEng}If you mean the law  
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.22,0:05:24.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,"警犬麦克"是本地唯一的警长\N{\rEng}only law round here is town sheriff   Mclawdog.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.53,0:05:26.83,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,1864年旧西部正值\N{\rEng}You see 1864 is a time of
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.83,0:05:28.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,增长发展期\N{\rEng}growth and development in the old west
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.64,0:05:31.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在不是说那个的时候\N{\rEng}This is not the time for that!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.91,0:05:34.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟  太爽了\N{\rEng}Oh   man   this is gonna be awesome!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.75,0:05:38.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  你要是再不放手的话\N{\rEng}Butters   if you don't let go of my hand
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.03,0:05:39.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大家都会以为我们是同性恋的\N{\rEng}everyone here is going to think we're gay.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.64,0:05:42.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那是你的问题\N{\rEng}Well   that's your problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.03,0:05:45.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  我受够了\N{\rEng}All right   Butters. I've seriously had enough!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.90,0:05:50.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天哪\N{\rEng}Jesus christ.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.36,0:05:53.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-一位  -两位\N{\rEng}- One   please. - Make that two.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.75,0:05:55.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,噢  你们两个小可爱手拉手\N{\rEng}Aw   aren't you two cute holding hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.60,0:05:57.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们是不是同性恋小朋友啊\N{\rEng}Are you special little buddies?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.24,0:05:59.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不是\N{\rEng}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.64,0:06:06.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,东西真多啊\N{\rEng}Dude   this place shreds!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.11,0:06:07.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,应该先玩哪个呢\N{\rEng}What should we do first?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.14,0:06:08.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该回先祖谷去\N{\rEng}We should get back to the Pioneer Village.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.93,0:06:10.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这才是我们应该做的\N{\rEng}That's what we should do!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.24,0:06:11.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  我们会在别人\N{\rEng}Butters   we're going to be back before
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.43,0:06:13.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,发现我们不见之前回去的\N{\rEng}anybody even notices we were gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.14,0:06:15.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快走  去玩碰碰车\N{\rEng}Let's go hit the bumper cars.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.22,0:06:19.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这边  这貌似是个办公室\N{\rEng}Over here! This looks like an office.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.98,0:06:23.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这儿  这有电话\N{\rEng}Here! Here's a phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.35,0:06:25.70,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,哇  真乃奇妙装置\N{\rEng}Why   what a strange contraption.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.71,0:06:27.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么没声音\N{\rEng}I can't get a dial tone.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.76,0:06:29.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,外拨号码是什么\N{\rEng}What's the number to dial out?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.18,0:06:30.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,外拨\N{\rEng}Dial out?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.28,0:06:33.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,贵客  此语甚是奇怪\N{\rEng}Partner   them are some funny words you're using.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.17,0:06:35.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,哥们儿  你明白我们的处境吗\N{\rEng}Dude   do you understand what's going on here?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.12,0:06:35.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也许他们是对的  布莱恩\N{\rEng}Maybe they're right   Brian.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.85,0:06:38.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这次是特殊情况\N{\rEng}I mean this is a special circumstance.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.41,0:06:42.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,记住  永不出戏\N{\rEng}REMEMBER NEVER BREAK CHARACTER!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.53,0:06:47.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,此屋煞是奇怪啊\N{\rEng}Hah   I mean   this here room sure is strange.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.37,0:06:50.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾等尚未有此等华丽物件\N{\rEng}We have nothing like these fancy devices in our time!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.28,0:06:52.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}Well   I'll say.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.05,0:06:53.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,接通了  喂  警察局\N{\rEng}I got through! Hello   police?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.77,0:06:55.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,911  你有什么紧急情况\N{\rEng}911   what's your emergency?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.37,0:06:56.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有恐怖分子还是银行抢劫犯什么的\N{\rEng}There's some terrorists or bank robbers or
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.57,0:06:58.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,挟持了我们班同学做人质\N{\rEng}something that've taken our class hostage.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.49,0:06:59.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在哪儿\N{\rEng}Taken hostage where?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.77,0:07:01.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吉卜林先祖谷\N{\rEng}The old Pioneer Village off of Kipling.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.63,0:07:02.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你是说那个\N{\rEng}You mean that annoying place where
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.97,0:07:05.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,员工永不出戏的囧地儿吗\N{\rEng}employees won't break character?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.40,0:07:07.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  你还完全不了解他们的囧样\N{\rEng}Sister   you don't know the half of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.18,0:07:15.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,爽翻天  哥们儿  我是太空人\N{\rEng}Check it out   dude! I'm a spaceman!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.03,0:07:17.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,太空人  爽\N{\rEng}Spaceman   yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.38,0:07:19.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我度过一段超级欢乐时光*\N{\rEng}* I'm having a super fun time day *
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.76,0:07:21.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,打那个人  打那个人\N{\rEng}yeah! Get that guy! Shoot that guy!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.90,0:07:23.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现在到这边\N{\rEng}Yeah   now over here!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.06,0:07:26.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,接到了  好球\N{\rEng}You got it! Nice!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.69,0:07:30.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*超级欢乐时光  请别离去*\N{\rEng}* Super fun time please don't go away *
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.72,0:07:37.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看个鸟啊\N{\rEng}What are you looking at?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.82,0:07:42.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*无忧无虑的超级欢乐时光*\N{\rEng}* No more worries or cares it's super fun time *
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.59,0:07:46.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*心想事成的超级欢乐时光*\N{\rEng}* the answer to my prayers super fun time *
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.46,0:07:50.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*超级欢乐时光  你是我的一切*\N{\rEng}* super fun time you're all I need *
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.83,0:07:55.87,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我要超级欢乐时光  直到我精尽人亡*\N{\rEng}* I wanna super fun time till I freakin' bleed *
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.99,0:07:59.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*我要你无论是早晨  中午还是夜晚*\N{\rEng}* I want you morning   noon and night*
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.18,0:08:00.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*超级欢乐时光*\N{\rEng}* super fun time *
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.19,0:08:02.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,耶  碰碰车  爽\N{\rEng}Yeah   bumper cars   sweeet!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.24,0:08:05.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,*你让我的生命有意义  超级欢乐时光*\N{\rEng}* you make my life so right super fun time *
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.02,0:08:07.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,够了  埃里克  我们得回去了\N{\rEng}That's it   Eric. We have to be getting back!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.41,0:08:08.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,再玩几样吧\N{\rEng}Aw   just a few more things.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.98,0:08:10.60,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不行  现在再不走\N{\rEng}No! If we don't leave right now  
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.60,0:08:12.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们就赶不上校车了\N{\rEng}we're gonna miss the bus
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.00,0:08:14.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们就会知道我们溜走了\N{\rEng}and then they'll know we left!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.40,0:08:17.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,也有可能  巴特斯  好吧  走吧\N{\rEng}I guess you're right   Butters. All right. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.86,0:08:19.63,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,设置卫星中继器\N{\rEng}Set up the satellite relay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.64,0:08:22.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,查下有没有别的路线可以离开这儿\N{\rEng}Check for alternate routes out of the area.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.03,0:08:25.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真不幸  警察听到我们抢劫的风声\N{\rEng}Unfortunately   your police department got wind of our robbery
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.07,0:08:26.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,来逮我们了\N{\rEng}and chased after us.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.62,0:08:28.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是你们的不幸\N{\rEng}That is unfortunate for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.56,0:08:30.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,因为我本来以为可以安全撤离了\N{\rEng}Because when I think it is clear to leave  
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.49,0:08:32.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但现在  我们必须挟持几个人质\N{\rEng}we will now need to take hostages with us to
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.75,0:08:35.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,以便我们的货物安全运抵目的地\N{\rEng}ensure our goods get to their final destination.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.77,0:08:38.52,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,求求你  要人质的话  千万别挟持我\N{\rEng}Please   if you must take anyone   don't take me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.55,0:08:41.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这些小孩对你更有价值\N{\rEng}These kids are worth more to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.71,0:08:43.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们怎么找到我们的\N{\rEng}How did they find us?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.01,0:08:47.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,把脏物拿出来  藏到那栋房子里去\N{\rEng}Get the loot out of the car and stash it in that building.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.22,0:08:52.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,大家听好了\N{\rEng}All right   men   listen up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.71,0:08:54.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,貌似那些贼躲在里面\N{\rEng}Looks like our thieves tried to hide out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.79,0:08:57.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们挟持工作人员和学生作为人质\N{\rEng}They've got the employees and some school kids held hostage.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.02,0:08:59.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,塔克  迪伦  设置包围圈\N{\rEng}Tucker   Dylan   set up a perimeter.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.74,0:09:01.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所有人打起精神\N{\rEng}Everyone stay on your toes.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.03,0:09:02.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们要对付的可是职业罪犯\N{\rEng}These are professionals we're dealing with here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.98,0:09:04.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,长官  他们抢劫了什么呢\N{\rEng}What did they rob   sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.01,0:09:07.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,一家汉堡王\N{\rEng}A Burger King.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.42,0:09:09.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很好  就这些了吗\N{\rEng}All right. Good. Is that all of it?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.97,0:09:12.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  还有这些\N{\rEng}No   don't forget we got these too.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.90,0:09:14.49,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很好  大家听好了\N{\rEng}Excellent. Now listen   everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.49,0:09:15.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们会没事的\N{\rEng}We're going to be all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.80,0:09:19.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们不过是螳臂挡车罢了\N{\rEng}This is only a small hitch in our plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.01,0:09:24.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让警察局长接电话\N{\rEng}I'd like to speak with the chief of police.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.13,0:09:25.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我是谁\N{\rEng}Who is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.45,0:09:27.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我就是即将杀光\N{\rEng}This is the man who is going to kill
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.08,0:09:28.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,四年级全班学生的人\N{\rEng}an entire class of fourth graders
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.39,0:09:32.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果得不到我想要的东西的话\N{\rEng}if he doesn't get exactly what he wants.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.66,0:09:40.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,警察干嘛不进来呢\N{\rEng}Why aren't the cops coming in?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.01,0:09:41.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们一定是在谈判\N{\rEng}They must be negotiating.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.33,0:09:43.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,此些山贼看起来很奇怪\N{\rEng}Them there bandits sure look mighty strange.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.98,0:09:46.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,彼之枪大过吾等之枪械\N{\rEng}And them pistols is way bigger than what we gots.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.75,0:09:48.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你能闭嘴吗\N{\rEng}Will you shut up?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.34,0:09:49.51,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,慢着  你们有枪啊\N{\rEng}Wait   you have guns here?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.53,0:09:52.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  警长差官内有众多来福枪\N{\rEng}Sure. Sheriff got lots of rifles in his office.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.39,0:09:54.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那你们去把枪拿过来吧\N{\rEng}Why don't you go get them and bring them back here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.60,0:09:56.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好  走吧  老板\N{\rEng}All righty. Come on   store hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.49,0:09:58.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,遵命\N{\rEng}Yepper!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.45,0:10:01.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  我迫不及待想看看凯尔的表情\N{\rEng}Oh   man   I can't wait to see the look on Kyle's face
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.37,0:10:02.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,当他知道他在雷人的先祖谷时\N{\rEng}when we tell him we had super fun time while
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.79,0:10:05.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们却度过了一段超级欢乐时光\N{\rEng}he was at the dumb   stupid Pioneer Village.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.30,0:10:06.89,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能告诉任何人\N{\rEng}We're not telling anybody!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.90,0:10:08.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不想惹祸上身\N{\rEng}I don't want to get in trouble.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.24,0:10:10.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,况且我也根本没有玩\N{\rEng}And I didn't have a super fun time anyways.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.02,0:10:12.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  脑子要放灵光啊\N{\rEng}Butters   you got to learn to chill.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.52,0:10:14.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,生命匆匆而逝\N{\rEng}Life goes by pretty fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.06,0:10:15.73,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,若你不曾停留  审视你周遭的一切\N{\rEng}If you don't stop and look around once in a while  
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.74,0:10:18.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,做爱做的事  你就会失去生命的意义\N{\rEng}and do whatever you want all the time   you could miss it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.19,0:10:20.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  呃  你讲的有点道理\N{\rEng}Yeah   well   I guess that's kinda true.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.45,0:10:25.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,操  他们叫警察来找我们了\N{\rEng}Crap   they called the cops on us.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.11,0:10:27.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧  他们报警了\N{\rEng}What? They called the caps?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.21,0:10:28.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们一定发现我们不见了  见鬼\N{\rEng}They must have realized we left. Damn!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.99,0:10:31.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  警察在找我们吗\N{\rEng}Oh   my god   the police are looking for us?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.19,0:10:33.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-巴特斯  -我们完蛋了\N{\rEng}- Butters! - We're gonna get it now.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.30,0:10:35.44,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  巴特斯  冷静  我有办法\N{\rEng}Butters   Butters   calm down. I know a way out of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.45,0:10:38.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你毁了我一生\N{\rEng}You just got me busted forever!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.89,0:10:41.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  听我说  听着\N{\rEng}Butters   listen to me. Listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.15,0:10:42.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不要\N{\rEng}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.10,0:10:43.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们只要再偷溜回去\N{\rEng}All we have to do is sneak back inside
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.41,0:10:44.99,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别让警察发现就行了\N{\rEng}without the cops seeing us.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.00,0:10:46.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们就可以说我们一直在里面\N{\rEng}Then we can say we were inside all along.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.70,0:10:49.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你说他们不会发现我们不见了的\N{\rEng}You said they wouldn't notice we were gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.41,0:10:51.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你保证过的\N{\rEng}You promised.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.88,0:10:56.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们再偷溜回去\N{\rEng}If we sneak back inside
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.07,0:10:58.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不就可以说我们从来没离开过吗\N{\rEng}we can say we never left. All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.82,0:11:01.26,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好了  现在放手吧\N{\rEng}All right. Now let go of my hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.27,0:11:02.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-不行  -巴特斯\N{\rEng}- No. -Butters --
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.63,0:11:03.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你让我违反了一次规定\N{\rEng}You made me break one rule.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.67,0:11:05.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不会再违第二次了\N{\rEng}I'm not breaking the other!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.08,0:11:07.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的底线\N{\rEng}It's all I have now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.44,0:11:09.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  走吧\N{\rEng}All right   come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.65,0:11:10.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别让人质说话\N{\rEng}Keep the hostages from talking
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.95,0:11:12.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,找找看还有没有反抗者\N{\rEng}and search for holdouts.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.36,0:11:15.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,每人2分钟报告一次\N{\rEng}Everyone check in at two-minute intervals.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.37,0:11:17.32,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,希望你有好消息  奥尔里奇\N{\rEng}I hope you have good news   Ohrlich.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.33,0:11:19.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,警察已经全方位包围了我们\N{\rEng}The police have us completely surrounded on all sides.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.11,0:11:21.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果从地面上出去的话\N{\rEng}There's no way we're getting out
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.41,0:11:23.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不可能全身而退\N{\rEng}above ground without being spotted.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.06,0:11:24.20,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,地面上\N{\rEng}Above ground?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.25,0:11:27.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  我在公园后面找到这个\N{\rEng}Look. I found this at the rear of the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.29,0:11:28.67,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是个老矿井通道\N{\rEng}It's an old mine shaft.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.68,0:11:29.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但因为有个小孩死在里面\N{\rEng}But Pioneer Village was sued
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.93,0:11:31.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,先祖谷曾被起诉\N{\rEng}when a kid died in it  
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.14,0:11:33.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,于是他们就用一把巨大的密码锁\N{\rEng}so they closed it down and protected it
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.09,0:11:35.09,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,把矿井锁上了\N{\rEng}with a huge metal door with a coded lock.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.12,0:11:36.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所以  只要我们能进到矿井里\N{\rEng}So   if we can get into the shaft  
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.98,0:11:38.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们就能从地下绕过警察逃走\N{\rEng}we can tunnel our way around the police.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.41,0:11:40.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,妙极了\N{\rEng}Excellent.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.46,0:11:42.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还有一件事  弗兰茨\N{\rEng}One more thing   Franz.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.23,0:11:44.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我现在就要我的分成\N{\rEng}I want my share of the take now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.56,0:11:47.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  奥尔里奇  失去信任感了吗\N{\rEng}What's the matter   Ohrlich? Lose your sense of trust?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.41,0:11:49.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不过是在想  当我们出去后\N{\rEng}I was just thinking maybe we get through that tunnel  
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.82,0:11:51.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你带上脏物去柏林\N{\rEng}then you take the loot to Berlin
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.01,0:11:52.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我有可能再也见不到你了\N{\rEng}and I never see you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.82,0:11:55.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我要我的那份\N{\rEng}I want my cut.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.25,0:11:56.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\rEng}Very well.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.34,0:12:08.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,再问你一次\N{\rEng}I'm going to ask you again  
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.14,0:12:11.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,矿井的密码是什么\N{\rEng}what is the door code to the tunnel?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.95,0:12:15.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老爷  吾怎知矿井密码\N{\rEng}I told you   mister   what would I know about a door code?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.55,0:12:17.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾乃单纯的铁匠\N{\rEng}I'm just a simple blacksmith.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.23,0:12:18.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾为全村打铁\N{\rEng}With my trusty forge
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.53,0:12:21.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,诚信为本  童叟无欺\N{\rEng}I makes all the metalworks for the village.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.24,0:12:22.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你是这儿的员工\N{\rEng}You are an employee here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.49,0:12:24.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所以法尔码要求你必须\N{\rEng}That means you are required to know the door code
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.45,0:12:26.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,知道门的密码\N{\rEng}for fire code reasons.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.18,0:12:29.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,科罗拉多斯布瑞斯的戴维·帕默先生\N{\rEng}Mr. David Palmer of Colorado Springs.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.54,0:12:32.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾非帕默  吾乃老史密夫\N{\rEng}My name ain't Palmer. It's ol' Smithy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.42,0:12:34.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾等从未听说过法尔码为何物\N{\rEng}And we ain't never heard of no fire code.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.49,0:12:38.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾等都自行灭火\N{\rEng}Why   we got to put fires out ourselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.09,0:12:41.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,够了  要么说出密码  要么死\N{\rEng}That's it. Tell me the code or you die.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.53,0:12:46.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,1  2\N{\rEng}One   two --
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.94,0:12:49.19,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-我  -嗯\N{\rEng}- I - Yes?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.49,0:12:52.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾实不知密码为何物\N{\rEng}I don't know nothing about no fancy door code.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.35,0:12:55.28,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾只是一单纯铁匠\N{\rEng}I'm just a simple blacksmith.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.89,0:13:01.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,先祖谷的员工真是敬业啊\N{\rEng}These Pioneer Village workers are really committed to their job.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.48,0:13:03.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  求求你  别伤害吾\N{\rEng}No! Please! Don't hurt me!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.92,0:13:07.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我们密码就放你走\N{\rEng}Give us the code to that door and we can leave!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.96,0:13:10.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾从未听说密码为何物\N{\rEng}I never heard of something called a door code.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.91,0:13:13.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,汝等何不问我点别的\N{\rEng}Please   can't you ask some other way?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.29,0:13:15.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我没时间跟你们玩这傻逼游戏\N{\rEng}I don't have time for your stupid game!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.39,0:13:17.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不告诉我的话  你就死定了\N{\rEng}Tell me or you die right now!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.16,0:13:18.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  好吧\N{\rEng}All right   all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.42,0:13:22.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那是新款"真经使"家庭防盗门锁\N{\rEng}it's just one of those new Jenkins home security locks.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.21,0:13:26.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,按下顶上的按钮  然后输入5  2\N{\rEng}You press the top button and then enter 5   2 --
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.31,0:13:30.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他想说的乃是\N{\rEng}What he meant to say   kids  
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.88,0:13:33.98,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾等从未听说过密码为何物\N{\rEng}is that we ain't never heard of no fancy door code
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.99,0:13:38.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,此时吾等仅使用木锁\N{\rEng}'cuz in our time we got to rely on wood locks and such.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.42,0:13:41.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我操  你们这些神经病\N{\rEng}God dammit   you people are fucking insane!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.66,0:13:43.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信\N{\rEng}I don't believe it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.14,0:13:44.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,多米诺  沃尔斯基\N{\rEng}Domino! Volski!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.36,0:13:45.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看看还有没有漏网的\N{\rEng}Find out if there are any other
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.42,0:13:47.82,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,员工或学生\N{\rEng}employees or students wandering about.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.83,0:13:50.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,全都带过来杀光\N{\rEng}Bring them here or shoot them.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.19,0:13:52.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,靠  快藏起来  快\N{\rEng}Oh   crap   we got to hide! Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.37,0:13:58.35,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对  我们  得  得快  出  出去\N{\rEng}Yeah   we gotta   get   get the hell outta here fast!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.65,0:14:04.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,二区  无动静\N{\rEng}Sector Bravo   no activity.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.20,0:14:07.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  警察在到处找我们\N{\rEng}Jeez   the cops are looking for us everywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.57,0:14:08.84,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  在我们安全潜回去之前\N{\rEng}Don't worry. They're not gonna find us
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.84,0:14:10.34,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们不会发现我们的\N{\rEng}until we're safely back inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.35,0:14:12.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看见那个红绿灯了吗\N{\rEng}Look   see that traffic signal down there?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.95,0:14:14.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们能从上面爬过去\N{\rEng}If we can climb across that  
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.29,0:14:16.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就可以跳到那个树枝上安全回去了\N{\rEng}we can jump to the tree branch and then we're home free.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.30,0:14:17.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看起来很危险\N{\rEng}That looks dangerous.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.57,0:14:20.59,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不会老是失败的  巴特斯  来吧\N{\rEng}Not getting busted always is   Butters. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.86,0:14:29.97,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好  上来了  好  走过去\N{\rEng}Good! That's got it. Good! All right   now head across.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.80,0:14:33.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,放松  很好\N{\rEng}Go easy. Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.19,0:14:34.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,上帝保佑啊\N{\rEng}Oh   gosh in heaven.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.48,0:14:36.94,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没事  很好\N{\rEng}It's all right. We got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.95,0:14:39.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-救命  -我要掉下去了\N{\rEng}- Save me! - I'm gonna fall!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.63,0:14:48.45,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我靠  真逊\N{\rEng}Oh   dude. Lame.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.74,0:14:53.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,弗洛里奇  汇报  有找到其它员工吗\N{\rEng}Frohlich   check in. Have you found any other employees?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.37,0:14:54.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,发现了一个人\N{\rEng}We found somebody.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.69,0:14:57.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,在差官的监狱里发现了这个人\N{\rEng}We found this guy in the jail of the sheriff's office.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.95,0:15:01.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,汝等居然释放杀人犯墨菲\N{\rEng}You let out murdering Murphy!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.06,0:15:04.50,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,君子报仇十年不晚  汝等走着瞧\N{\rEng}Y'all are gonna get it for putting me in that there jail.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.52,0:15:07.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,停  别再演那傻逼历史剧了\N{\rEng}Stop it! Stop your bad historical acting right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.76,0:15:10.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真讨厌  汝等为何释放杀人犯墨菲\N{\rEng}Tarnation   why'd you let murdering murphy go?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.56,0:15:11.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,彼乃坏人\N{\rEng}He's a bad man.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.79,0:15:13.78,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我他妈才是坏人\N{\rEng}I'm the fucking bad man!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.79,0:15:14.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你们明白吗\N{\rEng}Do you get that?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.72,0:15:18.01,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别他妈演了  快给我矿井密码\N{\rEng}Knock it off and give me the mine shaft access code.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.03,0:15:19.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老爷  汝只好杀了吾等\N{\rEng}You're just gonna have to kill us   mister.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.91,0:15:22.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,因为汝所言实非理性\N{\rEng}'Cuz you ain't making no sense at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.30,0:15:24.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你要是不说的话我不会杀你们\N{\rEng}I won't kill you if you don't tell me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.03,0:15:26.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我会杀了他们中的一个\N{\rEng}I'll kill one of them!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.17,0:15:29.74,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别杀我  别杀我  别杀我  别杀我\N{\rEng}Not me! Not me! Not me! Not me! Not me!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.40,0:15:32.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你想眼睁睁看着一个小孩死吗\N{\rEng}You want to see a child die?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.54,0:15:34.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  他们不想看着一个小孩死\N{\rEng}No! They don't want to see a child die.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.72,0:15:46.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我对自己真失望\N{\rEng}I am so disappointed in myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.80,0:15:48.80,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老师给了我责任\N{\rEng}Teacher gave me a responsibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.81,0:15:51.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,只不过是照看好我的搭档\N{\rEng}I was just supposed to look after my partner
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.00,0:15:53.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但我都没做到\N{\rEng}and I blew it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.11,0:15:54.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,别跟自己过不去  巴特斯\N{\rEng}Don't be too hard on yourself   Butters.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.67,0:15:57.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,谁叫你自己是个窝囊废\N{\rEng}You can't help being a douche bag.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.06,0:15:59.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  巴特斯  看\N{\rEng}Wait   Butters! Look!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.33,0:16:03.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,机会来了  荡过去  巴特斯  走\N{\rEng}This is it. This is our chance! Swing over   butters. Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.90,0:16:09.31,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快  你准备好了吗  要跳了\N{\rEng}Quick   are you ready? We got to jump!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.32,0:16:12.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-来吧  -准备  跳\N{\rEng}- Let's do it. - Ready? Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.02,0:16:21.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么样\N{\rEng}What about you?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.30,0:16:22.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你愿意告诉我们密码\N{\rEng}Will you tell us the access code  
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.55,0:16:24.95,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还是看着这个小孩被杀\N{\rEng}or do you want to see this kid die?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.96,0:16:26.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾很抱歉  吾乃女子\N{\rEng}I'm sorry. I'm a woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.92,0:16:28.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾时女子无权知晓\N{\rEng}And women in our timime ain't allowed to know
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.65,0:16:30.55,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这般要事\N{\rEng}the carryings-on of the town proper.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.56,0:16:33.07,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,玛丽隔壁\N{\rEng}God dammit!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.08,0:16:36.12,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,哥们儿  他们会杀了肯尼的\N{\rEng}Dude! They're gonna kill Kenny!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.13,0:16:38.00,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我不能让他们那么做\N{\rEng}I can't let them do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.01,0:16:40.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我必须要做出终极牺牲\N{\rEng}I've got to make the ultimate sacrifice.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.03,0:16:43.92,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,斯坦?\N{\rEng}Stan?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.93,0:16:46.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪儿  斯坦\N{\rEng}Where are you going   Stan?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.04,0:16:47.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  我不得不这样做\N{\rEng}Wendy   I have to do something.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.88,0:16:50.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,请不要看\N{\rEng}Please look away.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.15,0:16:54.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  没办法了\N{\rEng}All right   that does it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.28,0:16:56.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,数三下  这小孩就死定了\N{\rEng}On the count of three this child dies.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.38,0:16:59.61,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-1 2  -给他们密码\N{\rEng}- One   two - - Give them the fuckin' door code!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.62,0:17:02.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,各位贵安  陌生人们\N{\rEng}Well   howdy there   strangers!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.48,0:17:04.85,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉打扰汝等\N{\rEng}Sorry to interrupt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.86,0:17:06.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾乃帕格撒斯普林斯人\N{\rEng}But I done come from Pagosa Springs
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.30,0:17:09.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,前来购入杂货\N{\rEng}to buy me some wares and such.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.29,0:17:12.72,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-噢  欢迎贵客  -贵安\N{\rEng}- Oh   welcome   partner! - Howdy!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.73,0:17:14.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-欢迎  -贵安\N{\rEng}- Welcome! - Howdy there!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.03,0:17:15.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你在干嘛\N{\rEng}What   what are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.16,0:17:16.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾听闻汝等被一越狱\N{\rEng}Say   i heard y'all had some difficulty
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.91,0:17:18.91,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,的囚犯所困扰\N{\rEng}with a criminal getting out of your jail.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.92,0:17:20.54,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,没错  杀人犯墨菲\N{\rEng}That's right! Murdering Murphy!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.55,0:17:22.69,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,彼因其父被弑而发狂\N{\rEng}He's crazy 'cuz somebody killed his paw.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.70,0:17:24.76,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,尔等杀了我父亲\N{\rEng}They killed my paw!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.78,0:17:26.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,吾想  汝等兴许可使用数字\N{\rEng}I reckon that maybe you could make a jail
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.81,0:17:29.81,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,开启监狱之门  而非钥匙也\N{\rEng}door that opened with numbers instead of keys.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.83,0:17:33.15,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好似更加安全\N{\rEng}You know like a big safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.15,0:17:36.22,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,所言极是\N{\rEng}Yeah! I understand that!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.23,0:17:39.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,终有人讲话乃清晰明了矣\N{\rEng}Finally   a feller that talks some sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.48,0:17:42.02,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,若汝等欲求此安全\N{\rEng}If y'all was to have such a giant safe  
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.03,0:17:44.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,汝欲以何等数字\N{\rEng}what would you villagers want the number to be
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.65,0:17:46.75,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,开启监狱之门\N{\rEng}to unlock that there jail door shuck 'em up?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.77,0:17:49.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,呃  吾想  用以安全门锁之\N{\rEng}Well   i reckon the easiest number to remember
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.69,0:17:54.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,最易记忆数字乃1864\N{\rEng}for any big safe door lock would be 1864.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.91,0:17:59.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对  1864乃吾等所在之年份\N{\rEng}Up! 1864   'cuz that's what year it is!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.23,0:18:00.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,1 8 6 4\N{\rEng}Eighteen sixty-four
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.84,0:18:03.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,奥尔里奇  我们有密码了  收拾东西\N{\rEng}Ohrlich   we have the door code! Start packing up!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.14,0:18:04.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,带上人质一块儿走\N{\rEng}We'll take the hostages with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.79,0:18:07.03,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不  你已经得到密码了  放了我们\N{\rEng}No! You got your door code. Let us go!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.87,0:18:10.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,收到  密码是什么  结束\N{\rEng}Copy that. What's the code   over?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.67,0:18:12.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  警察还在找我们\N{\rEng}Sweet. There's still cops looking for us in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.14,0:18:14.25,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来  巴特斯\N{\rEng}All right. Follow my lead   Butters.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.78,0:18:17.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  这地方真是人间天堂  对吧\N{\rEng}Man   hasn't this place been fascinating   Butters?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.34,0:18:18.79,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,说得没错\N{\rEng}Yeah   it sure has.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.80,0:18:20.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道哪个我更爱\N{\rEng}Oh   I just don't know what I've liked better --
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.28,0:18:23.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是历史建筑  手工艺品  还是\N{\rEng}the historical buildings and artifacts or the   the --
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.10,0:18:25.05,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,还是百姓们机智诙谐的奇闻轶事呢\N{\rEng}Or the witty anecdotes of the towns people.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.06,0:18:26.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,机智诙谐的奇闻轶事\N{\rEng}Witty anecdotes   yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.21,0:18:27.41,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,对  那真是太牛逼了\N{\rEng}That's been awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.42,0:18:28.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我都上瘾了  对吧\N{\rEng}Been a hoot. All right!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.67,0:18:30.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,双手抱头\N{\rEng}Get your hands behind your head.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.18,0:18:32.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  我们一直在这里啊\N{\rEng}What'd we do? We've been here the whole time.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.05,0:18:35.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴  双手抱头  马上\N{\rEng}Shut up! Put your hands behind your head. Do it now!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.80,0:18:41.42,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,松开手\N{\rEng}Let go of each other!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.12,0:18:43.24,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,照我说的做\N{\rEng}Do what I tell you!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.25,0:18:44.68,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们老师说  待在这里\N{\rEng}Our teacher said we have to hold hands
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.68,0:18:46.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,就得一直手牵手\N{\rEng}the whole time we're here!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.49,0:18:48.66,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,松开手  要不然我就用子弹\N{\rEng}Let go or else I'll put a bullet through your hands
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.66,0:18:49.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,让你们松开\N{\rEng}and make you let go!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.87,0:18:50.65,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯\N{\rEng}Butters.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.66,0:18:53.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-马上  -不行\N{\rEng}- Now! - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.80,0:19:00.62,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天哪\N{\rEng}Jesus christ!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.17,0:19:08.43,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,快去帮忙  我在这儿看着人质\N{\rEng}Go! Go take care of it. I'll stay with the hostages.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.82,0:19:13.53,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,杀人犯墨菲  看见那个家伙了吗\N{\rEng}Hey   Murdering Murphy. You see that there feller?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.54,0:19:14.56,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,是\N{\rEng}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.57,0:19:16.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,汝父乃此人所杀\N{\rEng}He done killed your paw.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.24,0:19:19.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,小子  杀人偿命\N{\rEng}What? I'll rip his head off!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.26,0:19:24.36,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,有机会了  人质安全\N{\rEng}We got a chance! Hostages are clear!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.48,0:19:28.96,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,他们进来了\N{\rEng}They're coming in!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.58,0:19:42.58,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,人质安全转移到公园入口\N{\rEng}Hostages are secure at the park entrance.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.59,0:19:44.88,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,仇人见面了  先祖保罗\N{\rEng}I got you now   Pioneer Paul.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.89,0:19:48.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,真不当释放汝  杀人犯墨菲\N{\rEng}They should have never let you out of jail   Murdering Murphy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.65,0:20:01.04,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,不许动  人渣  你完蛋了\N{\rEng}Freeze   scumbag! It's all over!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.95,0:20:06.47,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,杀人犯墨菲欲杀先祖保罗\N{\rEng}Murdering Murphy's gonna kill Pioneer Paul.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.48,0:20:09.40,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,马上给我停下来  都结束了\N{\rEng}Stop right now! It's over!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.95,0:20:15.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,各位贵安  五点了\N{\rEng}Howdy   partners. It's 5 o'clock.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.34,0:20:18.13,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,先祖谷今日营业到此结束\N{\rEng}Pioneer Village is now closed for the day.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.15,0:20:21.23,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,架起马车回家吧\N{\rEng}Head back to your wagons and have a safe trip home!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.26,0:20:24.06,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我们成功了  成功了\N{\rEng}We made it! We maid it!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.04,0:20:27.30,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  我迫不及待想脱掉这身衣服\N{\rEng}Oh   god. It can't wait to get out of this dress!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.60,0:20:29.90,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-真不错  －难忘的一天\N{\rEng}- That was great! - Oh   what a day!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.91,0:20:31.48,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,要是还有人想知道的话\N{\rEng}Listen   if anyone still wants to know  
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.48,0:20:33.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,电话在行政楼里\N{\rEng}the phone is in the administration building.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.19,0:20:33.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,拨9外呼\N{\rEng}You dial 9 to get out
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.77,0:20:36.77,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,马厩后面其实有个后门\N{\rEng}and there's actually a back exit behind the horse troughs.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.79,0:20:39.64,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,各位晚安  感谢光临  我们成功了\N{\rEng}Good night   everybody. Thanks for coming. We did it   guys!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.65,0:20:42.10,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,去星期五餐厅吃点墨西哥胡椒吧\N{\rEng}Let's go to TGI Fridays and get some jalapeno poppers!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.11,0:20:43.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  好主意\N{\rEng}Yeah! That'd be great!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.09,0:20:46.57,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\rEng}All right Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.44,0:20:51.21,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,斯坦  刚刚你真勇敢\N{\rEng}Stan   you were really brave in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.22,0:20:53.17,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,但你说话的语气听起来很傻逼\N{\rEng}But you did kinda sound like a big dork.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.18,0:20:54.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\rEng}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.09,0:20:55.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老实点\N{\rEng}Come on   you!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.20,0:20:57.37,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,-弄疼我胳膊了  -不得了啊\N{\rEng}-You're hurting my arm! -Too bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.38,0:20:59.29,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,你会被关很长一段时间的\N{\rEng}You'll be going away a long time.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.31,0:21:00.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,值得吗\N{\rEng}Was it worth it?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.74,0:21:02.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,某种方面  值得的\N{\rEng}In a way   it was.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.50,0:21:04.08,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,我可能会失去自由  但是\N{\rEng}I might not have gotten away   but
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.08,0:21:07.38,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,至少我学到了许多西部先祖的知识\N{\rEng}at least I learned a lot about pioneer life in the old west.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.39,0:21:08.86,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,早期的居民们并没有\N{\rEng}Those early settlers didn't have
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.86,0:21:10.16,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,如今我们认为理所当然的\N{\rEng}all the modern conveniences
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.16,0:21:12.46,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,现代便利手段\N{\rEng}we all take for granted today.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.47,0:21:15.27,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,想想看  过去那年代  就算是洗衣服\N{\rEng}To think how difficult it was back those times
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.27,0:21:17.93,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,这样简单的事做起来也很艰苦\N{\rEng}to do something as simple as washing your clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.94,0:21:20.14,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,先祖谷教给了我们许多\N{\rEng}Pioneer Village has a lot to teach us all.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.15,0:21:22.18,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,那倒没错\N{\rEng}That's true.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.75,0:21:25.33,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,看啊\N{\rEng}Hey   look!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.15,0:21:43.71,*Default,说话人,0000,0000,0000,,老师  我搭档回到车上了\N{\rEng}Teacher   my partner is back on the bus.
