[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2008-10-10 06:38:08
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayDepth: 0
PlayResX: 1916
PlayResY: 1076
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 2
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H19000000,&H000E0300,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,2,2,134,120,68,1
Style: eng,Microsoft YaHei,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,26,1
Style: Top,微软雅黑,10,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Git,Comic Sans MS,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Chn,微软雅黑,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Eng,Comic Sans MS,60,&H002AF7FF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.00,0:00:11.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm going down to south park\N gonna have myself a time 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.85,0:00:15.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Friendly faces everywhere\N humble folks without temptation 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.13,0:00:17.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Going down to south park\N gonna leave my woes behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.52,0:00:21.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ample parking day or night\N people shouting howdy neighbor
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.76,0:00:24.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heading on out to south park\N gonna see if I can't unwind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.34,0:00:28.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I like girls with big vaginas\N I like girls with big fat titties
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.41,0:00:31.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.40,0:21:45.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0060,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译制作\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}YYeTs人人影视字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.40,0:21:46.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}荨香
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.40,0:21:47.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}校对\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}sunflo Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.41,0:21:48.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0050,,{\1c&HFDC282&}后期\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}csbeyond
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.41,0:21:49.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0060,,{\1c&HFDC282&}总监\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.00,0:00:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0150,,{\1c&HFDC282&}《南方公园》第12季  第08集\N{\rEng}South Park Season 12 Episode 08
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.00,0:00:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0100,,"中国问题"\N{\rEng}"China Problem"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.01,0:00:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎收看北京奥运会\N{\rEng}Welcome to the televised broadcast
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.31,0:00:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开幕式的现场转播\N{\rEng}of the Olympic Opening Ceremonies from Beijing!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.67,0:00:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数以千计的中国演员正在表演击缶\N{\rEng}Thousands of Chinese performers play ancient Chinese drums.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.01,0:00:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庞大的演员数量\N{\rEng}The precision of their movements
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.44,0:00:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精确一致的步调\N{\rEng}made even more impressive
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.26,0:00:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更让人叹为观止\N{\rEng}by their massive numbers.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.59,0:01:07.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中国人  不  一定得制止他们\N{\rEng}The Chinese, no! Somebody has to stop them!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.57,0:01:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小宝贝  你又在做中国人的噩梦了吗\N{\rEng}Sweetie, are you having nightmare about the Chinese again?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.10,0:01:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要统治全世界\N{\rEng}They're gonna take over the world!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.23,0:01:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们人太多了\N{\rEng}Too many of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.14,0:01:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离我们远点\N{\rEng}Leave us alone!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.66,0:01:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小宝贝  你没事吧\N{\rEng}Sweetiekins, are you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.44,0:01:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  中国人要来抓我\N{\rEng}Mom, the Chinese are gonna get me!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.43,0:01:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的  小宝贝\N{\rEng}No, sweetie,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.24,0:01:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中国人不会来抓你的\N{\rEng}the Chinese aren't going to get you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.66,0:01:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会的  他们有20亿人\N{\rEng}They are so! There's 2 billion of them
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.03,0:01:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们经济发展迅速\N{\rEng}and their economy is getting better
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.48,0:01:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会利用技术上的优势\N{\rEng}and with their advances in technology
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.00,0:01:52.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打倒美国的\N{\rEng}they're going to bring down America
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.97,0:02:03.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们  我们得谈一谈\N{\rEng}All right. Guys, we need to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.84,0:02:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以装作\N{\rEng}You know, We can all just pretend that
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.49,0:02:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没看过开幕式\N{\rEng}we didn't see those opening ceremonies,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.77,0:02:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但中国人却是来真的\N{\rEng}but the Chinese are very real.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.81,0:02:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得采取措施\N{\rEng}We gotta do something.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.90,0:02:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道我们还要自欺欺人美国会没事嘛\N{\rEng}Are we just going to pretend America is going to be okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.22,0:02:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道我们要袖手旁观他们统治世界吗\N{\rEng}Are we just gonna wait until they've taken over the world?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.59,0:02:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我受不了了  我不能\N{\rEng}I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I can't do this. I'm not doing this.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.63,0:02:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  你应该对卡特曼说\N{\rEng}Kyle, you're supposed to tell Cartman
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.06,0:02:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他这是种族歧视之类的话\N{\rEng}he's being racist or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.58,0:02:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  他是白痴  但很抱歉\N{\rEng}Yeah, he's an idiot, but I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.51,0:02:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是  我实在受不了了\N{\rEng}I just, I can't do this anymore. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.97,0:02:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能再这样了\N{\rEng}I can't do this anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.90,0:02:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  你不能老是这样\N{\rEng}Kyle, You can't keep doing this.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.90,0:02:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某些意义上来说  你得想开点\N{\rEng}You know at some point you've got to let this go.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.34,0:02:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你能忘记发生的一切\N{\rEng}Maybe you can forget what happened,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.11,0:02:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我却不能\N{\rEng}but I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.13,0:02:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去的事都已经过去了\N{\rEng}Look, what happened, happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.02,0:03:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们无法改变\N{\rEng}We can't change it now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.04,0:03:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们得向前看  -向前看\N{\rEng}- We all have to move on. - Move on?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.19,0:03:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的朋友被强奸了  斯坦\N{\rEng}Our friend was raped, Stan.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.18,0:03:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他被强奸  我们却袖手旁观\N{\rEng}He was raped and we all stood there and did nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.23,0:03:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们无能为力啊  凯尔\N{\rEng}There was nothing we could do, Kyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.70,0:03:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们无能为力\N{\rEng}There was nothing we could do.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.00,0:03:16.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们当时不得不离开\N{\rEng}We had to get out of there.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.97,0:03:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\rEng}Did we?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.35,0:03:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-也许我们能阻止他们  -怎么阻止\N{\rEng}- Maybe we could have stopped them. - How?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.78,0:03:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我每晚都梦见\N{\rEng}I dream about it every night.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.87,0:03:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次我一闭上眼\N{\rEng}Every time I close my eyes
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.64,0:03:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就看到我们逃走的画面\N{\rEng}I see us just running away.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.98,0:03:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他正一遍又一遍地被人强奸\N{\rEng}Running while they rape him over and over again.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.33,0:03:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正因为我们袖手旁观\N{\rEng}And because we did nothing,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.96,0:03:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们才得以脱身\N{\rEng}they got away.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.34,0:03:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别再折磨自己了  凯尔\N{\rEng}You can't keep torturing yourself like this, Kyle
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.71,0:03:43.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想开点\N{\rEng}Let it go.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.93,0:03:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴你们能继续你们的生活\N{\rEng}I'm glad that you guys can just keep living.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.55,0:03:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我不行\N{\rEng}I don't think I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.46,0:03:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的\N{\rEng}Goddammit.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.08,0:03:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱洗澡  皮肤好好\N{\rEng}I got some splish-splash.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.05,0:03:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全身上下  好多泡泡\N{\rEng}Splish-splashy more.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.94,0:04:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你在这儿啊  巴特斯  -埃里克\N{\rEng}- There you are, Butters! - Eric?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.67,0:04:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  我需要你帮忙\N{\rEng}Butters, I need your help.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.64,0:04:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不行  埃里克  我的样子很不雅\N{\rEng}Not now. Eric, I'm indecent!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.46,0:04:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中国人要来统治我们了\N{\rEng}The Chinese are going to take us over!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.64,0:04:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而只有我们俩关心这件事\N{\rEng}And we are the only people who seem to care.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.01,0:04:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中国人\N{\rEng}The Chinese?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.31,0:04:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发了集会的传单  但似乎\N{\rEng}I handed out flyers for meetings, but it's like
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.65,0:04:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好像都瞎了\N{\rEng}everyone's blind.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.63,0:04:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中国人要统治世界了\N{\rEng}The Chinese are taking over the world
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.87,0:04:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人却都无动于衷\N{\rEng}and nobody's doing anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.79,0:04:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以得靠你和我  巴特斯\N{\rEng}It's up to you and me. Butters
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.12,0:04:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得去阻止中国人  马上\N{\rEng}We have to stop the Chinese. Now!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.14,0:04:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚我不行\N{\rEng}I can't stop them tonight,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.38,0:04:24.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要跟我爸一起做模型小汽车\N{\rEng}I'm supposed to make a model car with my dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.90,0:04:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么还不明白  巴特斯\N{\rEng}You don't get it, Butters!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.86,0:04:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的生活即将改变\N{\rEng}Our lives are about to change!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.78,0:04:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一百万个中国人打我们一个\N{\rEng}The Chinese outnumber us a million to one.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.03,0:04:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等他们打到这儿  就会杀了你爸妈\N{\rEng}And when their army gets here, they're gonna kill your parents.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.61,0:04:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们为什么要杀我爸妈\N{\rEng}Why are they gonna kill my parents?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.60,0:04:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为中国人恨美国人\N{\rEng}Because the Chinese hate Americans.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.42,0:04:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才建立了美国解放战线\N{\rEng}That's why I've started the American Liberation Front.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.55,0:04:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,致力于将美国从\N{\rEng}A group dedicated to
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.53,0:04:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中国人的压迫统治中解放出来\N{\rEng}freeing America from Chinese tyranny.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.85,0:04:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你愿意加入吗  -我不希望我爸妈死\N{\rEng}- Will you join me? - I don't want my parents to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.70,0:04:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你加入美国解放战线吗\N{\rEng}So you'll join the American Liberation Front?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.81,0:04:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好啊  -你和我\N{\rEng}- Well, sure! - You and me,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.79,0:04:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们将成为自卫反击的民族英雄\N{\rEng}we're going to be the brave little boys who fought back.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.45,0:04:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们决不会让他们统治我们的国家\N{\rEng}We are not letting them take over our country.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.93,0:04:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去他妈的中国人\N{\rEng}Fuck the Chinese.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.38,0:04:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  去他妈的\N{\rEng}Yeah, fuck'em!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.48,0:05:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  等等  我们得阻止他们\N{\rEng}No. Wait. We have to stop them.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.97,0:05:10.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在强奸他  强奸\N{\rEng}They're raping him. Rape!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.89,0:05:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们快走吧  -不可以丢下他不管\N{\rEng}- Let's get out of here! - We can't just leave!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.01,0:05:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-走吧  -太可怕了\N{\rEng}- Come on! - It's horrible!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.11,0:05:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[夺宝奇兵之水晶骷髅]
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.30,0:05:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天哪  -帮帮忙啊\N{\rEng}- Oh, God! - Somebody do something!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.50,0:05:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们为什么要这样做\N{\rEng}Why are they doing this?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.23,0:05:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们抓到印第安纳·琼斯了\N{\rEng}They're just taking Indiana Jones and they're...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.80,0:05:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在强奸他\N{\rEng}they're raping him!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.62,0:05:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看不下去了  快走  凯尔\N{\rEng}I can't watch! Let's get out of here, Kyle!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.10,0:05:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯皮尔伯格和卢卡斯为什么这么做\N{\rEng}Why would Spielberg and Lucas do this?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.38,0:05:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走吧  走吧\N{\rEng}Come on. Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.84,0:05:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们为什么这么做  -快跑\N{\rEng}- Why are they doing this? - Just run!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.74,0:05:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  真是惨绝人寰\N{\rEng}Oh, God, what have they done?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.22,0:05:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么有外星人\N{\rEng}Why aliens?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.25,0:05:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夺宝奇兵不应该有外星人\N{\rEng}Aliens don't belong in an Indiana Jones movie!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.46,0:05:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快走吧  我们无能为力  -为什么\N{\rEng}- Come on, there's nothing we can do! - Why? Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.51,0:05:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们没办法帮他  -我觉得很好看啊\N{\rEng}- We can't help him now. - I thought it was pretty good!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.88,0:05:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走吧  快走吧\N{\rEng}Let's just go! Let's just go!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.06,0:06:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  巴特斯  我们到了\N{\rEng}All right, Butters. We're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.96,0:06:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-准备好了吗  -我很害怕\N{\rEng}- Are you ready? - I'm scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.61,0:06:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我知道国家需要我\N{\rEng}But I know my country needs me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.35,0:06:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就对了  巴特斯  我们得坚强点\N{\rEng}This is it, Butters. We have to be strong.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.80,0:06:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在就去推翻那些该死的中国人\N{\rEng}We're taking down those goddamn Chinese right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.83,0:06:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[张大妈酒馆]
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.18,0:06:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在里面可能会有麻烦\N{\rEng}Things could get ugly in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.83,0:06:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得混进去\N{\rEng}We've got to infiltrate
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.56,0:06:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞到中国入侵计划\N{\rEng}and find out the Chinese invasion plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.41,0:06:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  埃里克\N{\rEng}But, Eric
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.10,0:06:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中国人怎么会告诉我们入侵计划呢\N{\rEng}why would the Chinese tell us their invasion plans?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.62,0:06:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们要让他们以为\N{\rEng}Because we're going to make them think
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.98,0:06:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也是他们中的一员\N{\rEng}we're one of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.10,0:06:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  装上假牙\N{\rEng}Here, put these teeth in.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.30,0:06:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把"l"都发音成"r"[日式英语]\N{\rEng}And just say "harro" and "prease" a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.12,0:06:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好\N{\rEng}Oh, harro prease! Bing bao ching chong!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.93,0:06:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好\N{\rEng}Bing bing harro prease.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.06,0:06:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临   马上为您服务\N{\rEng}Welcome to P.F. Chang's. I'll be right with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.39,0:06:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  那些人不是中国人\N{\rEng}Eric, those peaparu aren't Chinese.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.44,0:06:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天哪  天哪  -干嘛\N{\rEng}- Oh my God! Oh my God! - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.64,0:06:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经开始了  白人在给中国人打工了\N{\rEng}It's already started. White people working for the Chinese.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.28,0:06:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们在自己国家挨饿  -请问要什么\N{\rEng}- Starving at their own country. - Can I Help you?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.33,0:07:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  是的  你好  我们是中国人\N{\rEng}Oh, yes. Harro prease. We're Chinese people.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.94,0:07:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\rEng}Harro prease, Bing bao ching chong!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.28,0:07:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请到这边来坐吧\N{\rEng}Yeah, well. Why don't I seat you over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.00,0:07:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-服务员等会儿会过来  -非常谢谢\N{\rEng}- Your waitress will be right with you. - Ping po ching cho.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.64,0:07:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事\N{\rEng}What the hell is going on here?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.33,0:07:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得偷偷溜到后面去  他们在那儿\N{\rEng}We've got to sneak our way into the back. There they are!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.05,0:07:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中国人  那儿有中国人\N{\rEng}Chinese people. There's Chinese people right over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.98,0:07:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见了吗\N{\rEng}You see them?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.49,0:07:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  这儿有中国人  吓死我了\N{\rEng}My God. The Chinese are here. Okay, I'm freaked out.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.45,0:07:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-吓死我了  -保持冷静\N{\rEng}- I'm freaking out. - Stay calm.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.11,0:07:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就在那儿...\N{\rEng}They're right there...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.44,0:07:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会开始叫喊  敲鼓\N{\rEng}and they're gonna scream and bang on those drums and...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.31,0:07:36.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  巴特斯  好了\N{\rEng}Thank you, Butters. All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.96,0:07:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得过去那边\N{\rEng}We need to go over there and find out
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.16,0:07:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞到那些共产党杂碎的秘密\N{\rEng}what we can from those commie rats.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.36,0:07:43.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们好  -你们好\N{\rEng}- Harro prease. Harro. - Harro, prease.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.24,0:07:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老乡见老乡  两眼泪汪汪\N{\rEng}So nice to see other Chinese peaparu.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.90,0:07:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如你们所见  我们也是中国人\N{\rEng}As you can see, we are Chinese peoparu ourselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.13,0:07:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[拙劣的模仿说中文]\N{\rEng}Bing bong bing bong. Ching cho fing fong.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.59,0:07:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在干什么啊\N{\rEng}What are they doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.97,0:07:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的不知道\N{\rEng}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.99,0:07:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[拙劣的模仿说中文]\N{\rEng}Yes! Bing bong bing bong!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.81,0:08:03.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们统治美国的计划是什么来着\N{\rEng}So what are the plans to take over America again?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.21,0:08:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忘了\N{\rEng}I forgot.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.03,0:08:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉米  我不知道该怎么安慰凯尔\N{\rEng}Jimmy, I don't know what to do about Kyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.56,0:08:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想他永远都无法回到从前一样了\N{\rEng}You know, I don't think he's ever going to be the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.30,0:08:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你呢  斯坦  那天我们都在电影院\N{\rEng}And what about you, Stan? We were all in the theater that day.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.55,0:08:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都目睹了事情的发生\N{\rEng}We all saw it happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.29,0:08:30.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃  我只是试着不去想\N{\rEng}Well, I just try not to think about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.36,0:08:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为我能和从前一样\N{\rEng}I thought I could go on like before.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.49,0:08:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但当我看到印地安纳被强奸后\N{\rEng}But after seeing Indiana get raped...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.32,0:08:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我看到印地安纳被强奸后\N{\rEng}After seeing Indiana get raped,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.42,0:08:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我不会再和从前一样了\N{\rEng}I know that I'll never be the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.50,0:08:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得印地安纳在冰箱里的镜头吗\N{\rEng}Do you remember the scene with Indiana in the refrigerator?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.75,0:08:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那根本不合理啊  斯坦\N{\rEng}It didn't make any sense, Stan.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.22,0:08:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想这样\N{\rEng}I don't need this now.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.33,0:08:55.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想让事情都和从前一样而已\N{\rEng}I just want things to be the way they were!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.51,0:08:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不可能永远逃避的  斯坦\N{\rEng}You can't run from it forever, Stan!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.86,0:09:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迟早\N{\rEng}Sooner or later,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.42,0:09:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都得面对我们所看到的\N{\rEng}we all have to face what we saw.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.27,0:09:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,印地安纳·琼斯  真棒\N{\rEng}Indiana Jones, all right!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.64,0:09:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  斯坦  准备好看我的新冒险了吗\N{\rEng}Hey there, Stan! All set to see my new adventure?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.09,0:09:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  印地安纳\N{\rEng}You bet, Indiana!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.14,0:09:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当心  是斯皮尔伯格和卢卡斯\N{\rEng}Look out, Indy! It's Steven Spielberg and George Lucas!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.30,0:09:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  印地安纳\N{\rEng}Well, well, hello there, Indiana.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.40,0:09:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起来不错\N{\rEng}You're looking good.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.40,0:09:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要干什么\N{\rEng}What are you doing to do to him?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.61,0:09:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他的裤子脱掉  把裤子脱掉\N{\rEng}Yeah, get his pants down. Get his pants down.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.02,0:09:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按住他  卢卡斯\N{\rEng}Hold him, Lucas. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.32,0:09:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他哪儿也去不了了\N{\rEng}He ain't going nowhere!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.93,0:09:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手  强奸啊\N{\rEng}Stop! Rape!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.61,0:10:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  巴特斯  我们就快\N{\rEng}All right, Butters. I think we almost got
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.99,0:10:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取得中国人的信任了\N{\rEng}the Chinese to trust us.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.40,0:10:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在等他们一告诉我们入侵计划\N{\rEng}Now as soon as they tell us their invasion plan,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.72,0:10:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们立刻就跑出那扇门  好吗\N{\rEng}make a run for that door, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.55,0:10:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不错啊\N{\rEng}That's a good one, pig ling.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.23,0:10:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚说到哪儿了  对  入侵计划\N{\rEng}So where were we? Oh, yes, the invasion pwan!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.75,0:10:24.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入侵计划\N{\rEng}Invasion pwan!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.48,0:10:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪天入侵美国呢  我忘了\N{\rEng}What day is American invasion again? I forget!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.78,0:10:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  小姐\N{\rEng}Excuse me, miss?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.44,0:10:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事  先生\N{\rEng}Yes, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.55,0:10:32.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这两个人一直在骚扰我们\N{\rEng}These people won't leave us alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.15,0:10:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  没关系  我们是中国人\N{\rEng}No, no! It's okay. We are Chinese perparu.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.21,0:10:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不是中国人\N{\rEng}You aren't Chinese.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.08,0:10:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天哪  -露馅了  怎么办\N{\rEng}- Oh, my god! - We're busted! What do we do?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.50,0:10:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我看你们还是走  -退后\N{\rEng}- Okay, why don't we go... - Stay back!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.32,0:10:50.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不许动  明白吗  别碰我们\N{\rEng}Nobody moves, you got that? Don't touch us!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.44,0:10:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道中国人要干什么\N{\rEng}We know what the Chinese are up to.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.22,0:10:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们看了奥运开幕式  那么多人\N{\rEng}We saw the Olympic opening ceremonies! The gig is up!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.71,0:10:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人靠墙站好  我是认真的\N{\rEng}Everyone just step over to that wall. I mean it!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.79,0:11:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-巴特斯  拿枪对着他们  -枪?\N{\rEng}- Butters, hold this gun on them. - A gun?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.02,0:11:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-拿好枪对着他们  -我不要枪\N{\rEng}- Hold the gun on them! - I don't want a gun!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.59,0:11:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们即将统治我们的国家\N{\rEng}They're taking over our country!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.04,0:11:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是生死存亡的问题  帮我\N{\rEng}This is life or death now! Help me!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.96,0:11:07.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪\N{\rEng}Oh, jeez!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.03,0:11:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都起来  靠墙站好  快\N{\rEng}Everyone get up and get over to that wall! Do it! Move!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.21,0:11:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是美国解放战线\N{\rEng}We are the American Liberation Front!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.54,0:11:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们所有人都会\N{\rEng}And you are all going to pay
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.25,0:11:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为向中国人背叛国家付出代价\N{\rEng}for betraying your country to the Chinese.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.97,0:11:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太蠢了  我要走了\N{\rEng}This is stupid. I'm leaving.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.80,0:11:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察到之前  你哪儿也不能去\N{\rEng}You go anywhere until the police arrive!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.68,0:11:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去死吧\N{\rEng}Screw you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.97,0:11:29.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-开枪  巴特斯  -不\N{\rEng}- Shoot him, Butters! - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.75,0:11:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须开枪射他\N{\rEng}You have to shoot him.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.08,0:11:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要去给中国人通风报信\N{\rEng}He's gonna warn the Chinese
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.86,0:11:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会杀了你爸妈  快动手\N{\rEng}and they'll kill your parents! Do it!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.54,0:11:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  你打中他小鸡鸡了\N{\rEng}Oh, dude, you shot him in the dick.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.58,0:11:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不酷  巴特斯\N{\rEng}That's not cool, Butters.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.50,0:11:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以打别人的小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}You don't shoot a guy in the dick.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.90,0:11:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我只是想制止他  你说  -那不是重点\N{\rEng}- I tried to stop him and you said... - It doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.89,0:11:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能打别人的小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}You never shoot a guy in the dick.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.37,0:11:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都知道这个道理\N{\rEng}Everyone knows that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.79,0:11:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打别人的小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}Shooting a guy in the dick?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.60,0:11:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直是  简直太卑鄙了\N{\rEng}That's just... That's just weak.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.52,0:11:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不能相信你做出这种事  巴特斯\N{\rEng}I can't believe you, Butters.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.17,0:12:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[南方公园律师事务所]
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.22,0:12:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫凯尔·布罗夫洛夫斯基\N{\rEng}my name is Kyle broflovski.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.02,0:12:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上周末的悼念日  我朋友被强奸了\N{\rEng}My friend was raped last Memorial Day weekend.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.86,0:12:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我\N{\rEng}And I...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.07,0:12:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想帮他起诉强奸他的人\N{\rEng}I want to help prosecute the men responsible.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.53,0:12:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想起诉斯皮尔伯格和卢卡斯\N{\rEng}You want to bring Spielberg and Lucas
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.52,0:12:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强奸了印地安纳·琼斯\N{\rEng}to trial for raping Indiana Jones?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.38,0:12:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我必须作证\N{\rEng}I know that I'll have to testify.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.43,0:12:22.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不得不重温我所看到的一切\N{\rEng}That I'll have to relive what I saw that day.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.36,0:12:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不能让斯皮尔伯格和卢卡斯\N{\rEng}But I can't let Spielberg and Lucas
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.72,0:12:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逍遥法外\N{\rEng}get away with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.74,0:12:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再也不能了\N{\rEng}Not this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.15,0:12:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算我是孤军奋战\N{\rEng}Even if I have to do it alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.63,0:12:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是一个人在战斗\N{\rEng}You aren't alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.15,0:12:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都会作证的\N{\rEng}We'll all testify.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.70,0:12:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能让他们再次得逞\N{\rEng}We can't let them ever do this again.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.65,0:12:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我爱你  -我也爱你  斯坦\N{\rEng}- I love you. - I love you too, Stan.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.75,0:12:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鬼们  我很抱歉  但这也太荒谬了\N{\rEng}Kids, kids. I'm sorry, but this is ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.29,0:12:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-为什么  -这不算是案件\N{\rEng}- Why? - You don't have a case here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.29,0:12:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不能真的说斯皮尔伯格和卢卡斯\N{\rEng}You can't really say that Spielberg and Lucas
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.29,0:12:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在新电影里强奸了印地安纳·琼斯\N{\rEng}raped Indiana Jones in the new film.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.56,0:13:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你看过吗  -我看过  但我\N{\rEng}- Did you see it? - Yes, I saw it, but I...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.28,0:13:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是尽量不去想\N{\rEng}but I just try not to think about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.47,0:13:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就看到了他们是怎么蹂躏他的\N{\rEng}Then you saw what Lucas and Spielberg did to him!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.71,0:13:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道看见了什么\N{\rEng}I don't know what I saw!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.72,0:13:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我是说  电影院里很黑\N{\rEng}All right, I mean, it was dark in the theater.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.37,0:13:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然情节有点失控\N{\rEng}I mean, maybe things got a little out of hand with the plot,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.81,0:13:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但第三场剪辑...\N{\rEng}but the third act clipped along...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.10,0:13:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,印地安纳理应得到尊重\N{\rEng}Indy deserved more than that!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.52,0:13:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出去\N{\rEng}Get out!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.85,0:13:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快给我滚出去\N{\rEng}Just get the hell out of here!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.93,0:13:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,印地安纳·琼斯  你看起来真诱人\N{\rEng}Well, well, Indiana Jones. You're looking nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.86,0:13:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧  卢卡斯  插他\N{\rEng}There you go, Lucas. Stick 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.15,0:13:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这儿干他\N{\rEng}He's gonna do it right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.32,0:13:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好样的  乔治\N{\rEng}All right. All right, Georgie!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.61,0:13:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住他的手\N{\rEng}Grab his hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.04,0:14:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开他\N{\rEng}Hey, leave him alone!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.54,0:14:01.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来啊  大个子\N{\rEng}Come on, big guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.67,0:14:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下\N{\rEng}Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.64,0:14:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下\N{\rEng}Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.13,0:14:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愿意帮你们\N{\rEng}I want to help!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.52,0:14:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都不知道你们在说什么\N{\rEng}Look, we don't know what you're talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.81,0:14:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中国根本没有什么统治美国的计划\N{\rEng}There is no Chinese plan to take over America.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.37,0:14:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴\N{\rEng}Shut up!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.48,0:14:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些叛徒也许相信了你们的花言巧语\N{\rEng}These American traitors might have bought your propaganda,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.76,0:14:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们不会\N{\rEng}But not us!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.22,0:14:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢上帝  警察来了  我们安全了\N{\rEng}Oh, thank God. The police are here! We're safe!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.01,0:14:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿枪的人  乖乖走出来\N{\rEng}You with the gun, step out
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.52,0:14:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则我们会向你开火\N{\rEng}or we will fire upon you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.62,0:14:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们搞错了\N{\rEng}You got it wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.37,0:14:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是中国人一伙的  我们是好人\N{\rEng}We aren't with the Chinese. We're the good guys
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.70,0:15:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  天哪\N{\rEng}Oh, my god. Oh, my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.24,0:15:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么了  -有个警察也是中国人\N{\rEng}- What? - One of the cops is Chinese!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.92,0:15:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狗娘养的  事情到什么程度了\N{\rEng}Son of a bitch, how high up does this thing go?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.10,0:15:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能相信这的任何人\N{\rEng}We can't trust anybody here!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.29,0:15:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别靠近我们  我们有情报\N{\rEng}Don't come any closer! We have information that
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.38,0:15:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们只能跟美国总统谈\N{\rEng}we will only trust with the President of the United States!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.59,0:15:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-总统  -行动  闯进去\N{\rEng}- The President? - Come on men, we're going in!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.39,0:15:21.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死  我们是认真的\N{\rEng}Goddammit, we're serious.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.59,0:15:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只和总统谈话  停下\N{\rEng}We only talk to the President. Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.75,0:15:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开枪警告他们  巴特斯\N{\rEng}Fire, warning shot, Butters.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.74,0:15:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  你他妈在干什么\N{\rEng}Dude, what the fuck are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.40,0:15:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  发生什么事了\N{\rEng}What? What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.84,0:15:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死  不是说了不许射鸡鸡嘛\N{\rEng}Goddammit, what did I say about shooting guys in the dick?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.26,0:15:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-又打到了  -你他妈什么毛病啊\N{\rEng}- I did it again. - What the hell is wrong with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.39,0:15:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不酷  巴特斯  一点也不酷\N{\rEng}That's not cool, Butters. That's not cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.91,0:15:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈不可以那么干\N{\rEng}You don't fuckin' do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.73,0:15:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不能打人家的小鸡鸡  -好的  对不起\N{\rEng}- You don't shoot a guy in the dick. - Okay, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.29,0:15:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好  要是你靠射人家小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}It's not okay. Defeating Chinese won't be anything
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.16,0:15:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打败中国人的话  一点意义都没有\N{\rEng}if you do it by going around, shooting people in the dick.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.22,0:16:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的\N{\rEng}God... dammit.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.40,0:16:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,探长  都在这儿了\N{\rEng}It's all right there in front of you, detective.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.58,0:16:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来自这些勇敢的小孩的...\N{\rEng}Five sworn statements from these...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.59,0:16:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五份证词  现在就看你的了\N{\rEng}brave boys. It's now up to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.42,0:16:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有病啊\N{\rEng}Are you nuts?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.84,0:16:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不会去逮捕\N{\rEng}I'm not going out and arresting
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.28,0:16:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯蒂文·斯皮尔伯格和乔治·卢卡斯的\N{\rEng}Steven Spielberg and George Lucas!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.94,0:16:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他们强奸了印地安纳·琼斯\N{\rEng}But they raped Indiana Jones!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.44,0:16:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道想起来就很难受\N{\rEng}I know it's hard to think about.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.06,0:16:24.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你得坚强些\N{\rEng}But you have to be strong.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.27,0:16:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记住那电影给你的感受\N{\rEng}Remember how that movie made you feel.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.43,0:16:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我根本没看\N{\rEng}I didn't see it!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.09,0:16:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你没看新的夺宝奇兵吗  -没看\N{\rEng}- You didn't see the new Indiana Jones movie? - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.92,0:16:35.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想这没人看过  你看过吗   米奇\N{\rEng}I didn't think anybody here saw it! Did you, Mitch?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.66,0:16:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这丛林小道上干嘛呢\N{\rEng}What you doing in our neck of the woods?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.84,0:16:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在脱掉你的裤子\N{\rEng}Now let's you just drop them pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.99,0:16:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-脱掉?  -马上脱了\N{\rEng}- Drop? - Just take 'em right off.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.41,0:16:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们想干嘛\N{\rEng}What do you guys want?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.52,0:16:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说话  照我们说的做\N{\rEng}Don't say anything. Just do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.34,0:17:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,衣服也脱掉\N{\rEng}Pull off that little ol' bitty... shirt there, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.66,0:17:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内裤  脱掉\N{\rEng}Them panties, take 'em off.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.32,0:17:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逮到了\N{\rEng}There boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.25,0:17:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打赌你会尖叫的\N{\rEng}I bet you can squeal.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.93,0:17:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打赌你会像猪一样尖叫的\N{\rEng}I bet you can squeal like a pig.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.18,0:17:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始  尖叫吧  尖叫啊\N{\rEng}Go ahead, squeal. Squeal now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.57,0:17:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尖叫\N{\rEng}Squeal.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.36,0:17:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尖叫\N{\rEng}Squeal.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.57,0:17:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫大声点\N{\rEng}Squeal louder!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.24,0:17:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大声点\N{\rEng}Louder!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.97,0:17:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大声点  趴下\N{\rEng}Louder. Get down there, boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.01,0:17:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脱掉短裤  对  快尖叫\N{\rEng}There, get them britches down. Yes, sir. Come on, squeal.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.49,0:17:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的\N{\rEng}It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.71,0:17:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再也不会感觉孤单了\N{\rEng}You don't have to feel alone anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.55,0:18:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你听我说\N{\rEng}No, you listen to me!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.31,0:18:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我逮住了中国刺客和中国支持者\N{\rEng}I have Chinese attackers here and Chinese supporters.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.10,0:18:11.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我出去\N{\rEng}If I go outside,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.98,0:18:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有更多的中国人要把我放倒\N{\rEng}there are more Chinese ready to take me down.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.20,0:18:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在最重要的是保卫美国\N{\rEng}Defending America is all that matters,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.70,0:18:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总统先生  我会不惜一切\N{\rEng}Mr. President, I will stop at nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.82,0:18:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明不明白我...\N{\rEng}Do you understand that I...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.33,0:18:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么了  -他们...\N{\rEng}- What happened? - They...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.83,0:18:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想从房顶进来\N{\rEng}tried to come in through the roof.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.16,0:18:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们想抢走我的枪\N{\rEng}They were gonna take the gun!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.57,0:18:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  你杀了他们吗\N{\rEng}Good. Did you kill 'em?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.49,0:18:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\rEng}Not exactly.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.78,0:18:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛啊\N{\rEng}Oh, it stings.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.03,0:18:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保证  我没瞄那里\N{\rEng}It's not where I aimed, honest!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.33,0:18:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计\N{\rEng}Dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.37,0:18:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的不是故意的\N{\rEng}I seriously didn't mean it!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.30,0:18:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计\N{\rEng}Dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.19,0:18:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道嘛  巴特斯\N{\rEng}You know what, Butters? You know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.36,0:18:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了\N{\rEng}Forget it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.38,0:18:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪儿\N{\rEng}Where you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.58,0:18:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你继续这么干的话\N{\rEng}You can deal with the Chinese invasion yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.62,0:18:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己去对付中国人吧  我不干了\N{\rEng}if that's how you're gonna do it. I'm out, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.50,0:18:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己?\N{\rEng}By, by myself?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.79,0:19:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我的本意\N{\rEng}I didn't sign up for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.51,0:19:02.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你的美国解放阵线\N{\rEng}You take your American liberation front
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.59,0:19:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你的吧\N{\rEng}And you shove it up your ass!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.53,0:19:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  杀我吧  随便你们怎么样\N{\rEng}That's it. Kill me. Do whatever.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.85,0:19:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不再是义胆忠肝的\N{\rEng}I can no longer conscionably be...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.55,0:19:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美国解放阵线的人\N{\rEng}Part of the American liberation front.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.24,0:19:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进去  行动\N{\rEng}Go inside. Move!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.44,0:19:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔治·卢卡斯  斯蒂文·斯皮尔伯格\N{\rEng}George Lucas and Steven Spielberg,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.08,0:19:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有你们的逮捕令\N{\rEng}We have a warrant for your arrest.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.45,0:19:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闯进去\N{\rEng}Break it in.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.80,0:19:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪\N{\rEng}My God!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.44,0:19:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们来这儿干嘛\N{\rEng}What the hell are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.17,0:19:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们没证据\N{\rEng}You got nothing on us!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.65,0:19:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,7亿美元的票房收入\N{\rEng}$700 million box office!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.17,0:19:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真操蛋\N{\rEng}This is bullshit!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.89,0:19:52.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们被捕了  -什么\N{\rEng}- Boys, they got 'em. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.00,0:19:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯皮尔伯格和卢卡斯\N{\rEng}Spielberg and Lucas
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.44,0:19:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察进门时  他们正在\N{\rEng}They were raping a stormtrooper
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.03,0:19:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强奸星球大战里的克隆人\N{\rEng}when the police broke in.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.35,0:19:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在衣柜里发现了被强奸过的\N{\rEng}And they found the dead raped bodies of yoda
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.55,0:20:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犹大大师和夺宝奇兵里的小孩的尸体\N{\rEng}And short round in their closet.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.67,0:20:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们再也不能为非作歹了\N{\rEng}They'll never be free to do this again.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.74,0:20:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那现在呢\N{\rEng}So what now?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.95,0:20:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得经历了这些事之后\N{\rEng}Do you think things can ever go back to
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.51,0:20:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情还能回到正常的轨道吗\N{\rEng}to normal after all this?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.23,0:20:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们该怎么办\N{\rEng}What do we do?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.78,0:20:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们继续生活\N{\rEng}We live.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.58,0:20:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这正是印地安纳所希望的\N{\rEng}That's what Indy would have wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.52,0:20:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们努力活下去\N{\rEng}We just try to live.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.16,0:20:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都待在原地别动\N{\rEng}Everyone just stay where you are
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.67,0:20:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们先调查一下\N{\rEng}until we can sort this all out.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.73,0:20:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么可调查的  把这些小孩抓起来\N{\rEng}There's nothing to sort out! These kids need to be put in jail!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.51,0:20:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要搜查每个人\N{\rEng}We're going to search everyone
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.13,0:20:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-录口供然后  -长官  结束了\N{\rEng}- and get statements and then... - Sir! Sir, it's over!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.71,0:20:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们被捕了  -谁\N{\rEng}- They got 'em. - Got who?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.34,0:20:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯皮尔伯格和卢卡斯  他们\N{\rEng}Spielberg and Lucas, they...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.25,0:20:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于被捕了  真是罪有应得\N{\rEng}finally got 'em for what they did to Indiana Jones, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.72,0:20:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们被捕了\N{\rEng}They got 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.00,0:20:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们被捕了  都结束了  -结束了\N{\rEng}- They got 'em. It's over. - It's over.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.38,0:20:49.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说  他们再也不能肆意强奸了\N{\rEng}That means they'll never be free to rape again!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.79,0:20:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束了\N{\rEng}It's over!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.10,0:20:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正义啊\N{\rEng}Justice!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.24,0:20:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们被捕了  -都结束了\N{\rEng}- They got 'em! - It's over!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.99,0:20:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我爱你  -我也爱你\N{\rEng}- I love you. - I love you, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.13,0:21:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  这就完了\N{\rEng}So wait. That's it?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.76,0:21:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中国侵略怎么办\N{\rEng}What about the Chinese invasion?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.56,0:21:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经不在乎了  巴特斯\N{\rEng}I really don't care anymore. Butters
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.64,0:21:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天学到了一些东西\N{\rEng}You see, I've learned something today.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.70,0:21:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为美国人  害怕看到\N{\rEng}As Americans, our fear of seeing
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.93,0:21:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别的国家变得强大\N{\rEng}another country become powerful
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.45,0:21:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使我们变得疯狂\N{\rEng}can turn us into monsters.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.23,0:21:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着你变得如此疯狂  看着你\N{\rEng}Watching how crazy you went, watching you just
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.77,0:21:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样射别人的小鸡鸡\N{\rEng}shoot people in the dick like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.98,0:21:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使我意识到  我希望美国安全\N{\rEng}It made me realize that I want America to be safe,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.75,0:21:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不能以尊严来换取\N{\rEng}but not at the cost of losing its dignity.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.41,0:21:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我情愿做中国人\N{\rEng}I'd rather us be Chinese,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.36,0:21:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不愿做无良的鸡鸡射手民族\N{\rEng}than a nation of unethical dick-shooters.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.35,0:21:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己好好想想\N{\rEng}You think about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.20,0:21:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信他们被捕了\N{\rEng}Can't believe they put 'em in jail.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.96,0:21:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得那部电影挺好看啊\N{\rEng}I thought that movie was pretty good!
