[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2008-10-10 06:38:08
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayDepth: 0
PlayResX: 1916
PlayResY: 1076
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 2
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H19000000,&H000E0300,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,2,2,134,120,68,1
Style: eng,Microsoft YaHei,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,26,1
Style: Top,微软雅黑,10,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Git,Comic Sans MS,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Chn,微软雅黑,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Eng,Comic Sans MS,60,&H002AF7FF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.00,0:00:11.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm going down to south park\N gonna have myself a time 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.85,0:00:15.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Friendly faces everywhere\N humble folks without temptation 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.13,0:00:17.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Going down to south park\N gonna leave my woes behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.52,0:00:21.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ample parking day or night\N people shouting howdy neighbor
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.76,0:00:24.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heading on out to south park\N gonna see if I can't unwind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.34,0:00:28.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I like girls with big vaginas\N I like girls with big fat titties
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.41,0:00:31.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.40,0:21:45.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0060,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译制作\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}YYeTs人人影视字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.40,0:21:46.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.40,0:21:47.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}校对\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}sunflo Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.41,0:21:48.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0050,,{\1c&HFDC282&}后期\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}csbeyond
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.41,0:21:49.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0060,,{\1c&HFDC282&}总监\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.00,0:00:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0150,,{\1c&HFDC282&}《南方公园》第12季  第09集\N{\rEng}South Park Season 12 Episode 09
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.00,0:00:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0100,,"乳癌风波"\N{\rEng}"Breast Cancer Show Ever"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.06,0:00:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  孩子们  全部回座位\N{\rEng}Okay. Chilildren,let's all take our seats.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.44,0:00:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始讲课前\N{\rEng}Before we get started today.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.72,0:00:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂·泰斯伯格要和\N{\rEng}Wendy Testaburger has asked to
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.46,0:00:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同学们分享一些东西\N{\rEng}Share something with the class.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.08,0:00:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂\N{\rEng}Wendy?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.44,0:00:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  加里森老师\N{\rEng}Thank you,Mr. Garrison.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.87,0:00:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同学们\N{\rEng}Fellow students,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.62,0:00:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,10月是女性主要\N{\rEng}October is awareness month for one of
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:53.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死因之一的宣传月\N{\rEng}The leading causes of death in women.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.19,0:00:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一种每天都能夺走数名\N{\rEng}A terrible disease that takes the lives
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.84,0:00:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美国女性的可怕疾病\N{\rEng}Of American women every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.53,0:00:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然我在说的是\N{\rEng}I'm talking of course
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.47,0:01:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳癌\N{\rEng}About breast cancer.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.46,0:01:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六分之一的女性\N{\rEng}An estimated one in six women
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.28,0:01:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在生活中要与癌症抗争\N{\rEng}will deal with cancer in their lifetime.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.20,0:01:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而乳癌是最常见的\N{\rEng}And breast cancer is the most common
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.69,0:01:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她居然又说了一次\N{\rEng}She said it again.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.00,0:01:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有问题吗\N{\rEng}Is there a problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.70,0:01:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为乳癌可不是玩笑\N{\rEng}Because breast cancer isn't funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.14,0:01:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳癌会要人命的\N{\rEng}Breast cancer is killing people.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.24,0:01:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加里森老师  我们有必要\N{\rEng}Mr. Garrison, do we really need
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.18,0:01:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在课堂上说这种琐事吗\N{\rEng}All of this potty talk in the classroom?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.61,0:01:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  拜托\N{\rEng}Eric, for the love of jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.02,0:01:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个严肃的话题  埃里克\N{\rEng}This is a serious issue Eric,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.54,0:01:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的行为非常无礼\N{\rEng}What you're doing is offensive.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.34,0:01:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  是你在说\N{\rEng}Me, you're the one
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.23,0:01:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀人咪咪\N{\rEng}Talking about killer titties,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.87,0:01:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心  伙计们\N{\rEng}Watch out,guys,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.45,0:01:34.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂说咪咪能杀人\N{\rEng}Wendy says boobs can kill people.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.61,0:01:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要抓你了  温蒂\N{\rEng}Ah,gonna get you.Wendy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.86,0:01:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想被咪咪杀掉\N{\rEng}I don't want to get killed by boobs.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.08,0:01:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁能想点办法\N{\rEng}Will somebody do something.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.67,0:01:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每周他越来越放肆\N{\rEng}Every week he gets worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.76,0:01:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却没有人制止\N{\rEng}And nobody does anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.83,0:01:45.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  别这么没礼貌\N{\rEng}Eric, stop being offensive.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.63,0:01:46.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想跟温蒂\N{\rEng}I'm trying to engage Wendy
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.85,0:01:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨论一下\N{\rEng}In a constructive dialog
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.66,0:01:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳癌的宣传  加里森老师\N{\rEng}About breast cancer awareness.Mr.Garrison
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.84,0:01:51.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你才不是\N{\rEng}No, you aren't.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.27,0:01:52.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  你要冷静点\N{\rEng}Wendy, you need to calm down,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.63,0:01:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会惹恼你的咪咪\N{\rEng}You'll get your boobs angry,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.63,0:01:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们会杀了所有人的\N{\rEng}And they'll start killing everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.44,0:01:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天很有状态啊\N{\rEng}Dude,I'm on fire today!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.84,0:02:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家小心\N{\rEng}Look out everyone,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.71,0:02:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这有逍遥法外的杀人咪咪\N{\rEng}There's some killer titties on the loose.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.79,0:02:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能有武器  我听到它们从楼顶过来了\N{\rEng}Could have sword, I heard them coming through the roof.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.62,0:02:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警官  我们要全国追查这些咪咪\N{\rEng}Officer, We need to get an apb out on those titties,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.12,0:02:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们是武装危险分子\N{\rEng}They're armed and dangerous.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.93,0:02:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么回事\N{\rEng}What is your problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.36,0:02:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳癌可不是玩笑\N{\rEng}Breast cancer isn't funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.47,0:02:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不是\N{\rEng}Not at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.95,0:02:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  我们要抓你了\N{\rEng}Wendy, we are going to get you wendy,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.43,0:02:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的咪咪在哪\N{\rEng}Where are your boobs,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.61,0:02:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要杀你\N{\rEng}We are going to kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.84,0:02:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好闭嘴\N{\rEng}You better shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.58,0:02:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则我会让你闭嘴\N{\rEng}Or I'll make you shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.16,0:02:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  你打算\N{\rEng}Really, what are you
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.00,0:02:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么做  温蒂\N{\rEng}Going to do about it Wendy?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.58,0:02:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会踹你屁股\N{\rEng}I'm going to kick your ass,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.32,0:02:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说到做到\N{\rEng}That's what I am going to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.05,0:02:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要踹我屁股\N{\rEng}Your gonna kick your ass?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.81,0:02:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我会踹你屁股\N{\rEng}That's right, i am gonna kick my ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.44,0:02:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想单挑吗  伙计\N{\rEng}You want to throw down,dawg.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.55,0:02:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我奉陪\N{\rEng}I'll throw down.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.67,0:02:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为你很牛逼吗\N{\rEng}You think you're tough.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.17,0:02:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎样\N{\rEng}What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.83,0:02:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会把你揍到屁股开花\N{\rEng}I'll smack the shit out of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.29,0:02:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就单挑  走吧  八婆\N{\rEng}Throw down right here,Let's go,bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.18,0:02:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放学后\N{\rEng}After school,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.87,0:02:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放学后单挑  你听到了吗\N{\rEng}We fight after school, you got that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.24,0:02:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要和我放学后单挑\N{\rEng}You're gonna fight me after school?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.33,0:02:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.33,0:02:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是个妞  伙计\N{\rEng}You're a chick, dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.91,0:02:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下课铃一响\N{\rEng}As soon as that bell rings,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.34,0:02:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就去外面单挑  听到没有\N{\rEng}We do it outside,you got that?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.77,0:02:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时别做缩头乌龟\N{\rEng}And you better be there.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.49,0:02:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么定  八婆\N{\rEng}It's on bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.70,0:02:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈死定了\N{\rEng}You're going fucking die!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.49,0:03:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂和埃里克放学后单挑\N{\rEng}Wendy and Eric are fighting after school.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.31,0:03:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位\N{\rEng}Hey,everybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.41,0:03:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂和埃里克放学后单挑\N{\rEng}Wendy and eric are fighting after school.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.76,0:03:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -哇\N{\rEng}- What? - Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.79,0:03:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂和卡特曼放学后单挑\N{\rEng}Wendy and Cartman Are going to fight after school
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.87,0:03:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗  -哇\N{\rEng}- Really? - Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.93,0:03:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂和卡特曼放学后单挑\N{\rEng}Wendy and Cartman Are fighting after school.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.06,0:03:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金属小子\N{\rEng}Hey, emo kids,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.83,0:03:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡特曼和温蒂放学后单挑\N{\rEng}Cartman and Wendy Are gonna fight after school.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.61,0:03:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她刚叫我们金属小子吗\N{\rEng}Did she just call us emos?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.09,0:03:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  难以置信\N{\rEng}Gee, i can't believe
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.97,0:03:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂要和你放学后单挑\N{\rEng}Wendy's gonna fight you after school.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.05,0:03:33.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她好生气\N{\rEng}She is pissed off.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.91,0:03:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不会来单挑的  伙计\N{\rEng}She's not gonna show up to a fight, dawg.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.39,0:03:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她肯定在想办法逃跑了\N{\rEng}I'm sure she's already tried to Figure a way to get out of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.11,0:03:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看  她在用目光压倒你\N{\rEng}Hey, check it out, She's totally staring you down.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.94,0:03:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她似乎相当自信\N{\rEng}She sure seems confident,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.10,0:03:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是对她下手轻点  伙计\N{\rEng}You should properly go easy on her, dude,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.82,0:03:52.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会想把她打到进医院吧\N{\rEng}You don't want to Put her in hospital or anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.75,0:03:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想教训一下她\N{\rEng}I'm gonna teach her a lesson,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.08,0:03:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会往死里打的\N{\rEng}I'm not gonna totally kick her ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.89,0:04:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也别太便宜她\N{\rEng}Can't go too easy on her, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.03,0:04:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算她没那个能力揍你\N{\rEng}God forbid she has a good punch to beat you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.58,0:04:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  如果你被女生撂倒\N{\rEng}Yeah, if you get beat by a girl,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.68,0:04:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都会把你看成基佬\N{\rEng}Everyone would think you're a faggot.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.16,0:04:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  我能和你谈谈吗\N{\rEng}Wendy, could i talk to you for a second?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.20,0:04:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.66,0:04:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  我想向你道歉\N{\rEng}Wendy, i want to apologize,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.47,0:04:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并告诉你\N{\rEng}And tell you that...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.21,0:04:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.75,0:04:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想向你道歉\N{\rEng}I want to apologize,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.97,0:04:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并告诉你\N{\rEng}And tell you that,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.18,0:04:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉我说的话\N{\rEng}I'm sorry for what i said, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.69,0:04:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我错了\N{\rEng}It was wrong of me,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.33,0:04:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向你保证不会有第二次\N{\rEng}And i promise you That it won't happen again.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.36,0:04:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想放学后跟你单挑\N{\rEng}I don't want to fight you after school,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.78,0:04:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗\N{\rEng}All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.87,0:04:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\rEng}So, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.24,0:04:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是真想道歉\N{\rEng}If you're really sorry,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.04,0:04:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就当着大家的面说\N{\rEng}You can say it in front of everyone!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.03,0:04:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其实是这样想的\N{\rEng}Actually i was thinking
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.01,0:04:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就私下了结\N{\rEng}Let's just keep this between us.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.26,0:04:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拿乳癌开玩笑是不对\N{\rEng}I was wrong to make fun of breast cancer.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.71,0:04:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对此我非常后悔\N{\rEng}And I'm very remorse for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.53,0:05:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你要是真的后悔\N{\rEng}No, if you're really sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.09,0:05:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要向我道歉\N{\rEng}And you want to apologize to me,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.75,0:05:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就当着所有人的面说\N{\rEng}Then do it in front of everyone!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.75,0:05:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道歉\N{\rEng}Apologize?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.93,0:05:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没说过  臭婊子\N{\rEng}That's not what i said dumb bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.90,0:05:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说了\N{\rEng}Yes, you did,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.45,0:05:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚刚站在这里说你很抱歉\N{\rEng}You just stood there And said you apologized
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.68,0:05:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说不想单挑了\N{\rEng}And you don't want to fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.26,0:05:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂\N{\rEng}Wendy,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.88,0:05:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怕到用这种方法逃避\N{\rEng}Such a desperate attempt to get out of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.27,0:05:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些学生这么聪明\N{\rEng}These students are too smart to see
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.31,0:05:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接就能看穿你在找借口脱逃\N{\rEng}You're just making excuses not to fight me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.42,0:05:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不用找借口\N{\rEng}I don't want excuses.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.68,0:05:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我他妈会揍扁你\N{\rEng}I'm gonna beat the fucking shit out of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.59,0:05:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑\N{\rEng}That's funny,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.40,0:05:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你死定了  基女\N{\rEng}You're going to die,you lezbo.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.87,0:05:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  真的\N{\rEng}Wendy, seriously, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.04,0:05:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的想道歉\N{\rEng}I do want to apologize,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.80,0:05:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我非常抱歉\N{\rEng}I'm really sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.12,0:05:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得还是不要打架了\N{\rEng}And i don't think we should fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.55,0:05:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离我远点\N{\rEng}Get away from me!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.23,0:05:52.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都在说埃里克·卡特曼\N{\rEng}So, everyone is saying There's going to be a fight 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.09,0:05:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你女朋友要单挑\N{\rEng}between Eric cartman and your girlfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.01,0:05:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是\N{\rEng}I guess so.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.28,0:05:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你难道准备让那小子抽你女人\N{\rEng}And you're going to Just let that guy beat up on your woman?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.72,0:06:01.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不觉得这有违你的\N{\rEng}Doesn't that like Go against your
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.49,0:06:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男友职责什么的吗\N{\rEng}Jockey man code or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.22,0:06:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  我不记得AC/DC唱过有关\N{\rEng}Yeah, i don't ever remember AC/DC singing about 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.56,0:06:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让别人打自己女友的歌\N{\rEng}letting dudes Beat up on your girlfriends.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.69,0:06:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能怎么办\N{\rEng}What am i supposed to do about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.47,0:06:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  斯坦\N{\rEng}Don't worry, stan,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.24,0:06:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得不太可能单挑了\N{\rEng}I don't think the fight is going to happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.96,0:06:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡特曼说温蒂已经求他取消单挑了\N{\rEng}Cartman says that wendy's already Begging him to call it off.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.57,0:06:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真胆小\N{\rEng}How bitchy she is!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.76,0:06:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想这样\N{\rEng}I hope not,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.72,0:06:21.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想看埃里克把她打到屁股开花\N{\rEng}I want to see Eric kick the crap out of her.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.88,0:06:27.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-温蒂  -干嘛\N{\rEng}- Wendy. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.05,0:06:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快说完  很快\N{\rEng}Real quick,Just,Real quick.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.67,0:06:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  你肯定不会相信\N{\rEng}Wendy, you're not gonna believe this,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.05,0:06:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚发现我妈妈有乳癌\N{\rEng}I just found out my mom has breast cancer.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.96,0:06:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我真是罪有应得\N{\rEng}Man, i sure got what was coming to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.63,0:06:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是个混球  现在\N{\rEng}I was a real jerk and now
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.96,0:06:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要切掉我妈的咪咪\N{\rEng}They're gonna cut off my mom's boobs.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.39,0:06:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我会信你的鬼话吗\N{\rEng}You really think that's going to work on me?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.07,0:06:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  我这有27美元现钞\N{\rEng}Wendy, i have here 27 dollars in cash.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.99,0:06:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你能取消单挑  我就\N{\rEng}If you just call off the fight then i...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.06,0:06:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你休想用钱买出路\N{\rEng}You can't bribe your way out of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.15,0:07:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  我有肌肉萎缩症\N{\rEng}Wendy, i have muscular dystrophy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.47,0:07:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才没有\N{\rEng}No, you don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.66,0:07:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈有肌肉萎缩症\N{\rEng}My mom has muscular dystrophy
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.10,0:07:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的咪咪有\N{\rEng}In her boobs.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.35,0:07:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还不懂吗  白痴\N{\rEng}You don't get it asshole,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.78,0:07:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你休想阻止这次单挑\N{\rEng}There's nothing you can do To stop this fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.00,0:07:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会用你刷遍操场\N{\rEng}I am gonna wipe the playground with you
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.72,0:07:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当着大家的面\N{\rEng}Right in front of everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.43,0:07:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把你的屁股塞到你喉咙里\N{\rEng}I'm gonna shove your ass down your throat
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.56,0:07:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你吃你的内裤\N{\rEng}And make you eat your underwear.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.48,0:07:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃我的内裤\N{\rEng}Eat my underwear?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.33,0:07:20.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.21,0:07:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  温蒂\N{\rEng}Okay, wendy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.51,0:07:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在就吃给你看  就在这\N{\rEng}I'll eat my underwear right here right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.72,0:07:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝\N{\rEng}Jesus christ.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.64,0:07:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就一点自尊都没有吗\N{\rEng}Do you have no sense of self-respect.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.86,0:07:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  除非你想要\N{\rEng}No, unless you want me to,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.45,0:07:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想的话我就有自尊\N{\rEng}You want me to have self-respect then i will.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.35,0:07:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真他妈的操蛋\N{\rEng}You fucking suck so hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.65,0:07:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会吃内裤的  温蒂\N{\rEng}I'll eat my underwear,Wendy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.44,0:07:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你就满足了\N{\rEng}And then you'll be satisfy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.76,0:07:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以忘掉这件事\N{\rEng}We can put this whole thing behind us.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.53,0:07:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干嘛\N{\rEng}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.54,0:07:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我热衷和平  温蒂\N{\rEng}I'm committed to peace, Wendy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.63,0:07:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要让你看\N{\rEng}I want you to see,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.65,0:07:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有多谦卑\N{\rEng}Just how humbleed i am,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.43,0:07:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我多么\N{\rEng}How much i ...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.60,0:07:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  看着我\N{\rEng}Wendy, look at me, wendy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.08,0:07:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\rEng}Oh, my god.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.99,0:08:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们和好了吗\N{\rEng}So, are we cool?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.12,0:08:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\rEng}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.22,0:08:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把内裤都吃了\N{\rEng}I ate my underwear,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.44,0:08:07.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还想要我怎么样\N{\rEng}What the hell do you want from me?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.29,0:08:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是可悲\N{\rEng}You are so pathetic.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.03,0:08:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  这不公平\N{\rEng}Wendy,it isn't fair.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.12,0:08:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为你吃了内裤啊  不\N{\rEng}I ate my underwear for you, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.52,0:08:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  伙计\N{\rEng}Yo,what's up dawg?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.54,0:08:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯坦  伙计  我们要谈谈\N{\rEng}Stan.Dude we need to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.09,0:08:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.05,0:08:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂和我估计要打上3个小时\N{\rEng}You know, wendy and I Are suppose to fight like three hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.52,0:08:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对  -伙计  你不担心吗\N{\rEng}- Yeah. - Dude, aren't you worried?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.27,0:08:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂是个女生\N{\rEng}Wendy is a girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.10,0:08:32.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她可能会严重受伤的  斯坦\N{\rEng}She could end up getting really hert, stan,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.80,0:08:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我兄弟\N{\rEng}You're my bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.48,0:08:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是你的马子\N{\rEng}And she's your bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.65,0:08:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想伤害我兄弟的马子\N{\rEng}I don't wanna hurt my bro's bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.25,0:08:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无能为力\N{\rEng}I can't do anything,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.07,0:08:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很想跟你打\N{\rEng}She really wants to fight you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.95,0:08:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  她不想\N{\rEng}No,no.she doesn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.01,0:08:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她跟我说她不想单挑\N{\rEng}She told me she doesn't want to fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.67,0:08:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就是想不开  老兄\N{\rEng}She just stuck,men.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.63,0:08:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为她知道我会踹她的屁股\N{\rEng}Because she knows I'm gonna kick her ass
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.88,0:08:46.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她觉得她不跟我单挑\N{\rEng}But she feels like she doesn't fight me
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.59,0:08:48.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他小孩会叫她胆小鬼\N{\rEng}All the kids will call her chicken.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.07,0:08:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\rEng}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.76,0:08:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道她做了什么吗\N{\rEng}You know what she did,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.39,0:08:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她道歉了\N{\rEng}She apologized
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.88,0:08:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还求我不要跟她打\N{\rEng}And begged me not to fight her.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.75,0:08:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  温蒂  你要是真想道歉\N{\rEng}I said,well,wendy,if you're so sorry,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.18,0:08:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就当着大家的面说\N{\rEng}The say it in front of everyone,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.27,0:08:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她做不到\N{\rEng}But she wouldn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.84,0:08:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看她多绝望\N{\rEng}That's how desperate she is.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.37,0:09:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得想办法  斯坦\N{\rEng}You have to do something, stan.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.60,0:09:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈要像个男人\N{\rEng}You have to be a fucking man,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.65,0:09:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阻止她打架\N{\rEng}And forbid her from fighting.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.85,0:09:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她才有出路\N{\rEng}So she has a way...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.64,0:09:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  我内裤就是放在这的\N{\rEng}Oh, that's where i put those.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.73,0:09:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样  斯坦\N{\rEng}Anyway, stan.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.09,0:09:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得阻止这次单挑\N{\rEng}You've got to put a stop to the fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.70,0:09:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂想不开  她需要你\N{\rEng}Wendy stuck,and she needs you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.74,0:09:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  我无能为力\N{\rEng}Dude, there's nothing I can do about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.94,0:09:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  你真是个娘娘腔  斯坦\N{\rEng}God, you are such a pussy,stan.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.66,0:09:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是个娘娘腔\N{\rEng}You're such a pussy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.04,0:09:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要是伤了温蒂\N{\rEng}When i hurt wendy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.93,0:09:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你一手造成的\N{\rEng}It's gonna be on your fucking hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.24,0:09:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以这个时候\N{\rEng}And so you see at this point.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.52,0:09:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欧里庇得斯知道他不可能赢得战争\N{\rEng}Euripides knew he could not win the battle.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.46,0:09:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会用你刷遍操场\N{\rEng}I'm going to wipe the playground with you,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.32,0:09:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当着大家的面\N{\rEng}Right in front of everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.08,0:09:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是被女生撂倒\N{\rEng}If you got beat by a girl
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.52,0:09:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都会把你看成基男\N{\rEng}Everyone would say you're a faggot.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.74,0:09:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  孩子们  今晚的作业\N{\rEng}Alright,kids.for your homework tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.57,0:10:02.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你们阅读第七章\N{\rEng}I want you all to read chapter seven.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.81,0:10:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踹死这个白痴  温蒂\N{\rEng}Kick this asshole,Wendy!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.64,0:10:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下课铃只要一响\N{\rEng}Soon as the bell rings.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.26,0:10:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们冲到外面\N{\rEng}We've got to get out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.20,0:10:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找个好地点观看单挑\N{\rEng}And find a good place to watch the fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.45,0:10:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没出路了\N{\rEng}There's no way out,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.19,0:10:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她会在大家面前踹我的屁股\N{\rEng}She's gonna kick my ass In front of everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.74,0:10:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就快到了\N{\rEng}Almost there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.04,0:10:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好  明天早上要测验\N{\rEng}And be ready for a quiz tomorrow morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.72,0:10:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看不了单挑了  伙计\N{\rEng}I totally can't see the fight,dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.15,0:10:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我放学后要留堂\N{\rEng}I've got detention after school.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.46,0:10:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留堂  对了\N{\rEng}Detention, that's it!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.01,0:10:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须要留堂  要快\N{\rEng}I've got to get detention fast!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.89,0:10:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  你刚在我桌上拉屎吗\N{\rEng}Eric, did you just take a crap on my desk?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.71,0:10:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎样\N{\rEng}What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.55,0:10:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你桌上拉屎  伙计\N{\rEng}Crapped on your desk,dawg.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.57,0:10:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能怎样\N{\rEng}What's up with that?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.37,0:11:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎被留堂  好嘛\N{\rEng}Welcome to detention,m'kay?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.12,0:11:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要呆在这\N{\rEng}You're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.84,0:11:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到家长来领你们回去\N{\rEng}Until your parents come and pick you up.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.21,0:11:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,利用这个时间好好学习\N{\rEng}Use your time to study.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.82,0:11:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了\N{\rEng}Oh, sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.84,0:11:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克\N{\rEng}Eric.Hey,Eric.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.28,0:11:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  怎么回事\N{\rEng}Eric,what's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.70,0:11:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都说你故意留堂\N{\rEng}Everyone is start to say You got detention on purpose
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.67,0:11:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃避和温蒂单挑\N{\rEng}To get out of fighting with wendy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.35,0:11:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  荒谬\N{\rEng}What?that's ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.90,0:11:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有人说\N{\rEng}But some people said
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.61,0:11:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在老师桌上拉屎\N{\rEng}You crapped on teacher's desk
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.54,0:11:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就为逃避单挑\N{\rEng}To get out of the fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.37,0:11:35.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是呢\N{\rEng}That's not why i did it!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.67,0:11:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你干嘛在加里森桌上拉屎\N{\rEng}Why did you crap on Garrison's desk.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.40,0:11:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我是硬汉\N{\rEng}Because i'm hardcore.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.01,0:11:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很反叛\N{\rEng}You know.I'm anti-establishment,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.72,0:11:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是这样  伙计\N{\rEng}That's how i roll, dawgs.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.15,0:11:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我经常做这种剽悍的事\N{\rEng}I do hardcore stuff like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.42,0:11:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也这么说\N{\rEng}That's what i said.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.22,0:11:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟外面的人说\N{\rEng}I told everyone outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.70,0:11:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡特曼才不怕和温蒂单挑\N{\rEng}Cartman ain't scared of fighting wendy,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.59,0:11:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是没办法去\N{\rEng}He'd do it if he could.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.14,0:11:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太对了\N{\rEng}Damn straight.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.75,0:11:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是心血来潮\N{\rEng}I just got all punk rock
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.81,0:11:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被留堂而已\N{\rEng}And got detention, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.78,0:11:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是个坏小子\N{\rEng}I'm just a bad dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.49,0:11:55.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好\N{\rEng}Okey,that's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.29,0:11:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们把单挑改到\N{\rEng}Because we moved the fight
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.61,0:11:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天一早进行了\N{\rEng}To first thing tomorrow morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.16,0:11:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上课前\N{\rEng}Before school starts.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.02,0:12:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都会早点来\N{\rEng}Everyone is going to get there early.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.02,0:12:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不用担心会被留堂了\N{\rEng}Cause that way won't matter If you get detention.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.01,0:12:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  给我滚回来  好嘛\N{\rEng}Eric, get your buns back over here.m'key.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.22,0:12:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂说她在上课前一小时会到\N{\rEng}Wendy says she will be here An hour before school starts,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.20,0:12:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天见\N{\rEng}See you in the morning, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.35,0:12:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天早上\N{\rEng}Tomorrow morning,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.10,0:12:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明天早上死定了\N{\rEng}You fucking die tomorrow morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.96,0:12:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-温蒂  -干嘛\N{\rEng}- Wendy! - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.17,0:12:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要跟你谈谈  现在就下来\N{\rEng}We need to talk to you right now!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.86,0:12:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  你在学校欺负小朋友啦\N{\rEng}Wendy, have you been Bullying kids at school?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.68,0:12:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  没有\N{\rEng}What? No!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.85,0:12:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你怎么解释\N{\rEng}Well, do you want to explain
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.83,0:12:46.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个小男生的妈妈\N{\rEng}Why this little boy's mother
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.95,0:12:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来找我们谈话呢\N{\rEng}Had to come talk to us?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.56,0:12:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟这个小男生说\N{\rEng}Did you tell this little boy
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.61,0:12:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要揍他吗\N{\rEng}You were going to beat him up?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.83,0:12:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不明白\N{\rEng}You don't understand
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.78,0:12:57.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说了很难听的话\N{\rEng}He said horrible things.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.13,0:12:59.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实是  我完全道过歉了\N{\rEng}The thing is, I totally said I was sorry,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.87,0:13:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她还是要揍我\N{\rEng}But she still wants to beat me up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.06,0:13:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  不管别人说什么\N{\rEng}Wendy, no matter what a person says,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.11,0:13:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都不能诉诸暴力\N{\rEng}You don't respond with violence.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.53,0:13:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是教过你吗\N{\rEng}Haven't we taught you that?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.38,0:13:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  温蒂\N{\rEng}The thing is wendy,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.92,0:13:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的觉得你很好\N{\rEng}I really think you're awesome,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.57,0:13:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\rEng}And i know,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.11,0:13:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在你眼里只是个小喽罗\N{\rEng}I'm just a nerdy little weakling to you,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.45,0:13:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我想做你的朋友  因为\N{\rEng}But i want to be your friend,because,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.61,0:13:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在学校很少朋友\N{\rEng}I don't have that many friends at school.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.94,0:13:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  你告诉这个小男生\N{\rEng}Wendy, you tell this little boy
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.71,0:13:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会伤害他\N{\rEng}You aren't going to hurt him!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.49,0:13:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  你不\N{\rEng}Mom, you don't...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.31,0:13:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就说  小姑娘\N{\rEng}Now, young lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.84,0:13:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会伤害你\N{\rEng}I'm not going to hurt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.48,0:13:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要是听到你在学校打架\N{\rEng}If there's any word of you fighting at school,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.47,0:13:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就完蛋了  小姑娘  明白了吗\N{\rEng}It's over for you missy, do you understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.21,0:13:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了\N{\rEng}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.58,0:13:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在抱歉  卡特曼夫人\N{\rEng}We're so sorry about this, Mrs.Cartman.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.55,0:13:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  谢谢你们\N{\rEng}Oh, no, thank you so much for your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.11,0:13:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会再有下次了\N{\rEng}It really won't happen again.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.22,0:13:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们太好了\N{\rEng}You're very sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.26,0:13:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再次感谢\N{\rEng}Thank you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.18,0:13:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  小可爱\N{\rEng}Come on, muffin.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.80,0:13:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  妈咪  妈妈  妈妈\N{\rEng}Okay, mommy, ma ma, ma ma.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.28,0:14:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都快开始上课了\N{\rEng}Man, it's almost time for school to start.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.70,0:14:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂还没来\N{\rEng}Wendy still isn't here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.27,0:14:05.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道怎么回事\N{\rEng}Yeah, I don't know what's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.47,0:14:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可来了\N{\rEng}I mean i showed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.53,0:14:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她去哪了\N{\rEng}Where is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.45,0:14:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂为什么没来单挑\N{\rEng}How could wendy not showing up for the fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.49,0:14:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她来了\N{\rEng}Here she comes!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.57,0:14:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  温蒂\N{\rEng}What's up, wendy.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.28,0:14:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为我们要早到单挑的\N{\rEng}I thought we were meeting early to fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.98,0:14:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明知道我不能和你单挑\N{\rEng}You know i can't fight you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.04,0:14:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  你怕了\N{\rEng}Why not? You chicken?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.92,0:14:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咯咯  咯咯  咯咯\N{\rEng}Bwawk bwawk bwawk.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.66,0:14:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能单挑是因为你昨晚\N{\rEng}I can't fight you because you came crying
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.74,0:14:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哭着和你妈来我家\N{\rEng}To my house last night with your mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.71,0:14:26.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可笑  温蒂\N{\rEng}Oh, that's a doozie, wendy,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.88,0:14:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己瞎编乱造\N{\rEng}You come up with that one on your own?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.99,0:14:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对\N{\rEng}Yeah,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.14,0:14:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己瞎编乱造\N{\rEng}You come up with that one on your own?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.36,0:14:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不怕你  开打吧\N{\rEng}I ain't frighten dawg, let's do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.87,0:14:34.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在就开打吧\N{\rEng}let's do it right now,yo'll.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.45,0:14:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快啊  温蒂  踹他屁股\N{\rEng}Come on,wendy kick his ass!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.06,0:14:38.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能\N{\rEng}I can't!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.31,0:14:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\rEng}God dammit,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.01,0:14:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怕了\N{\rEng}She chickened out.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.14,0:14:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早跟你们说了\N{\rEng}Told you guys!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.81,0:14:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真高兴结束了\N{\rEng}Oh, i'm glad that's over with.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.43,0:14:50.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  看是谁躲过一劫了  装逼\N{\rEng}Yeah, guess who dodged a bullet, galahad.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.85,0:14:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都知道\N{\rEng}I always knew deep down
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.70,0:14:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂没这个胆量\N{\rEng}Wendy didn't have any balls.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.99,0:15:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  我们每天都要回收废品\N{\rEng}And so we must all recycle every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.99,0:15:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回收很重要\N{\rEng}Recycling is important.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.51,0:15:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这能拯救我们的地球\N{\rEng}And it will save our planet earth.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.94,0:15:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完毕\N{\rEng}The end.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.59,0:15:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  克莱德\N{\rEng}Very nice, clyde.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.71,0:15:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,课间休息前还能再读一篇报告\N{\rEng}Okay, we have time For one more report before recess,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.21,0:15:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁想来  \N{\rEng}Who would like to go?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.07,0:15:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克\N{\rEng}Okay, eric.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.24,0:15:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\rEng}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.55,0:15:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天的报告\N{\rEng}My report today
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.54,0:15:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有关乳癌宣传的\N{\rEng}Is on breast cancer awareness.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.59,0:15:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得宣传的力度不够\N{\rEng}I do not believe enough is being done,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.30,0:15:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像一些乳癌的受害者\N{\rEng}And like the victims of breast cancer,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.10,0:15:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想吐露一些心声\N{\rEng}There's something I'd like to get off my chest.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.05,0:15:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都要抗争\N{\rEng}We all must fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.84,0:15:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望有一天\N{\rEng}And hopefully one day.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.04,0:15:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咪咪癌能变成遥远的记忆\N{\rEng}Titty cancer will be a distant memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.77,0:15:43.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是个混蛋\N{\rEng}You unbelievable bastard.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.68,0:15:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赢了我  还不收手\N{\rEng}You beat me, but you won't stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.40,0:15:46.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳癌对波兰猴子\N{\rEng}What did the breast cancer
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.57,0:15:48.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了什么呢\N{\rEng}Say to the polish monkey.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.38,0:15:51.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  埃里克  吹牛吹够了\N{\rEng}Okay, eric, that's enough you smart ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.31,0:15:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\rEng}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.71,0:15:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛要这样对我\N{\rEng}Why are you doing this to me?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.05,0:15:55.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么还不善罢甘休\N{\rEng}Why won't you just stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.60,0:15:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂\N{\rEng}Wendy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.80,0:15:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂·泰斯伯格\N{\rEng}Wendy testaburger
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.59,0:15:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请到校长室\N{\rEng}To the principal's office, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.67,0:16:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂·泰斯伯格\N{\rEng}Wendy testaburger
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.38,0:16:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请到校长室\N{\rEng}To the principal's office!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.48,0:16:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天\N{\rEng}God!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.49,0:16:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  我听说你和\N{\rEng}Wendy, I've been hearing rumors of
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.42,0:16:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克·卡特曼要打架\N{\rEng}a fight Between you and eric cartman.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.72,0:16:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  女士  不会打架的\N{\rEng}No, ma'am.there isn't going to be a fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.01,0:16:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  你确定\N{\rEng}Oh, no? Are you sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.34,0:16:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  女士\N{\rEng}Yes, ma'am.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.23,0:16:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂了\N{\rEng}I see.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.92,0:16:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我注意到了你在乳癌\N{\rEng}I noticed all the things you've done
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.37,0:16:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宣传月所做的一切\N{\rEng}For breast cancer awareness month.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.61,0:16:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我曾是乳癌患者吗\N{\rEng}Did you know I'm a breast cancer survivor?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.44,0:16:34.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士\N{\rEng}Ma'am?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.63,0:16:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,7年前  我确诊患有乳癌\N{\rEng}I was diagnosed seven years ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.16,0:16:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,癌症是纯粹的恶魔\N{\rEng}Cancer is pure evil,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.18,0:16:41.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它是个需要被摧毁的\N{\rEng}It's a fat little lump that needs to be
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.47,0:16:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小肥肉\N{\rEng}Destroyed.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.93,0:16:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当癌症出现时\N{\rEng}When there is a cancer,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.44,0:16:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定要与其抗争\N{\rEng}You have to fight it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.84,0:16:51.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能跟癌症理论\N{\rEng}You can't reason with cancer,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.50,0:16:53.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能指望它自己离开\N{\rEng}You can't wish it away.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.41,0:16:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,癌症不遵守规则\N{\rEng}Cancer doesn't play by the rules,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.70,0:16:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也可以不遵守\N{\rEng}So neither can you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.00,0:17:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父母说如果我打架\N{\rEng}My parents said that if i fight--.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.46,0:17:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也不能听从其他人\N{\rEng}And you can't listen to What anybody else tells you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.10,0:17:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得愿意放弃一切\N{\rEng}You have to be willing to give up everything
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.11,0:17:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为癌症会夺走一切\N{\rEng}Because the cancer will take everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.54,0:17:13.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂了吗\N{\rEng}Do you understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.27,0:17:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂了  女士\N{\rEng}Yes, ma'am!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.09,0:17:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了癌症  一定要抗争\N{\rEng}When you have cancer, you fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.20,0:17:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为不管你能不能战胜它\N{\rEng}Because it doesn't matter If you beat it or not.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.22,0:17:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都不能让那堆小肥肉\N{\rEng}You refuse to let that
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.99,0:17:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你觉得自己无能为力\N{\rEng}Fat little lump make you feel powerless.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.41,0:17:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要单挑了\N{\rEng}She's gonna fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.68,0:17:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂现在就要和卡特曼单挑\N{\rEng}Wendy's gonna fight cartman right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.88,0:17:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.07,0:17:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往前跑  克雷格\N{\rEng}Go deep craig.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.20,0:17:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样  白痴\N{\rEng}Not that dude, retard.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.84,0:17:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她来了\N{\rEng}She's coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.46,0:17:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  走开\N{\rEng}Butters,just get out of there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.48,0:17:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂来和你单挑了\N{\rEng}But wendy's coming to fight you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.01,0:18:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  开始啦\N{\rEng}Oh, boy, here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.79,0:18:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于开始了\N{\rEng}About freaking time.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.53,0:18:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  开打吧\N{\rEng}All right. Let's do it!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.30,0:18:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\rEng}What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.29,0:18:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂  别忘了\N{\rEng}Wendy, don't forget
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.45,0:18:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会向我妈告发你的\N{\rEng}I'll tell my mom on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.13,0:18:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管\N{\rEng}I don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.04,0:18:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,课间休息快结束了\N{\rEng}Recess is almost over,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.20,0:18:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道够不够时间\N{\rEng}I don't know if there's really time.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.77,0:18:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴  快打吧\N{\rEng}Shut up and fight!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.04,0:18:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  来吧  温蒂\N{\rEng}All right, fine, wendy,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.20,0:18:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你单挑\N{\rEng}I'll fight you.you big buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.12,0:19:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,揍死他  温蒂\N{\rEng}Fuck him up, wendy!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.85,0:20:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温蒂\N{\rEng}Wendy?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.10,0:20:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打完了\N{\rEng}I'm finished.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.14,0:20:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来人  快通知校长\N{\rEng}Somebody, somebody call the principal!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.76,0:20:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们什么都不用说\N{\rEng}You don't have to say anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.34,0:20:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都知道\N{\rEng}I know how it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.38,0:20:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不再是酷小孩了\N{\rEng}I'm no longer the cool kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.95,0:20:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们现在都觉得我是基佬\N{\rEng}Now you all think i'm a fag.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.17,0:20:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的校园生活玩完了\N{\rEng}My school life is over cause now
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.10,0:20:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你们都觉得我不酷了\N{\rEng}All the guys don't think i'm cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.36,0:20:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  我们从来不觉得你很酷\N{\rEng}Dude, we never thought you were cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.32,0:20:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是真的\N{\rEng}That's not true.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.36,0:20:49.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们只是嘴上说说\N{\rEng}You're just saying that.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.61,0:20:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  真的  我们一直觉得你很逊\N{\rEng}No, really, we've always thought you suck.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.97,0:20:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  什么也没改变\N{\rEng}Yeah, nothing's changed.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.21,0:20:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们对你的看法\N{\rEng}Our opinion of you
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.86,0:20:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不能再低了\N{\rEng}Can't possibly go any lower.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.41,0:21:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这么说只是想安慰我\N{\rEng}You're just saying that To make me feel better.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.23,0:21:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是真的  我们一直讨厌你\N{\rEng}No, it's true. We've always hated you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.66,0:21:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对\N{\rEng}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.96,0:21:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们别安慰我了\N{\rEng}Don't try and make me feel better, you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.19,0:21:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等  等等\N{\rEng}Wait, wait a minute,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.60,0:21:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们为什么会说这些来安慰我\N{\rEng}Why would you guys be saying stuff To make me feel better?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.68,0:21:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非  你们确实觉得我很酷\N{\rEng}Unless, Unless you do think I'm cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.24,0:21:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.13,0:21:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都在安慰我\N{\rEng}If you're all trying to make me feel better
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.10,0:21:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们肯定还喜欢我\N{\rEng}Then you must still like me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.26,0:21:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还一直在担心\N{\rEng}I've been so worried about
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.70,0:21:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要是被女生撂倒\N{\rEng}What you guys were going to think of
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.29,0:21:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们会怎么看我\N{\rEng}Me getting beat up by a girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.31,0:21:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来不管怎样  你们都觉得我很酷\N{\rEng}It turns out you think I'm cool no matter what!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.40,0:21:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  松了口气\N{\rEng}Oh, god, what a relief!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.84,0:21:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\rEng}Yea!
