[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由TimeM生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.net
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayDepth: 0
PlayResX: 1916
PlayResY: 1076
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 2
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H19000000,&H000E0300,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,2,2,134,120,68,1
Style: eng,Microsoft YaHei,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,26,1
Style: Top,微软雅黑,10,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Git,Comic Sans MS,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Chn,微软雅黑,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Eng,Comic Sans MS,60,&H002AF7FF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.00,0:00:11.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm going down to south park\N gonna have myself a time 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.85,0:00:15.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Friendly faces everywhere\N humble folks without temptation 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.13,0:00:17.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Going down to south park\N gonna leave my woes behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.52,0:00:21.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ample parking day or night\N people shouting howdy neighbor
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.76,0:00:24.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heading on out to south park\N gonna see if I can't unwind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.34,0:00:28.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I like girls with big vaginas\N I like girls with big fat titties
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.41,0:00:31.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.48,0:21:45.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译制作\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}YYeTs人人影视字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.48,0:21:46.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}DayDay
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.48,0:21:46.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0020,,{\1c&HFDC282&}校对\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Foresee Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.48,0:21:47.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0020,,{\1c&HFDC282&}后期\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}csbeyond
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.49,0:21:48.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0060,,{\1c&HFDC282&}总监\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.00,0:00:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0150,,{\1c&HFDC282&}《南方公园》第12季  第10集\N{\rEng}South Park Season 12 Episode 10
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.00,0:00:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0100,,"流行病(上)"\N{\rEng}"Pandemic (part 1)"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.50,0:00:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞不懂  肯尼\N{\rEng}I don't get it, Kenny. 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.83,0:00:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛买剃须刀和剃须膏\N{\rEng}Why did you buy razors and shaving cream?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.68,0:00:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我要给我蛋蛋刮毛\N{\rEng}'Cuz, dude, I'm gonna shave my balls.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.75,0:00:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刮蛋毛  你干嘛刮蛋毛\N{\rEng}Shave your balls? Why would you shave your balls?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.50,0:00:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为女生们喜欢刮过的蛋蛋\N{\rEng}Because girls like shaved balls.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.29,0:00:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-女生喜欢  -对  她们喜欢\N{\rEng}- Girls like shaved balls? - Yes, they do.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.69,0:00:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么女生要看你的蛋啊\N{\rEng}What girl is gonna see your balls?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.48,0:00:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道\N{\rEng}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.49,0:00:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  又有一支\N{\rEng}Oh, Jesus, there's another one!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.37,0:01:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又一支排箫乐队\N{\rEng}Another pan flute band.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.04,0:01:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们注意到了吗\N{\rEng}Have you guys noticed there's
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.16,0:01:07.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种乐队最近到处都是\N{\rEng}bands like this everywhere you go lately?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.00,0:01:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  我昨天在丹佛\N{\rEng}Yeah, I saw like three of those bands 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.66,0:01:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到有三支\N{\rEng}down in Denver yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的烂音乐听起来都差不多\N{\rEng}All their crappy music sounds the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.39,0:01:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真受不了走到哪都听到这种音乐\N{\rEng}I'm so sick of hearing this music everywhere I go!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.66,0:01:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼好像蛮喜欢的\N{\rEng}I think Kenny likes it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.67,0:01:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要回家吃晚餐了  -我也要\N{\rEng}- I gotta get home for dinner. - Yeah, me too.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.25,0:01:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐\N{\rEng}God!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.18,0:01:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都他妈给我停下\N{\rEng}Shut up already!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.72,0:01:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要走了  兄弟们再见\N{\rEng}I'm outta here. See you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.54,0:01:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚  旅游频道带您游览伦敦\N{\rEng}Tonight, the Travel Channel takes you to London!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.20,0:01:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伦敦有大家喜欢的东西\N{\rEng}London has something for everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.23,0:01:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名胜  剧院  还有出色的街头表演者\N{\rEng}Sights. Theater. And wonderful street performers.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.48,0:01:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-伦敦也有他们  -孩子们  开饭了\N{\rEng}- They're in London, too? - Hey, time for dinner, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.75,0:01:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好了  孩子们  开动吧  -爸呢\N{\rEng}- All right, kids. Dig in. - Where's Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.39,0:02:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在楼上给你浴缸里的爷爷录像\N{\rEng}He's upstairs videotaping your grandfather in the bathtub.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.63,0:02:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\rEng}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.41,0:02:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你爸一拿到那白痴录像机\N{\rEng}Because ever since your father got that stupid video camera,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.10,0:02:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就觉得应该记录家庭每天的点滴\N{\rEng}he thinks he has to film everything the family does.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.49,0:02:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看这边\N{\rEng}All right, here we are!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.02,0:02:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马什家又聚在一起吃晚餐咯\N{\rEng}Marsh family gathered for another dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.44,0:02:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  我们吃晚餐的录像够多了\N{\rEng}Randy, we have plenty of video of us eating dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.80,0:02:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是谢莉  你的晚餐吃得开心吗\N{\rEng}There's Shelley. You excited about dinner, Shelley?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.29,0:02:19.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关掉它  爸爸\N{\rEng}Turn it off, Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.82,0:02:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看  斯坦在吃土豆\N{\rEng}Oh, look! Stan's eating a tater tot.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.89,0:02:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朝镜头挥挥手  斯坦\N{\rEng}Wave to the camera, Stan!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.70,0:02:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苍了个天的\N{\rEng}Jesus Christ!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.11,0:02:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷耶  有一支秘鲁排箫乐队\N{\rEng}Oh, neat-o! It's one of those Peruvian pan flute bands!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.60,0:02:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯坦  出去跟他们站一起  我拍一下\N{\rEng}Stan, go out and stand with 'em. I can get a shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.50,0:02:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要用这张卡  叫凯尔后退七步\N{\rEng}I will play this card to move Kyle back seven spaces.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.63,0:02:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚蛋咯  凯尔\N{\rEng}Screw you, Kyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.79,0:02:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到你了  肯尼\N{\rEng}And all right, your turn,Kenny.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.95,0:02:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大伙  快听我说\N{\rEng}You guys! You guys, check this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.20,0:02:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚我家门外有一支排箫乐队\N{\rEng}I saw another Peruvian flute band outside my house last night!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.08,0:02:56.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎样\N{\rEng}So?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.87,0:02:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我就坐着看了一下他们\N{\rEng}So I just sat there and watched them for a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.97,0:03:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜猜他们用那些烂CD赚了多少钱\N{\rEng}Guess how much money they made selling their crappy CDs?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.52,0:03:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-多少  -200多块耶\N{\rEng}- How much? - Over $200 bucks!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.26,0:03:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-200美金  -你说真的吗\N{\rEng}- $200? - Really, are you sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.42,0:03:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  我开始觉得\N{\rEng}Yeah dude, I'm starting to
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.38,0:03:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是世界上最容易干的活了\N{\rEng}realize it's like the easiest job in the world,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.22,0:03:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也能干\N{\rEng}you know? I mean we could do that!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.79,0:03:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-组个排箫乐队吗  -对啊  不行吗\N{\rEng}- Become a Peruvian flute band? - Yeah! Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.30,0:03:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄点乐器和服装来\N{\rEng}We get some instruments and some costumes
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.86,0:03:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己在电脑里\N{\rEng}and then make some crappy 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.38,0:03:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,录些排箫音乐\N{\rEng}pan flute music CDs on my computer.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.07,0:03:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  \N{\rEng}Oh, my God! 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.53,0:03:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们他妈的要赚大钱了\N{\rEng}We're gonna make so much fucking money, you guys!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.12,0:03:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是嘛\N{\rEng}Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.04,0:03:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去哪弄钱来\N{\rEng}But where are we gonna get
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.36,0:03:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买服装和乐器呢\N{\rEng}the money to buy costumes and instruments?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.06,0:03:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格  老弟  你过得好吗\N{\rEng}Craig, dude. How you doing, bro?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.72,0:03:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还好  -不错嘛  真好\N{\rEng}- Fine. - Cool. Awesome!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.63,0:03:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格  我记得你说\N{\rEng}Craig, remember you were telling us
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.25,0:03:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你奶奶给过你100块钱过生日\N{\rEng}how your grandma gave you $100 bucks for your birthday?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.23,0:03:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.60,0:03:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格  \N{\rEng}Craig, 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.38,0:03:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想不想让那100块变成1000块\N{\rEng}how would you like to turn that $100 into $1,000?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.89,0:03:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来吧克雷格  坐吧  欢迎加入\N{\rEng}Come on in, Craig. Have a seat! Welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.44,0:03:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们想干嘛\N{\rEng}What do you guys want?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.63,0:04:00.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格  我们相中你加入我们的排箫队\N{\rEng}Craig, we have chosen you to join our Peruvian flute band!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.95,0:04:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好耶  克雷格\N{\rEng}All right, Craig!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.30,0:04:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说满大街都是的那种吹箫乐队吗\N{\rEng}You mean like those guys you see at all the tourist spots?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.63,0:04:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们能满大街自有原因  克雷格\N{\rEng}There's a reason they're everywhere, Craig.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.98,0:04:08.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他们很能赚钱\N{\rEng}Because they make bank.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.45,0:04:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要你的钱来买乐器和录CD\N{\rEng}We just need your money to buy instruments and make CDs.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.71,0:04:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要一个下午\N{\rEng}And we'll double your money 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.61,0:04:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就能赚双倍  克雷格\N{\rEng}in one afternoon, Craig.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.90,0:04:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们从来不跟我玩\N{\rEng}You guys never hang out with me, 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.47,0:04:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也从来不邀请我\N{\rEng}you never invite me to do stuff,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.97,0:04:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在却让我跟你们组乐队\N{\rEng}but now you want me to be in a band with you
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.61,0:04:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为我奶奶给了我100块\N{\rEng}because my grandma gave me $100.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.15,0:04:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格  别给脸不要脸\N{\rEng}Craig, don't be an asshole.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.84,0:04:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去拿钱\N{\rEng}I'll go get the money.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.52,0:04:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  大家按排练的那样做\N{\rEng}All right, guys. Just like we rehearsed it!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.15,0:04:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格准备好没\N{\rEng}You ready, Craig?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.04,0:04:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好嘞  开演\N{\rEng}All right, let's jam!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.36,0:04:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  二\N{\rEng}And a one, and a two, and a...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.90,0:04:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  好有文化气息的音乐\N{\rEng}Wow, that's such cultural music.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.79,0:04:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  很有文化感 \N{\rEng}Very cultural, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.53,0:04:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请买张我们的CD吧\N{\rEng}Por favor, buy our CDs de musica!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.00,0:04:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[草泥马兄弟出品  "心情风景"]
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.41,0:04:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢\N{\rEng}Gracias!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.85,0:05:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多有文化感啊\N{\rEng}How cultural!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.72,0:05:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽翻了\N{\rEng}This is awesome!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.65,0:05:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到没  克雷格\N{\rEng}You see, Craig?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.11,0:05:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不能在这演  我们先来的\N{\rEng}Hey, you guys can't play here! We were here first!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.61,0:05:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里禁止演出  滚开[西语]\N{\rEng}No trabajar aqui! Vaya!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.01,0:05:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这条步行街禁止你们奏乐[西语]\N{\rEng}No playa la musica en la promenade! No es bueno!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.87,0:05:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们的地盘  懂吗\N{\rEng}This is our Peruvian flute band's turf. You got that?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.05,0:05:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我靠  -不准吹\N{\rEng}- Goddammit! - No! No es bueno!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.96,0:05:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弟兄们  走吧\N{\rEng}Come on, guys!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.67,0:05:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苍你妈个天的\N{\rEng}Jesus Christ!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.97,0:06:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不许在这里演出\N{\rEng}No! No es bueno! No trabajar aqui!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.81,0:06:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[美国国土安全部]
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.21,0:06:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士们  先生们  我们国家和全世界\N{\rEng}Ladies and gentlemen,our nation and our world is facing
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.14,0:06:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在面临着严重的经济衰退和生态危机\N{\rEng}an economic and ecological crisis of disastrous proportions.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.92,0:06:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的当然是指秘鲁排箫乐队\N{\rEng}I'm talking of course about Peruvian flute bands.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.70,0:06:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红色区域代表着\N{\rEng}The red dots indicate where
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.06,0:06:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘鲁排箫队的高度密集区\N{\rEng}the highest concentration of Peruvian bands are.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.92,0:06:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们遍布全球  集中在游客和购物者密集处\N{\rEng}All over the world, wherever there are tourists or shoppers,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.60,0:06:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平均每平方公里\N{\rEng}there are now on average
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.10,0:06:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就有65支排箫队\N{\rEng}65 Peruvian flute bands per square kilometer.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.82,0:06:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上将\N{\rEng}General?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.93,0:06:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法国  日本  以及\N{\rEng}France, Japan, and the
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.22,0:06:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美国北部  近来受灾最重\N{\rEng}northeastern US are currently the hardest hit.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.69,0:06:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫无疑问\N{\rEng}Make no mistake...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.29,0:06:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一种吹箫流行病\N{\rEng}This is a pan flute epidemic.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.14,0:06:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流行病\N{\rEng}A pandemic?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.16,0:06:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚洲有三个国家  欧洲有七个\N{\rEng}Three countries in Asia, and seven in Europe
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.29,0:06:48.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经向我们发出求助\N{\rEng}have already asked for our help
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.38,0:06:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请求帮他们驱赶秘鲁排箫乐队\N{\rEng}in getting rid of their Peruvian flute bands.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.41,0:06:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要调集各种有效资源来解决该问题\N{\rEng}We will need every resource available to see this through.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.42,0:06:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问  只是援助其他国家吗\N{\rEng}Excuse me, but aid other countries?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.78,0:06:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参议员\N{\rEng}Senator?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.76,0:06:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我直言\N{\rEng}With all due respect, 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.93,0:07:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得要首先处理好本国领土内的排箫队\N{\rEng}we need to be dealing with our own pan flute bands.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.38,0:07:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让其他国家自生自灭去吧\N{\rEng}Let other countries fend for themselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.12,0:07:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个没心肝的\N{\rEng}You heartless bastard.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.30,0:07:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是建立在自由和廉正基础上的国度\N{\rEng}This country was founded on beliefs in freedom and integrity.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.45,0:07:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们决不袖手旁观\N{\rEng}And we will not sit back and do nothing
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.59,0:07:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决不容许贫困国家\N{\rEng}while less fortunate countries 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.85,0:07:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被排箫乐队恣意践踏\N{\rEng}are ravaged by Peruvian flute bands.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.60,0:07:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听清楚没\N{\rEng}Is that clear?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.71,0:07:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为国安部的领导\N{\rEng}As director of Homeland Security,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.10,0:07:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由我掌控军队\N{\rEng}I am taking control of the military
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.54,0:07:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直至此危机平息\N{\rEng}until the crisis is contained.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.69,0:07:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行动\N{\rEng}Go, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.18,0:08:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活该了吧  混蛋\N{\rEng}Serves you right, assholes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.82,0:08:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我们走 \N{\rEng}Let's go! Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.31,0:08:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边还有一支\N{\rEng}One more over here!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.71,0:08:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他们带走\N{\rEng}Let's go get 'em out!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.61,0:08:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清场了  快走\N{\rEng}Clear out. Move!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.41,0:08:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位听着  现在是国安部行动  上\N{\rEng}This is a Homeland Security operation, people. Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.22,0:08:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  放开我\N{\rEng}Hey, back off!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.52,0:08:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确保收缴所有排箫音乐CD\N{\rEng}Make sure all pan flute music CDs are contained.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.06,0:08:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是莎朗和谢莉  她们在看电视\N{\rEng}There's Sharon and Shelley. They're watching some television.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.45,0:08:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向镜头招手  谢莉\N{\rEng}Wave to the camera, Shelley!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.23,0:08:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在看什么呢\N{\rEng}What are you watching, guys?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.99,0:08:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新闻\N{\rEng}The news.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.58,0:08:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在看新闻\N{\rEng}We're watching the news.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.58,0:08:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我们客厅的电视机\N{\rEng}That's the TV in our living room.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.07,0:08:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在还在放广告\N{\rEng}Still showing commercials right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.81,0:08:43.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得电视怎么样啊  谢莉\N{\rEng}What you think about the television, Shelley?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.01,0:08:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新闻开始了\N{\rEng}The news is starting!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.14,0:08:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,政府解除秘鲁排箫队危机的行动\N{\rEng}The government efforts to stop the Peruvian flute band crisis
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.17,0:08:51.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已进入第三天\N{\rEng}are now in their third day.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.67,0:08:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全球各大城市里\N{\rEng}In cities all over the world,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.15,0:08:55.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排箫乐队已被遣散并隔离\N{\rEng}flute bands have been removed and quarantined,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.77,0:08:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但依有大量残留\N{\rEng}but more may still be out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.70,0:08:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国土安全部要求\N{\rEng}Homeland Security is requesting
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.34,0:09:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如有看到秘鲁排箫队  请勿靠近\N{\rEng}that if you see a Peruvian flute band, do not approach it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.31,0:09:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记下他们出没的地点\N{\rEng}Mark down the flute band's location
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.10,0:09:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在任何情况下都千万别买他们的CD\N{\rEng}and do not under any circumstances, buy their CDs.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.73,0:09:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排箫队现已被控制住\N{\rEng}The flute bands that have been contained
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.59,0:09:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并正押往迈阿密隔离区\N{\rEng}are being taken to a quarantine area in Miami.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.38,0:09:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[秘鲁排箫乐队收容所]
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.36,0:09:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  请问\N{\rEng}Excuse us. Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.95,0:09:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  长官\N{\rEng}Excuse me, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.51,0:09:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官  一定是误会了\N{\rEng}Sir, there's been a misunderstanding.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.13,0:09:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能跟您谈谈吗\N{\rEng}Could I talk to you for a minute?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.53,0:09:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官  我们能跟您谈一下吗\N{\rEng}Sir, sir, could we talk to you for just a second?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.53,0:09:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站回去  我不会买你们的烂CD的\N{\rEng}Get back! I'm not buying any of your damn CDs!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.72,0:09:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的  长官  天大的误会啊\N{\rEng}No, sir, there's been a big misunderstanding.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.79,0:09:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们其实不是秘鲁\N{\rEng}We actually aren't a Peruvian--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.79,0:09:46.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了今天不会买你们的烂CD的\N{\rEng}I said I'm not buying any goddamn CDs today!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.62,0:09:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂没有\N{\rEng}You got that?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.39,0:09:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真受不了\N{\rEng}I'm sick of it!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.99,0:09:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官  要不要买张CD[西语]\N{\rEng}Comprar CD la musica?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.66,0:09:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  他被打死了\N{\rEng}Jesus Christ! He shot that guy!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.95,0:10:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"嘿  克雷格"\N{\rEng}"Hey, Craig."
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.41,0:10:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"你还记得你奶奶"\N{\rEng}"You know that money your grandma"
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.60,0:10:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"给你过生日的钱吗"\N{\rEng}"gave you for your birthday?"
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.06,0:10:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"你想投资在秘鲁排箫乐队里吗"\N{\rEng}"How would you like to invest in a Peruvian flute band?"
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.24,0:10:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"你下午就能成倍地赚回来"\N{\rEng}"You can double your money in one afternoon."
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.57,0:10:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"别闹了  克雷格  别给脸不要"\N{\rEng}Come on, Craig. Don't be an asshole.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.10,0:10:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了  秘鲁排箫乐队成员们\N{\rEng}Attention, Peruvian flute bands...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.59,0:10:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了  秘鲁排箫乐队成员们[西语]\N{\rEng}Attenciones, bandas de flauta Peru.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.05,0:10:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你们能耐心合作\N{\rEng}We appreciate your cooperation and patience.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.25,0:10:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你们能耐心合作[西语]\N{\rEng}Cooporation y paciencia es apreciado!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.21,0:10:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天  你们就会上船\N{\rEng}Tomorrow, you will be boarding ships.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.62,0:10:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天  你们就会上船[西语]\N{\rEng}Manana, sera el ambarque de barcos!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.92,0:10:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你们送回关塔那摩湾\N{\rEng}Which will take you to Guantanamo Bay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.57,0:10:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你们送回关塔那摩[西语]\N{\rEng}Que le llevara a bahia Guantanamo!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.88,0:10:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们将在那里安享余生\N{\rEng}Where you will spend the rest of your lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.61,0:10:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们将在那里安享余生  谢谢[西语]\N{\rEng}Donde pasar el resto de sus vidas! Gracias!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.37,0:11:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关塔那摩湾\N{\rEng}Guantanamo Bay?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.77,0:11:03.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可不能去关塔那摩湾\N{\rEng}We can't go to Guantanamo Bay!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.01,0:11:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心\N{\rEng}Don't worry, you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.14,0:11:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢说我们父母\N{\rEng}I'm sure our parents are
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.23,0:11:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在一定找我们快找疯了\N{\rEng}freaking out right now trying to find us.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.21,0:11:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  塔克先生和夫人\N{\rEng}Please, Mr. And Mrs. Tucker,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.78,0:11:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们孩子走失前是跟你家克雷格一起玩的\N{\rEng}our boys were last seen hanging out with your son Craig.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.75,0:11:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们知道他们会去哪里吗\N{\rEng}Do you have any idea where they could have gone?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.88,0:11:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  我说了这一点也不像克雷格\N{\rEng}No! I'm telling you this isn't like Craig at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.62,0:11:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我真的好担心  -警察那边有消息吗\N{\rEng}- I'm really worried! - You've checked with the police?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.80,0:11:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  孩子们好像人间蒸发了\N{\rEng}Nobody knows anything. It's like the boys just vanished.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.01,0:11:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他孩子们都没有见过他们  自从...\N{\rEng}None of the other kids have seen them since the...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.73,0:11:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  你还拍\N{\rEng}Randy, will you put that thing down?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.68,0:11:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你发什么神经啊  我们儿子都丢了\N{\rEng}What is wrong with you? Our son is missing!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.41,0:11:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也很担心他的  莎朗\N{\rEng}Hey, I'm worried about him too, Sharon.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.25,0:11:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就别发神经了  来帮忙\N{\rEng}Well, then stop being an idiot and help!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.31,0:11:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能孩子们都离家出走了\N{\rEng}Maybe the boys all ran away.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.43,0:11:41.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的孩子有没有出现过悲伤情绪\N{\rEng}Were any of your boys upset about anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.46,0:11:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只知道他们是跟克雷格玩\N{\rEng}All we know is they were seen hanging out
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.31,0:11:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是现在就走丢了\N{\rEng}with Craig and now they're gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.51,0:11:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才叫凯尔不许跟那小子玩\N{\rEng}This is exactly why I've told Kyle not to hang around that boy!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.23,0:11:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话什么意思\N{\rEng}What is that supposed to mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.83,0:11:50.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实在的  塔克夫人\N{\rEng}To be honest, Mrs. Tucker,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.15,0:11:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们觉得克雷格会教坏我们孩子\N{\rEng}we think Craig is a bad influence on our boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.91,0:11:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我说清楚\N{\rEng}Now wait just a minute!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.46,0:11:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  你儿子有问题\N{\rEng}I'm just saying that your son has some problems.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.68,0:11:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁家孩子没问题\N{\rEng}Like every kid doesn't have some problems!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.44,0:12:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然是克雷格把他们卷入麻烦里了\N{\rEng}Obviously Craig has gotten them into some kind of trouble!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.77,0:12:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天哪  -这太好玩了\N{\rEng}- Oh, my God! - Oh, this is good!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.62,0:12:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是无理取闹\N{\rEng}That's not ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.65,0:12:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官  好消息  看来我们成功了\N{\rEng}Sir, good news. Looks like we did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.09,0:12:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各大城市都是零秘鲁排箫乐队报告  \N{\rEng}Every major city is reporting zero Peruvian flute bands. 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.76,0:12:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们被彻底清除了\N{\rEng}We got 'em all.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.02,0:12:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好啦  成功啦  感谢上帝\N{\rEng}All right! We did it! Thank God!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.96,0:12:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静  各位  革命尚未成功\N{\rEng}Calm down, people. We still have work to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.67,0:12:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要端掉他们的老窝\N{\rEng}We have to take out the place these flute bands came from,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.49,0:12:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样他们就无法卷土重来\N{\rEng}so they never come again.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.16,0:12:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不知道他们是从哪里来的  长官\N{\rEng}We don't know where they came from, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.47,0:12:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们查过了  但查不出来\N{\rEng}We've been researching, but we can't figure it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.43,0:12:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动脑子想想  白痴\N{\rEng}Well, think about it, idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.25,0:12:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘鲁的排箫乐队还能从哪来\N{\rEng}Where else would Peruvian flute bands come from?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.92,0:12:37.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乐队名里不就有国家名吗\N{\rEng}The country is in the name!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.68,0:12:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  长官  我们查过了整张地图\N{\rEng}No, sir, we checked the entire map.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.86,0:12:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有叫秘[mi]鲁的国家\N{\rEng}There isn't a country called "Peruvian" Anywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.73,0:12:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是秘[mi]鲁  白痴  \N{\rEng}Not "Peruvian", retards. 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.59,0:12:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是秘[bi]鲁\N{\rEng}Peru!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.52,0:12:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这里\N{\rEng}It's right here!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.23,0:12:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘[bi]鲁\N{\rEng}Peru.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.92,0:12:50.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们要计划一举灭掉秘鲁\N{\rEng}Now I want a plan in place to take Peru out once and for all.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.44,0:12:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有这个必要吗  长官\N{\rEng}Is that really necessary, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.81,0:12:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有点极端吧  -就是\N{\rEng}- It seems a little extreme. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.59,0:12:59.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不把他们斩草除根\N{\rEng}Peruvian flute bands will never stop annoying us
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.99,0:13:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就会一直来骚扰我们\N{\rEng}unless they are stopped at the source!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.86,0:13:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官  快来\N{\rEng}Sir, you better come quick.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.53,0:13:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们抓了一个想逃跑的排箫乐队\N{\rEng}One of the pan flute bands was caught trying to escape.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.52,0:13:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到没  真可恶\N{\rEng}You see? Goddammit!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.76,0:13:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"草泥马兄弟出品  心情风景"\N{\rEng}"The Llama Brothers. Tapas and moodscapes."
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.62,0:13:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,误会了  长官\N{\rEng}This is a mistake, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.68,0:13:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是真的秘鲁排箫乐队\N{\rEng}We aren't really a Peruvian flute band.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.45,0:13:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  你们也不过是在商业中心演奏排箫\N{\rEng}Right. You just play pan flute music at the mall
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.91,0:13:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你们的草泥马卖卖CD\N{\rEng}and sell CDs of you with an llama 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.78,0:13:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你们并非秘鲁排箫乐队  是吧\N{\rEng}but you're not a Peruvian flute band.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.50,0:13:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还是孩子\N{\rEng}We're just kids, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.24,0:13:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只想赚点外快\N{\rEng}We were just trying to make some money.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.56,0:13:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想家了\N{\rEng}We just want to go home!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.96,0:13:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官  求您了  \N{\rEng}Sir, please. I'm supposed to get laid 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.01,0:13:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来要在周六破处的\N{\rEng}for the first time on Saturday.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.30,0:13:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是在哪个旅游点演奏的\N{\rEng}Which tourist location were they playing at?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.52,0:13:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科罗拉多的一个户外购物商场\N{\rEng}An outdoor mall in Colorado.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.58,0:13:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就是从科罗拉多来的\N{\rEng}Look, we're from Colorado.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.30,0:13:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土生土长美国人\N{\rEng} We grew up in the United States!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.12,0:13:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们说英语  -我们是白种人\N{\rEng}- We speak English! - And we're white!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.10,0:13:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们出去说\N{\rEng}Let me talk to you guys out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.41,0:13:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你怎么想  -我也不知道  长官\N{\rEng}- What do you think? - I don't know what to make of it, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.43,0:13:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这没有先例啊\N{\rEng}It's like nothing I've ever seen before.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.51,0:13:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很明显他们是排箫队  不过又不是\N{\rEng}Clearly, they are a Peruvian flute band and yet they aren't.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.48,0:13:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们像其他人一样奏排箫音乐\N{\rEng}They play pan flute music like the others,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.72,0:14:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他们的言行\N{\rEng}but they talk and act like...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.60,0:14:02.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-跟我们一样  -没错\N{\rEng}- one of us. - I agree.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.06,0:14:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们很明显是混血的\N{\rEng}They are obviously some kind of hybrid.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.01,0:14:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混血儿  怎么可能\N{\rEng}A hybrid? How is that possible?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.61,0:14:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是秘鲁乐队跟我国女子的结晶\N{\rEng}Perhaps a Peruvian flute band mated with one of our females.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.19,0:14:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道\N{\rEng}Who knows?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.96,0:14:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  既然如此\N{\rEng}Well however, they came to be,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.41,0:14:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们也算是我们唯一的救命稻草了\N{\rEng}they're about the only piece of good luck we've had.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.55,0:14:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官\N{\rEng}Sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.43,0:14:19.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们真的是我们所说的混血\N{\rEng}If they are the hybrid we're talking about,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.08,0:14:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们便可一劳永逸地除掉秘鲁了\N{\rEng}then they could be our way of taking out Peru once and for all.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.86,0:14:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们知道为什么\N{\rEng}Do you guys know why nobody
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.11,0:14:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校里没人喜欢跟你们玩吗\N{\rEng}else at school likes hanging out with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.27,0:14:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你们老是在干这种事\N{\rEng}Because you're always doing stuff like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.19,0:14:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们总会想出\N{\rEng}You're always coming up with some 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.43,0:14:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一些馊主意\N{\rEng}stupid idea to do something
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.59,0:14:38.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后又事与愿违  然后就被遣送出国\N{\rEng}and then it backfires and then you end up in a foreign country
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.32,0:14:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者丢出外太空什么的\N{\rEng}or in outer space or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.33,0:14:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以没人愿意跟你们玩\N{\rEng}That's why no one likes hanging out with you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.87,0:14:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是消极到家了  克雷格\N{\rEng}You're being extremely negative, Craig.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.44,0:14:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  干脆这样吧\N{\rEng}All right, here's the deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.99,0:14:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你们是不是自己人\N{\rEng}Maybe you are on our side and maybe you aren't,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.14,0:14:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果你们能协助我们\N{\rEng}but if you help us,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.32,0:14:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们就送你们回家  -怎么协助\N{\rEng}- We'll get you home. - Help you how?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.23,0:14:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们可以潜入秘鲁排箫乐队中\N{\rEng}You are able to walk amongst the Peruvian flute bands.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.53,0:14:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们对你们没有戒心\N{\rEng}They see you as one of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.92,0:15:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会把你们送去他们的首都\N{\rEng}We are going to send you to their capital.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.94,0:15:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能让我们回家  长官\N{\rEng}Can we please just go home, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.54,0:15:04.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还不知道你们是敌是友\N{\rEng}We still don't know who's side you're on!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.87,0:15:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们肯做  我们才会清楚\N{\rEng}You do this and we'll know.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.49,0:15:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们明早动身\N{\rEng}You leave for Peru in the morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.40,0:15:10.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不要去秘鲁\N{\rEng}No. No, I'm not going to Peru!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.25,0:15:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不要去秘鲁  -凯尔  冷静点\N{\rEng}- Not Peru! - Kyle, calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.02,0:15:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我不能去的  斯坦\N{\rEng}You know I can't go there, Stan!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.01,0:15:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有个朋友在秘鲁被爆过菊\N{\rEng}One of our friends was raped in Peru.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.77,0:15:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是片伤心地\N{\rEng}It was very traumatic.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.43,0:15:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们别无选择\N{\rEng}You don't have a choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.36,0:15:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不去秘鲁\N{\rEng}Either you go to Peru,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.84,0:15:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不就跟其他排箫队永远关在一起\N{\rEng}or you get locked up forever with the other flute bands.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.71,0:15:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汤普森  能过来一下吗\N{\rEng}Thompson, can you come over here?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.66,0:15:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些排箫乐队老是叽哩呱啦吵个不停\N{\rEng}The flute band players won't shut up about something
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.66,0:15:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又听不懂\N{\rEng}and I can't understand them.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.07,0:15:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了  我们不能走\N{\rEng}Por favor! No podemos ir!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.47,0:15:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来这里是为了保护你们的\N{\rEng}Estamos aqui para proteger a ustedes!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.18,0:15:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对  我们不能走  -为了保护你们\N{\rEng}- Si, no podemis ir! - Que son protectores.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.52,0:15:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们大概在说  你们不能遣送我们\N{\rEng}They're saying something like you can't send us away.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.21,0:15:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们是守护者  -守护什么\N{\rEng}- We are the protectors. - Protectors from what?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.68,0:15:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛茸茸的死神啊\N{\rEng}La muerte peludo!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.22,0:15:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛茸茸的死神啊\N{\rEng}La muerte peludo!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.70,0:15:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他说什么呢  -我猜他是在说\N{\rEng}- What does that mean? - I think he said,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.26,0:15:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"毛茸茸的死神"\N{\rEng}"The furry death."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.53,0:15:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛茸茸的死神\N{\rEng}La muerte peludo!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.60,0:16:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛茸茸的死神啊\N{\rEng}La muerte peludo!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.00,0:16:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎收看CNN\N{\rEng}This is CNN.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.38,0:16:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一支秘鲁排箫乐队\N{\rEng}The last of the Peruvian flute bands
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.26,0:16:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已被成功地从世界各地根除\N{\rEng}have successfully been eradicated from every part of the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.71,0:16:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保罗·哈里斯在步行街发来报道  保罗\N{\rEng}Paul Harris is at the shopping promenade. And Paul,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.50,0:16:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想大街上没有了秘鲁排箫队\N{\rEng}pretty nice not having any Peruvian flute music there,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.89,0:16:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉很好吧\N{\rEng}I suspect?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.26,0:16:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实耳根清净了不少  汤姆\N{\rEng}Really welcome silence, Tom.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.35,0:16:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现已好几天看不到\N{\rEng}There hasn't been a Peruvian pan flute band
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.15,0:16:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一支排箫队了\N{\rEng} in sight for days now
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.62,0:16:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个人都非常享受这种安静祥和\N{\rEng}and everyone is really been enjoying the peace.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.88,0:16:28.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在世界人民都能安心舒一口气了\N{\rEng}The world can breathe a collective sigh of relief now
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.44,0:16:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要感谢\N{\rEng}as we thank the--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.07,0:16:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么鬼\N{\rEng}What the...?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.67,0:16:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天哪  -噢  天哪\N{\rEng}- Oh, my God! - Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.68,0:16:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苍了个天的\N{\rEng}Jesus Christ!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.05,0:16:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边出了一些状况\N{\rEng}There's something else here!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.91,0:16:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是秘鲁排箫队\N{\rEng}It's not a Peruvian flute band. It's...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.29,0:16:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天爷  那是什么鬼东西\N{\rEng}Oh, my God. What is that thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.27,0:16:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保罗  你看到了什么\N{\rEng}Paul? What are you seeing?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.73,0:16:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛茸茸的\N{\rEng}It's furry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.01,0:16:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当毛茸茸的\N{\rEng}It's very furry!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.17,0:17:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  显然是有些异物显身了\N{\rEng}Okay. Obviously something different has shown up.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.15,0:17:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是说"毛茸茸"吗\N{\rEng}Did he say "Furry"?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.75,0:17:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我们现在也遭到一些\N{\rEng}Okay, we are experiencing some...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.83,0:17:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  那是什么东西\N{\rEng}My God! What is that thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.90,0:17:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  我们距秘鲁还有800公里\N{\rEng}All right. We're about 800 kilometers from Peru.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.67,0:17:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有一辆卡车带你们入境\N{\rEng}There will be a truck to take you inside the border
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.78,0:17:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并有简短的任务说明\N{\rEng}where you'll be briefed on mission specifics.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.94,0:17:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有没有这样想过\N{\rEng}Was there ever a moment
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.36,0:17:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你们想出天才计划\N{\rEng}when you guys first came up with the genius plan
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.59,0:17:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为秘鲁排箫乐队的时候\N{\rEng}to become a Peruvian flute band
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.24,0:17:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有人会说"嘿  知道吗"\N{\rEng}that any of you said, "Hey, you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.08,0:17:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"这个计划可能会出岔子"\N{\rEng}"This plan might backfire?"
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.23,0:17:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不会这么想\N{\rEng}No, that never occurs to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.19,0:17:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你们都是混蛋\N{\rEng}Because you guys are jerks
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.69,0:17:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远不会吸取教训\N{\rEng}and you never learn from your mistakes.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.88,0:18:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以学校的人\N{\rEng}And that's why everyone at school 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.24,0:18:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都鄙视你们\N{\rEng}thinks you guys are assholes.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.95,0:18:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是  全校都好喜欢我们\N{\rEng}That's not true! Kids at school like us!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.47,0:18:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吗\N{\rEng}Don't they?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.21,0:18:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  全校都爱死我们了\N{\rEng}Yeah, dude, kids at school totally like us.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.73,0:18:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在有难了\N{\rEng}Craig's just being a dick
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.75,0:18:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格就拽起来了\N{\rEng}because we're having a tough time right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.00,0:18:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说我拽\N{\rEng}I'm being a dick.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.56,0:18:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是\N{\rEng}Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.47,0:18:16.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们拿走我的钱\N{\rEng}You guys took my birthday money,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.00,0:18:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害我被捕  还被发配到迈阿密\N{\rEng}got me arrested and sent to Miami
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.68,0:18:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不拆了秘鲁这个国家就不能回家\N{\rEng}with no way home except to take down the county of Peru
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.07,0:18:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我拽了\N{\rEng}and I'm being a dick.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.91,0:18:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-跟这小子没话说  -好吧  克雷格\N{\rEng}- There's no talking to this guy. - All right, fine, Craig.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.43,0:18:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一回家\N{\rEng}When we get back home,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.31,0:18:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把钱都还给你  \N{\rEng}we'll get you your money back, 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.37,0:18:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后再也不鸟你\N{\rEng}and we'll never talk to you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.23,0:18:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何\N{\rEng}How's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.07,0:18:31.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求之不得  谢了\N{\rEng}That would be great. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.98,0:18:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对呀  这说不通嘛\N{\rEng}This is wrong. This just doesn't make any sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.58,0:18:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么国安部要送我们去秘鲁\N{\rEng}Why would Homeland Security send us into Peru?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.36,0:18:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为秘鲁人要掌控世界吗\N{\rEng}Because they were starting to take over the world?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.59,0:18:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  只是觉得\N{\rEng}I don't know. It just feels like...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.30,0:18:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中应该另有文章\N{\rEng}there's got to be something else going on here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.63,0:18:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托啦  我都不知道该找谁了\N{\rEng}Please, I don't know where else to turn.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.70,0:18:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警方一点帮助都没有\N{\rEng}The police haven't been any help.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.76,0:18:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们孩子现在可能真的麻烦大了\N{\rEng}I think our boys might really be in trouble this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.00,0:18:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  麻烦确认后打给我  谢了\N{\rEng}Yes, yes, please check and call me right back. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.37,0:19:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  我向上帝发誓  你要再不住手\N{\rEng}Randy, I swear to God if you don't put that thing away...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.18,0:19:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莎朗  总有一天你会因为我\N{\rEng}Sharon, you're going to be really glad
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.35,0:19:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,录了那么多家庭轶事而高兴的\N{\rEng}I have all this footage of the family some day.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.50,0:19:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没跟你开玩笑  兰迪  够了\N{\rEng}I mean it, Randy. That's enough!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.39,0:19:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你何必录下每分每秒\N{\rEng}You don't have to videotape every single...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.76,0:19:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么鬼东西\N{\rEng}What the hell was that?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.76,0:19:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐\N{\rEng}Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.84,0:19:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面出事了  别出去\N{\rEng}Something's going on outside. Stay here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.95,0:19:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  爸\N{\rEng}What's going on, Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.44,0:19:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回你房间去  谢莉\N{\rEng}Get back to your room, Shelley!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.76,0:19:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了\N{\rEng}What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.77,0:19:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们无处不在啊\N{\rEng}They're all over the place!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.66,0:19:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么东西  -毛茸茸的东西\N{\rEng}- What are? - They're really furry!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.31,0:19:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁干的\N{\rEng}What did that?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.14,0:19:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么东西\N{\rEng}What is that thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.37,0:19:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马什先生  你们快转移  这不安全了\N{\rEng}Mr. Marsh, you have to move. It isn't safe to be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.81,0:20:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐\N{\rEng}Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.33,0:20:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快  从另一边回去\N{\rEng}Go, go back the other way!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.17,0:20:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  天呐\N{\rEng}Oh, God! Oh, God!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.99,0:20:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我非常  震惊\N{\rEng}I'm so... startled.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.04,0:20:34.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官  我们遇上了更大的麻烦\N{\rEng}Sir, we've got a bigger problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.53,0:20:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能有什么问题\N{\rEng}And what might that be?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.06,0:20:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从世界各地发出的新报告上说\N{\rEng}New reports are coming in from cities all over the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.93,0:20:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,造成巨大伤亡和损失的好像是\N{\rEng}Word of massive destruction and death by what appear to be...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.57,0:20:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豚鼠\N{\rEng}Guinea pigs?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.31,0:20:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  长官\N{\rEng}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.16,0:20:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您怎么知道的\N{\rEng}How did you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.65,0:20:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你差点就看出来了  戴维斯\N{\rEng}You were so close to figuring it all out, Davis.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.35,0:20:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗\N{\rEng}Did you know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.08,0:20:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}Sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.99,0:21:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你在迈阿密就知道了呢\N{\rEng}I really thought you had me at Miami.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.00,0:21:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你就是没能看透各中端倪\N{\rEng}But you just couldn't quite put the pieces together.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.27,0:21:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你\N{\rEng}You...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.74,0:21:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你\N{\rEng}You...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.98,0:21:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早就知道会有这天\N{\rEng}knew this was going to happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.90,0:21:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才只是个开始呢  戴维斯\N{\rEng}Oh, this is only the beginning, Davis.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.52,0:21:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  我不会让你坏事的\N{\rEng}And I can't let you interfere.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.61,0:21:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不住了  朋友\N{\rEng}Sorry, my friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.72,0:21:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我千辛万苦才等到今天\N{\rEng}But I've work too hard to make all this happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.58,0:21:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排箫队正走向灭亡\N{\rEng}The pan flute bands are on their way to their deaths,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.20,0:21:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们豚鼠时代已经来临\N{\rEng}the guinea pigs are rising.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.96,0:21:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而唯一能够制止这一切的人\N{\rEng}And the only person who could have stopped all this...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.64,0:21:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正去往一个不名之地\N{\rEng}is on his way to the middle of nowhere.
