[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由TimeM生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.net
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayDepth: 0
PlayResX: 1916
PlayResY: 1076
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 2
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H19000000,&H000E0300,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,2,2,134,120,68,1
Style: eng,Microsoft YaHei,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,26,1
Style: Top,微软雅黑,10,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Git,Comic Sans MS,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Chn,微软雅黑,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Eng,Comic Sans MS,60,&H002AF7FF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.00,0:00:11.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm going down to south park\N gonna have myself a time 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.85,0:00:15.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Friendly faces everywhere\N humble folks without temptation 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.13,0:00:17.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Going down to south park\N gonna leave my woes behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.52,0:00:21.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ample parking day or night\N people shouting howdy neighbor
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.76,0:00:24.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heading on out to south park\N gonna see if I can't unwind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.34,0:00:28.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I like girls with big vaginas\N I like girls with big fat titties
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.41,0:00:31.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.46,0:21:45.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译制作\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}YYeTs人人影视字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.46,0:21:46.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Emerson_y
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.46,0:21:46.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0020,,{\1c&HFDC282&}校对\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}finalaya Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.46,0:21:47.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0020,,{\1c&HFDC282&}后期\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}csbeyond
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.47,0:21:48.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0060,,{\1c&HFDC282&}总监\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.00,0:00:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0150,,{\1c&HFDC282&}《南方公园》第14季  第07集\N{\rEng}South Park Season 14 Episode 07
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.00,0:00:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0100,,"流行病(下):震惊"\N{\rEng}"Pandemic (Part 2): The Startling"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.30,0:00:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正黑体简体\fs60\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[你本不该目睹]
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.80,0:00:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  出什么事了\N{\rEng}What's going on, Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.11,0:00:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马什先生  你必须离开  这不\N{\rEng}Mr. Marsh, you have to move. It isn't...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.49,0:00:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我非常\N{\rEng}I'm so...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.36,0:00:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,震惊\N{\rEng}startled.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.81,0:01:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正黑体简体\fs60\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[流行病(下):震惊]
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.58,0:01:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫克雷格·塔克 \N{\rEng}My name is Craig Tucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.95,0:01:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上周我生日\N{\rEng}Last week was my birthday.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.43,0:01:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶奶给了我一张100美元的票子\N{\rEng}My grandma gave me a check for $100.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.94,0:01:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高兴极了\N{\rEng}I was so happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.56,0:01:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是后来  四个同学来家里找我\N{\rEng}But then, four kids from school came to my house
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.60,0:01:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说我应该利用这100块\N{\rEng}And said I should use my $100
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.22,0:01:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去投资成立\N{\rEng}to invest in becoming
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.09,0:01:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个秘鲁排箫乐队\N{\rEng}a Peruvian flute band.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.06,0:01:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们向我保证\N{\rEng}They promised 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.95,0:01:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要一下午  我的钱就能翻倍\N{\rEng}I would double my money in one afternoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.09,0:01:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是警察把我们给逮了\N{\rEng}But the government arrested us,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.47,0:01:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有其他的秘鲁排箫乐队\N{\rEng}along with all the other Peruvian flute bands,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.89,0:01:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我们押到迈阿密一所集中营\N{\rEng}and took us to an internment camp in Miami.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.57,0:01:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们哀求他们放我们回家  \N{\rEng}We begged to go home. 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.78,0:01:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果  他们\N{\rEng}But instead, the government told us 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.38,0:01:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要送我们去秘鲁\N{\rEng}they were sending us to Peru.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.27,0:01:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我现在在秘鲁\N{\rEng}And so that is why I am now in Peru.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.49,0:01:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我不幸挂掉\N{\rEng}If I die, 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.29,0:01:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要知道这全是因为\N{\rEng}let it be known that it is because four guys
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.71,0:01:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被学校的四个讨厌鬼骗了 \N{\rEng}I don't even like from school lied to me 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.54,0:01:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还拐了我的生日红包\N{\rEng}and took my birthday money.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.89,0:01:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格  我们没有骗你 \N{\rEng}We didn't lie, Craig! 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.89,0:01:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这本来是个生财之道\N{\rEng}It was a sweet idea!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.10,0:01:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是嘛  我们怎么知道\N{\rEng}Yeah. How were we supposed to know
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.41,0:01:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排箫乐队是非法的\N{\rEng}that pan flute bands would be outlawed?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.94,0:01:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事\N{\rEng}I don't get it. 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.53,0:02:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说会有军队在这里与我们碰头吗\N{\rEng}They said the military would meet us here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.42,0:02:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说了让我们在这着陆\N{\rEng}This is where they told us to land.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.23,0:02:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你能和华府联系上吗  -正在联系\N{\rEng}- Can't you get through to Washington? - I'm trying.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.42,0:02:06.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是华盛顿的康纳\N{\rEng}This is Conner in Washington!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.39,0:02:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,康纳  国安部派我们\N{\rEng}Hey Conner. The place that Homeland Security
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.31,0:02:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,执行任务的地方\N{\rEng}told us to start the operation,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.11,0:02:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人跟我们碰头\N{\rEng}there's nobody here to meet us.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.32,0:02:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似我们被派到无人地带了\N{\rEng}It's like they sent us to no man's land.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.78,0:02:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娘啊  到处都是\N{\rEng}Jesus, they're everywhere!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.72,0:02:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么到处都是\N{\rEng}What are everywhere?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.81,0:02:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛茸茸的\N{\rEng}So furry!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.77,0:02:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们正在袭击\N{\rEng}They're attacking...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.15,0:02:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每一个城市\N{\rEng}every city.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.09,0:02:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们一个个地死去\N{\rEng}People dying!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.53,0:02:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豚鼠\N{\rEng}Guinea pigs...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.84,0:02:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到处都是\N{\rEng}All over!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.75,0:02:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-豚鼠?  -没法阻止它们\N{\rEng}- Guinea pigs? - Can't stop them.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.97,0:02:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得离开\N{\rEng}Need to get out.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.58,0:02:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚吃了\N{\rEng}I just ate...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.17,0:02:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个花生\N{\rEng}a peanut.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.77,0:02:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花生卡在\N{\rEng}Peanut now stuck
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.71,0:02:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喉咙了\N{\rEng}in throat.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.38,0:02:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不该吃花生\N{\rEng}I shouldn't eat peanuts...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.77,0:02:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是在恐惧时\N{\rEng}when scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.92,0:02:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我重新打开了摄像机\N{\rEng}I've got the video camera.  Got it turned on again.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.98,0:02:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是兰迪·马什  \N{\rEng}This is Randy Marsh.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.14,0:03:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摄像机正对着我\N{\rEng}I'm shooting this video of myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.42,0:03:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,20分钟前  一些\N{\rEng}20 minutes ago, some...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.05,0:03:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巨型生物袭击了我们小镇\N{\rEng}huge creatures attacked our town.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.01,0:03:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在外面仍旧一片混乱\N{\rEng}It's still chaos out the window.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.19,0:03:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我差点没能活着回家\N{\rEng}I barely made it back to the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.76,0:03:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莎朗现在和我在一起\N{\rEng}Sharon is here with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.66,0:03:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有谢莉  谢莉  对镜头挥挥手\N{\rEng}And there's Shelley. Wave to the camera, Shelley.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.07,0:03:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  你就不能放下摄像机吗\N{\rEng}Randy, will you put down that camera?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.41,0:03:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得想想怎么办\N{\rEng}We need to figure out what to do!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.09,0:03:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道怎么办  我被吓傻了\N{\rEng}I don't know what to do. I'm so startled.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.24,0:03:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看新闻上怎么说\N{\rEng}We have to see what the News is saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.28,0:03:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是纽约现场发来的报道  \N{\rEng}This is a shot of New York city 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.72,0:03:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纽约同样受到巨型豚鼠的袭击  \N{\rEng}where the giant guinea pigs have also attacked. 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.43,0:03:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豚鼠\N{\rEng}Guinea pigs?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.17,0:03:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据报道  豚鼠袭击事件\N{\rEng}Reports of attacks are coming in
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.46,0:03:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已席卷全球各大城市\N{\rEng}from major cities all over the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.64,0:03:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  全世界都有\N{\rEng}Jesus, this thing is worldwide?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.77,0:03:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看那个怪物\N{\rEng}Look at that thing!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.45,0:03:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  我们该怎么办\N{\rEng}Randy, what are we gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.12,0:03:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  偶滴娘啊  \N{\rEng}Oh, my god! Oh, my god! 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.14,0:03:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  快跑\N{\rEng}Go, Randy! Run!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.46,0:03:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们快逃啊\N{\rEng}We gotta get out!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.65,0:04:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麦克斯  哈里森  有人吗\N{\rEng}Michels? Harrison? Anybody?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.60,0:04:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卫星无法连接  无线也没回应\N{\rEng}Nothing. lsat is down, and no answer at RCU.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.63,0:04:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边肯定出了大事\N{\rEng}Whatever is going on out there, it's huge.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.89,0:04:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我搞清楚状况\N{\rEng}All right, just let me get this straight.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.68,0:04:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国安部长命令你们\N{\rEng}The head of homeland security ordered you 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.72,0:04:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我们五个孩子带到秘鲁\N{\rEng}to fly us, five kids, to Peru,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.38,0:04:15.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但让你们在秘鲁的\N{\rEng}But had you land way up 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.19,0:04:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安第斯山脉上着陆\N{\rEng}in the Andes Mountains of Peru
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.83,0:04:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好让其他政府人员来接我们\N{\rEng}So that other government people could meet us and then...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.48,0:04:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再告诉我们怎么去\N{\rEng}somehow tell us how to go to the capital of Peru
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.95,0:04:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘鲁首都利马\N{\rEng}Way over in Lima
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.00,0:04:24.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并打倒秘鲁政府\N{\rEng}And take down their government?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.74,0:04:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  就是这样\N{\rEng}Yes, that was the order.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.20,0:04:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们觉得有道理吗\N{\rEng}And that makes sense to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.00,0:04:31.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没道理\N{\rEng}Nope, not at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.67,0:04:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话  整个围剿排箫乐队的行动\N{\rEng}Actually, the whole rounding up of the pan flute bands
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.13,0:04:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都让我们摸不清头脑\N{\rEng}didn't make sense to any of us either.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.00,0:04:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然他们做的事没有一件有道理\N{\rEng}None of what that Homeland Security guy does make sense!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.42,0:04:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那能送我们回家了吗  拜托\N{\rEng}So, could you just fly us home, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.83,0:04:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没搞明白\N{\rEng}You don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.33,0:04:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们计划在这等加油车\N{\rEng}The plan was to have a refueling truck meet us here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.09,0:04:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不加油  哪也去不了\N{\rEng}We don't have enough gas to fly anyplace.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.81,0:04:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下好了\N{\rEng}Oh, that's awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.64,0:04:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们只能另谋出路了\N{\rEng}So, we've got to find another way out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.98,0:04:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似是这样\N{\rEng}It's starting to look that way, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.06,0:04:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个好玩\N{\rEng}This is fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.37,0:05:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们进阴森林子里走走\N{\rEng}Let's walk for miles through a spooky jungle.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.99,0:05:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是越来越好玩了\N{\rEng}It just keeps getting better and better.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.27,0:05:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格  你这态度真讨嫌\N{\rEng}You know, we're getting pretty sick of your attitude, Craig.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.37,0:05:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是\N{\rEng}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.16,0:05:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁愿意跟个怨夫一起玩\N{\rEng}Nobody likes hanging out with people who complain
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.15,0:05:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们看  连光都没有\N{\rEng}Look at that. No lights on, nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.67,0:05:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像没人来过这里 \N{\rEng}It's like humans have never been to this part of Peru.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.51,0:05:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似越来越多豚鼠从各个方向涌来\N{\rEng}More guinea pigs seem to be moving in from all directions.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.69,0:05:34.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们查了维基百科\N{\rEng}We checked on Wikipedia,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.25,0:05:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现豚鼠是一种\N{\rEng}and found out that guinea pigs are
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.23,0:05:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来自安第斯山脉的生物  这里\N{\rEng}from the Andes Mountains here?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.20,0:05:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排箫乐队处理得如何\N{\rEng}What about the pan flute bands?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.02,0:05:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都押往关塔那摩湾了吗\N{\rEng}Are they on their way to Guantanamo Bay?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.50,0:05:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官  我们现在的麻烦\N{\rEng}Sir, we believe we have bigger problems
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.69,0:05:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比排箫乐队更加棘手\N{\rEng}right now than pan street...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.75,0:05:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有把他们押到船上\N{\rEng}Have they been loaded on to the boats or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.31,0:05:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  我们把所有人员\N{\rEng}No, sir. We diverted all the resources away
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.99,0:05:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都从处理排箫乐队\N{\rEng}from the pan flute bands to 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.69,0:05:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转到豚鼠事件上了\N{\rEng}deal with the guinea pigs.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.70,0:05:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给过命令了\N{\rEng}That was an order!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.36,0:05:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些排箫乐队 \N{\rEng}The flute bands were to be 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.72,0:06:00.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚就该上船去关塔那摩\N{\rEng}put on boats to Guantanamo last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.66,0:06:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里还是我说了算\N{\rEng}I am still in charge here!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.25,0:06:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上把排箫乐队押上去关塔那摩的船只\N{\rEng}I want those pan flute bands on the boats to Guantanamo!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.31,0:06:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命  长官\N{\rEng}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.91,0:06:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可也没必要对人家吼嘛\N{\rEng}I don't see why you have to yell at people.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.99,0:06:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  没事了  主干道\N{\rEng}Okay, darling. Main street...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.66,0:06:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看啊\N{\rEng}Look at that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.81,0:06:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  我们该去哪里  \N{\rEng}Where do we go, Randy? 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.64,0:06:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得离开小镇\N{\rEng}We've got to get out of town.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.67,0:06:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那边走\N{\rEng}Go through that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.74,0:06:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的胳膊\N{\rEng}My arm!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.85,0:06:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  -兰迪  快跑\N{\rEng}- Oh, jesus! - Randy, run!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.05,0:06:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快跑\N{\rEng}Run!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.84,0:06:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我们正在逃命\N{\rEng}Okay... We're running now!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.64,0:06:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莎朗和谢莉正在逃命\N{\rEng}There's Sharon and Shelley running.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.19,0:06:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢莉  朝镜头挥挥手\N{\rEng}Wave to the camare Shelley?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.56,0:06:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸\N{\rEng}Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.44,0:06:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快进去\N{\rEng}In there!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.20,0:06:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  太可怕了\N{\rEng}Oh, god. Oh, god. I'm so startled.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.23,0:06:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莎朗  你害怕吗 \N{\rEng}Are you startled, Sharon? 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.54,0:06:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  放下它\N{\rEng}Randy, put down the--
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.76,0:07:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它会杀了我们\N{\rEng}It's gonna kill us!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.35,0:07:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蹲下  谢莉  它进不来的\N{\rEng}Just stay down, Shelley. It can't come in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.69,0:07:09.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下  我要从外面拍个特写\N{\rEng}Hold on. I need to get a shot of it from outside...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.57,0:07:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  你要去哪里\N{\rEng}Randy, where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.49,0:07:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是在巴士外面拍到的画面\N{\rEng}Here we see a view from outside the bus.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.80,0:07:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪\N{\rEng}Randy!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.52,0:07:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈到底在干嘛\N{\rEng}What the hell are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.57,0:07:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拍到个好镜头  莎朗\N{\rEng}I got a really good shot of it, Sharon.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.43,0:07:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞不懂  雷姆斯基 \N{\rEng}I don't know, Lemski.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.78,0:07:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地图上根本没有这里的标注\N{\rEng}This entire area of Peru isn't even charted on the maps.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.16,0:07:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个峡谷都很奇怪\N{\rEng}This whole valley is strange.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.69,0:07:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的水果都好大\N{\rEng}Just look at the size of fruit. 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.18,0:07:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是桃子吗\N{\rEng}Ain't that a peach?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.38,0:07:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有那些苹果\N{\rEng}And how do you like them apples?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.66,0:07:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看这个\N{\rEng}Take a look at this!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.69,0:07:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似是\N{\rEng}They look like...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.25,0:07:56.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜂巢\N{\rEng}Beehive combs.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.39,0:07:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶滴神呐\N{\rEng}Oh, my god.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.36,0:08:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  这是什么地方  \N{\rEng}Dude, what is this place? 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.34,0:08:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似是一片未知之境\N{\rEng}It's like an unknown valley
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.10,0:08:06.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被时间遗忘的角落\N{\rEng}that time forgot
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.27,0:08:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东西都大得吓人\N{\rEng}where everything grows huge.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.93,0:08:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这太刺激了\N{\rEng}That's a shock.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.15,0:08:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当初决定跟你们走\N{\rEng}I decided to follow you guys
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.05,0:08:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在却困在这个巨型的迷失世界\N{\rEng}And now I'm in land of the giants' lost world.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.00,0:08:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格  这又不是我们的错\N{\rEng}Craig, it isn't our fault!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.62,0:08:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得好像\N{\rEng}You make it sound like 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.26,0:08:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是故意的似的\N{\rEng}we always want to be in the any choice!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.79,0:08:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们又没办法\N{\rEng}But we don't have any choice!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.95,0:08:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是  事情就这么发生了\N{\rEng}Yeah, stuff just happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.03,0:08:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-事情就这么发生了  -没错\N{\rEng}- Stuff just happens. - That's right!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.15,0:08:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们只是被政府\N{\rEng}You just wind up being sent by the government
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.44,0:08:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,派来打倒利马\N{\rEng}to take down the city of Lima
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.95,0:08:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果被送到一个失落地带\N{\rEng}Only to wind up in land of the giants lost world.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.63,0:08:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.18,0:08:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们知道大多数孩子会碰上什么事吗\N{\rEng}You know what stuff happens to most kids?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.62,0:08:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从自行车上摔下来\N{\rEng}They fall off their bikes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.30,0:08:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和父母吵架\N{\rEng}They get in fights with their parents.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.50,0:08:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被人骗走生日红包\N{\rEng}They get swindled out of their birthday money.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.95,0:08:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管我们在哪里 \N{\rEng}Look, wherever we are, 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.59,0:08:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还是继续前进吧\N{\rEng}I think we better keep moving.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.36,0:08:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  小心\N{\rEng}Dude, look out!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.39,0:08:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  谁能来阻止它\N{\rEng}Oh, god! Somebody make it stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.29,0:08:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事了\N{\rEng}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.71,0:09:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莎朗和谢莉在百思买的楼顶\N{\rEng}Here's Sharon and Shelley on the roof of Best Buy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.49,0:09:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们从街上逃到这里\N{\rEng}We ran up here to get off the streets.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.33,0:09:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们发现斯托奇一家也躲在这里\N{\rEng}We found the Stotch family hiding out up here also.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.06,0:09:10.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是克里斯和琳达\N{\rEng}There's Chris and Linda, 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.27,0:09:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有他们的儿子巴特斯\N{\rEng}and their son Butters.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.11,0:09:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好\N{\rEng}Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.40,0:09:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么\N{\rEng}What is that? 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.99,0:09:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克里斯  那到底是什么\N{\rEng}Chris, what is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.99,0:09:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没听过这种声音\N{\rEng}That--that's a new sound.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.65,0:09:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  快看\N{\rEng}Oh, god. Look!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.13,0:09:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那些不是豚鼠  -快下去\N{\rEng}- Those aren't guinea pigs. - Get off the roof!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.24,0:09:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快跑  快快快\N{\rEng}Go! Go, go, go, go, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.28,0:09:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我们正在下楼梯\N{\rEng}Oh, god. Going down the stairs now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.21,0:09:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快下楼梯\N{\rEng}Get down the stairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.85,0:09:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最新消息  一种巨型蜜蜂\N{\rEng}And we are now getting word of giant bees.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.98,0:09:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已出现在美国以及欧洲\N{\rEng}The giant bees have been seen in the U.S. and Europe.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.74,0:09:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶滴个娘\N{\rEng}Oh, god.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.13,0:09:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快跑  到处都是蜜蜂\N{\rEng}Get away. There's bees everywhere!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.93,0:09:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边也有一只\N{\rEng}There's another one right there!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.66,0:09:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶滴娘啊\N{\rEng}Oh, my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.81,0:10:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被蜇了\N{\rEng}It stung me!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.51,0:10:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓死我了\N{\rEng}Oh, that startled me!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.11,0:10:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太吓人了\N{\rEng}That was really startling!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.00,0:10:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们往山里越走越深了\N{\rEng}I think we're just heading deeper into the mountains.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.83,0:10:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我们应该走那条路\N{\rEng}Yeah, maybe we should start heading that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.93,0:10:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们死定了\N{\rEng}I think we're fucked.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.80,0:10:27.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看这个\N{\rEng}Hey, hey, look at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.41,0:10:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么\N{\rEng}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.74,0:10:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  貌似很古老\N{\rEng}I don't know. Looks old.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.15,0:10:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去里面看看\N{\rEng}Let's see what's in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.62,0:10:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去里面看看\N{\rEng}Let's see what's in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.73,0:10:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你们才会落得这种地步\N{\rEng}That's why you guys get into these situations.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.77,0:10:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们遇到一座阴森古老的废墟  就说\N{\rEng}Because when you come across a spooky ancient ruin, you say,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.68,0:10:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"去里面看看"\N{\rEng}"let's see what's in there."
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.48,0:10:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可能是条出路呢  克雷格  \N{\rEng}It might be a way out, Craig! 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.21,0:10:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是嘛  怨夫\N{\rEng}Yeah, Mr. complainy-pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.15,0:11:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里估计几个世纪都没人来过\N{\rEng}I don't think anybody's been in here for centuries.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.58,0:11:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对是\N{\rEng}Yeah, centuries.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.66,0:11:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家快看这个\N{\rEng}You guys look at this!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.40,0:11:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墙上绘着古代壁画\N{\rEng}It's a wall of ancient drawings.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.82,0:11:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是排箫乐队\N{\rEng}Dude, it's a peruvian flute band!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.21,0:11:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  看这边\N{\rEng}I know! And look.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.11,0:11:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似排箫音乐\N{\rEng}Looks like the pan flute music 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.27,0:11:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在赶走巨型豚鼠\N{\rEng}is driving away giant Guinea pig?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.72,0:11:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧  快看\N{\rEng}Oh, no way! Look!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.76,0:11:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排箫乐队被囚禁了\N{\rEng}The pan flute bands put in prison.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.73,0:11:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就跟现实一样\N{\rEng}Just like what happened!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.80,0:11:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着豚鼠吞噬人类  之后\N{\rEng}And then the guinea pigs killing people. And then...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.17,0:11:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  那是克雷格\N{\rEng}Dude, it's craig!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.93,0:11:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.41,0:11:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实是克雷格\N{\rEng}That is Craig!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.30,0:11:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-克雷格  这是怎么回事  -我不知道\N{\rEng}- Dude, Craig, what's going on? - I have no idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.76,0:11:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你能不能告诉我们\N{\rEng}Well, do you mind telling us 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.49,0:11:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么会被画在古印加墙上\N{\rEng}what you're doing on an ancient incan wall, Craig?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.89,0:11:52.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\rEng}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.84,0:11:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有消息称\N{\rEng}There is now word of 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.40,0:11:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美加两国的城市中正出现一些巨蜂巢\N{\rEng}huge beehives forming in cities across the U.S. and Canada.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.89,0:12:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欧洲和中国报导\N{\rEng}Europe and China are reporting 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.31,0:12:02.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死亡人数以万计\N{\rEng}deaths by guinea pigs of tens of thousands.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.93,0:12:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在局面控制得怎么样\N{\rEng}And how are the efforts to contain all this going?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.90,0:12:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很糟糕  长官\N{\rEng}It's bad, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.38,0:12:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前看来无法阻止他们\N{\rEng}It seems we have no way of stopping it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.08,0:12:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,场面已经完全失控\N{\rEng}We've lost complete control.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.84,0:12:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官\N{\rEng}Sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.36,0:12:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我刚想起一个好笑的段子\N{\rEng}I'm sorry. I just thought of a funny joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.58,0:12:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,言归正传  准备喷射机\N{\rEng}All right. Get the jets ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.00,0:12:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去一趟马丘比丘[秘鲁印加遗址]\N{\rEng}I need to get t- Machu Picchu.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.58,0:12:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马丘比丘吗\N{\rEng}Machu Picchu, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.64,0:12:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  马上送我去马丘比丘\N{\rEng}Yes, I need to be taken to Machu Picchu.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.34,0:12:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你聋了吗\N{\rEng}Have you lost your hearing?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.08,0:12:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  长官  \N{\rEng}But sir, 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.01,0:12:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去马丘比丘有什么用\N{\rEng}what could possibly be at Machu Picchu to help--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.92,0:12:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里到底谁说了算\N{\rEng}Am I in charge or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.84,0:12:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们和其他幸存者正躲在杂货铺\N{\rEng}We're in the grocery store now. Some other survivors here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.10,0:12:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能从高速逃出去吗\N{\rEng}Can we get out through the highway?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.81,0:12:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上不了高速  那边全是豚耗\N{\rEng}The highway's unreachable. There's guinea rats all over it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.52,0:12:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-豚耗?  -太可怕了\N{\rEng}- Guinea rats? - So startled.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.34,0:12:51.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是豚耗\N{\rEng}What do you mean guinea rats?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.61,0:12:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不光只有豚鼠\N{\rEng}There are guinea pigs,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.63,0:12:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有豚蜂和豚耗\N{\rEng}But there's also guinea bees, guinea rats.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.86,0:12:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还看到外面有豚蜘蛛\N{\rEng}I've even seen some guinea spiders out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.58,0:12:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  你能不能别拍了\N{\rEng}Randy, will you stop doing that?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.15,0:13:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们得从地下找出路\N{\rEng}Look, I think we need to find a way out under the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.81,0:13:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下水管道  那里肯定不安全\N{\rEng}In the sewers? It can't be safe down there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.29,0:13:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我们到底该怎么办\N{\rEng}Oh, god. What are we going to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.41,0:13:12.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\rEng}Oh my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.90,0:13:14.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有东西进来了\N{\rEng}Something's inside the store!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.96,0:13:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豚兔  在那儿  进来了\N{\rEng}Guinea rabbits! There, inside!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.38,0:13:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-它们到处都是  -救命\N{\rEng}- They're everywhere! - Help me!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.79,0:13:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命\N{\rEng}Help...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.71,0:13:31.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  特拉维斯  不要啊\N{\rEng}No! Travis, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.59,0:13:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你救不了他\N{\rEng}You can't help him.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.06,0:13:35.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边又来了个东西\N{\rEng}There's something over there!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.26,0:13:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是豚熊\N{\rEng}It's a guinea bear!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.98,0:13:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢货  那是豚耗\N{\rEng}No, it's a guinea mouse, stupid!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.74,0:13:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了我吧\N{\rEng}Kill me!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.70,0:13:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰迪  去仓库  \N{\rEng}Randy, the storeroom! 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.73,0:13:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们快点躲到仓库里\N{\rEng}We've got to get to the storeroom!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.98,0:13:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  我什么都看不到\N{\rEng}Mom, I can't see!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.52,0:13:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  谢莉\N{\rEng}It's okay, Shelley.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.36,0:13:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸这就打开夜间模式\N{\rEng}Daddy's gonna turn on night vision.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.11,0:14:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  没事了\N{\rEng}There, there. Okay...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.24,0:14:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛  怎么了\N{\rEng}What? What? What? 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.01,0:14:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我把自己吓到了\N{\rEng}Nothing. I just startled myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.13,0:14:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走这边  伙计们\N{\rEng}Let's head over this way, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.58,0:14:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到了吗  好像是水流的声音\N{\rEng}You hear that? It sounds like water.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.58,0:14:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  从那边传来的\N{\rEng}Yeah, it's coming from up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.72,0:14:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  太不可思议了 \N{\rEng}Dude, that's awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.41,0:14:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走\N{\rEng}All right. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.71,0:14:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不去\N{\rEng}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.53,0:14:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是什么意思\N{\rEng}What do you mean no?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.49,0:14:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想再跟着你们\N{\rEng}I'm not following you guys anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.04,0:14:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  我们必须过去看看\N{\rEng}Dude, we have to go check this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.18,0:14:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\rEng}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.71,0:14:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为  只能这样了\N{\rEng}Because just-- that's just the way it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.25,0:14:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每每遇到什么坏事\N{\rEng}Every time bad things happen,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.88,0:14:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们非要把自己\N{\rEng}You guys end up putting yourselves
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.56,0:14:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搅和进去\N{\rEng}deeper into the middle of it
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.03,0:14:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为"只能这样了"\N{\rEng}Because "that's just the way it is."
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.17,0:14:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们又没有画在\N{\rEng}Hey, we aren't the ones
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.03,0:14:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神庙的预言墙上  胆小鬼\N{\rEng}on an ancient temple prophecy wall, butt-wipe!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.01,0:15:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无所谓\N{\rEng}I don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.28,0:15:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我心意已决\N{\rEng}I've decided that I'm done.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.21,0:15:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我决定不再跟你们搅和了\N{\rEng}I am choosing not to be a part of this anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.92,0:15:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要怎么做\N{\rEng}How do you do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.57,0:15:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很简单  看好了\N{\rEng}It's easy. Watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.30,0:15:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格  等等\N{\rEng}Craig, dude, wait up.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.84,0:15:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格  我们应该回去\N{\rEng}Dude, Craig, we should go back now.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.22,0:15:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要\N{\rEng}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.87,0:15:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看  这里好像有东西\N{\rEng}Hey, look! There's something here!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.83,0:15:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不看\N{\rEng}Nope.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.99,0:15:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  这真无聊\N{\rEng}Dude, this is boring.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.24,0:15:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是在游荡\N{\rEng}This is just a bunch of walking around.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.69,0:15:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  美好而又无聊\N{\rEng}Yep. Nice and boring.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.46,0:15:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是喜欢这样\N{\rEng}Just the way i like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.15,0:15:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豚鼠和豚蜂\N{\rEng}It's been three days now
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.64,0:15:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经袭击我们三天了\N{\rEng}Since the guinea pigs and the guinea bees attacked.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.26,0:15:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豚兔还是无处不在\N{\rEng}Guinea rabbits are still everywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.00,0:15:59.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一些豚豹\N{\rEng}Along with a few guinea panthers.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.38,0:16:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们躲在澳拜客牛排馆避难\N{\rEng}We've taken shelter at the outback steakhouse.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.96,0:16:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是莎朗和谢莉\N{\rEng}There's Sharon and Shelley.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.49,0:16:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟大家打个招呼 \N{\rEng}Say hey, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.06,0:16:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么\N{\rEng}What is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.27,0:16:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这就出去看看\N{\rEng}I'm going to take a look outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.28,0:16:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么 \N{\rEng}What is it? 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.14,0:16:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个蜥蜴豚王[阿森纳吉祥物蜥蜴枪王]\N{\rEng}It's a guinea-saurus rex.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.24,0:16:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶滴个娘啊\N{\rEng}Oh, my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.40,0:16:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我快被吓死了\N{\rEng}I'm way too startled!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.01,0:16:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看 \N{\rEng}Look!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.51,0:16:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  根本伤不了它们\N{\rEng}Jesus, they can't kill it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.87,0:16:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢莉  你觉得蜥蜴豚王怎么样\N{\rEng}What do you think about the saurus-rex, Shelley?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.17,0:16:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样好\N{\rEng}That's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.20,0:16:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是谢莉  蜥蜴豚王充当背景\N{\rEng}There's Shelley with the guinea saurus-rex in the background
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.54,0:16:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢莉  来个V手势  我想到了\N{\rEng}Give a little peace sign, Shelley. Oh, I know!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.95,0:16:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摊开手  假装\N{\rEng}Hold out your palm so it looks like
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.43,0:16:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在举着蜥蜴豚王\N{\rEng}you're holding the guinea saurus-rex.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.59,0:16:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢莉  -兰迪\N{\rEng}- Shelley? - Randy!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.60,0:16:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我受够了\N{\rEng}I have had it!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.88,0:16:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上放下那该死的摄像机\N{\rEng}You are putting down that goddamn camera!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.33,0:16:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莎朗  你总有一天会感激\N{\rEng}Sharon, you're gonna be really glad
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.90,0:16:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记录了这个片段\N{\rEng}we have all this footage of the family some day.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.87,0:17:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这等着\N{\rEng}Wait here a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.95,0:17:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊\N{\rEng}Behold!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.63,0:17:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我站在你的土地上\N{\rEng}I am standing on your precious land.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.03,0:17:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一刻我已经等太久了\N{\rEng}I've waited a long time for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.01,0:17:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在干嘛\N{\rEng}What's he doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.72,0:17:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的狗屁预言呢\N{\rEng}What of your prophecy now?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.65,0:17:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人能阻止我\N{\rEng}Nothing can stop me!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.97,0:17:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格\N{\rEng}Craig!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.28,0:17:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你怎么会在这里\N{\rEng}No! How did you get here?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.66,0:17:45.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个白痴把我们送到\N{\rEng}Hey, it's that asshole who sent us to
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.13,0:17:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人接应的荒野里\N{\rEng}the jungle and nobody picked up
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.92,0:17:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官  没什么事吧\N{\rEng}Sir, is everything all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.16,0:17:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-干掉它们  -为什么?\N{\rEng}- Shoot them! - Shoot them?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.42,0:17:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是潜逃出来的一支秘鲁乐队\N{\rEng}They're a peruvian band that escaped!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.29,0:17:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须斩草除根\N{\rEng}We must keep them contained!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.91,0:17:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的  听我说\N{\rEng}No, listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.36,0:17:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘鲁排箫乐队\N{\rEng}The peruvian flute bands were 
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.58,0:17:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以驱除豚兽\N{\rEng}keeping the guinea creatures away
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.92,0:18:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界之所以陷入恐慌\N{\rEng}Whatever is happening to the world is happening
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.49,0:18:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正因为你们将乐队撵走了\N{\rEng}Because you guys got rid of all the flute bands!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.66,0:18:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫你们开枪\N{\rEng}I said, "shoot them!"
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.16,0:18:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不信你们去看  这都是印加预言\N{\rEng}Go look! It's all an ancient Incan prophecy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.41,0:18:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许我们应该去看看  长官\N{\rEng}Maybe we should look at it, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.27,0:18:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈的克雷格\N{\rEng}Damn you, Craig!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.28,0:18:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是不肯罢休  是吧\N{\rEng}You just don't ever stop, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.56,0:18:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我什么都没说  -几千年来\N{\rEng}- I didn't say anything. - You see for thousands of years,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.25,0:18:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪兽都生活在秘鲁的山谷中\N{\rEng}Horrid creatures have lived in the guinea valley of Peru.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.58,0:18:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,印加人知道如何困住怪兽\N{\rEng}The Incas learned how to keep the creatures at bay,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.74,0:18:25.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,利用排箫音乐\N{\rEng}By playing pan flute music.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.95,0:18:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豚兽比人类还讨厌那种音乐\N{\rEng}Guinea creatures hate it even more than humans do.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.94,0:18:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但预言说有一天\N{\rEng}But the prophecy foretold that one day,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.87,0:18:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪兽会被释放\N{\rEng}the creatures would be on the unleashed
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.58,0:18:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,释放怪兽的人就是我\N{\rEng}And I have made that happen!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.06,0:18:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,印加人预言会出现一位救世主\N{\rEng}The Incas predicted the world would be saved,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.09,0:18:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是克雷格\N{\rEng}By Craig,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.72,0:18:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这个预言不会成真\N{\rEng}But that part of the prophecy will not come true!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.95,0:18:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你们都会死在这里\N{\rEng}For you will all die on this mountain!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.03,0:18:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是个怪物\N{\rEng}You're some kind of monster!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.10,0:18:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远远不止\N{\rEng}Oh, I'm much more than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.30,0:18:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豚蜂 豚兔 还有蜥蜴豚王\N{\rEng}Guinea bees, guinea rabbits, guinea-saurus rexes.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.66,0:19:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可比他们厉害得多\N{\rEng}I am something much more evil.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.08,0:19:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豚海盗\N{\rEng}Guinea pirate!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.70,0:19:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶滴神呐\N{\rEng}Jesus Christ!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.10,0:19:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  我向你保证\N{\rEng}Sir, I promise you,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.92,0:19:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会破坏你的计划\N{\rEng}I'm not going to ruin your plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.76,0:19:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这就走  你瞧\N{\rEng}I'll just walk away. See?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.66,0:19:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的眼睛正在喷射火光\N{\rEng}Okay, now there's sparks shooting out my eye.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.45,0:19:36.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克雷格  我诅咒你\N{\rEng}Curse ye, Craig!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.07,0:19:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手\N{\rEng}Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.15,0:19:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫克雷格·塔克\N{\rEng}My name is Craig Tucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.41,0:19:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上周  我阻止了一个豚海盗\N{\rEng}Last week, I stopped a guinea pirate 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.33,0:19:59.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,企图掌控地球的计划\N{\rEng}from taking over the earth.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.40,0:20:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有秘鲁排箫乐队均被释放\N{\rEng}All the Peruvian flute bands were released.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.02,0:20:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并把所有豚兽赶回了安第斯山脉\N{\rEng}And drove the guinea creatures back to Andes Mountains.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.94,0:20:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然牺牲了很多人  \N{\rEng}Many people had died, 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.19,0:20:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但人类取得了胜利\N{\rEng}but mankind had prevailed.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.32,0:20:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界各地的幸存者均已获救\N{\rEng}All over the world, survivors were found.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.23,0:20:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多人见证了灾难现场\N{\rEng}Living witnesses to the terror that had been seen.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.06,0:20:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来  快看啊\N{\rEng}Here, here. Look, look!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.68,0:20:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事  \N{\rEng}What the... 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.17,0:20:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没放带子进去\N{\rEng}I didn't have a tape in it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.04,0:20:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豚海盗还活着\N{\rEng}The guinea pirate lived,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.66,0:20:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但被送进监狱了其残生\N{\rEng}But was taken to prison to live out the rest of his days.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.84,0:20:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界各地的人\N{\rEng}And people all over the world
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.59,0:20:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都开始支持当地的秘鲁排箫乐队\N{\rEng}Learned to support their local Peruvian flute bands.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.10,0:20:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买他们的专辑\N{\rEng}And buy their cds,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.42,0:20:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他们保护人类不受豚兽迫害\N{\rEng}For they protect us from the guinea creatures.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.52,0:20:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被国安部送回了家\N{\rEng}As for me, I was returned home by Homeland Security.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.82,0:20:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸妈都高兴极了\N{\rEng}My parents were so happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.12,0:20:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我意识到我们没法时刻\N{\rEng}I realized that we don't always have
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.05,0:20:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掌控自己的生活\N{\rEng}control over what happened to us
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.88,0:20:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只不过是生活中的角色\N{\rEng}We are, but players on the stage of life.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.51,0:21:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此外我还学到了一点\N{\rEng}And I also learned to never listen
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.37,0:21:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人向你借钱时  别理他们\N{\rEng}When people come asking you for money.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.81,0:21:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那小子真是混蛋\N{\rEng}That guy's an asshole.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.24,0:21:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是  混蛋一个\N{\rEng}Yeah, what a dick.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.61,0:21:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真他妈讨厌克雷格\N{\rEng}I fucking hate Craig!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.85,0:21:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官  我们有麻烦了 \N{\rEng}Sir. sir, we have a problem. 
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.22,0:21:21.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又怎么了\N{\rEng}What now?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.38,0:21:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上任国安部长\N{\rEng}The former director of Homeland Security
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.38,0:21:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那个变成豚鼠的家伙\N{\rEng}that turned out to be a guinea pig.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.63,0:21:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,袭击了守卫  逃出了牢房\N{\rEng}It attacked the guards, got out of its holding cell.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.79,0:21:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  你是说\N{\rEng}My god, are you telling me...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.51,0:21:35.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  它越狱了\N{\rEng}Yes, sir. It broke out of prison.
