[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2008-10-10 06:38:08
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayDepth: 0
PlayResX: 1916
PlayResY: 1076
Defaultr: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 2
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H19000000,&H000E0300,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,2,2,134,120,68,1
Style: eng,Microsoft YaHei,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,26,1
Style: Top,微软雅黑,10,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Git,Comic Sans MS,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Chn,微软雅黑,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Eng,Comic Sans MS,60,&H002AF7FF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.00,0:00:11.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm going down to south park\N gonna have myself a Default 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.85,0:00:15.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Friendly faces everywhere\N humble folks without temptation 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.13,0:00:17.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Going down to south park\N gonna leave my woes behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.52,0:00:21.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ample parking day or night\N people shouting howdy neighbor
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.76,0:00:24.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heading on out to south park\N gonna see if I can't unwind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.34,0:00:28.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I like girls with big vaginas\N I like girls with big fat titties
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.41,0:00:31.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.40,0:21:46.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0060,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译制作\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}YYeTs人人影视字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.32,0:21:47.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}鲤鱼幡
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.17,0:21:48.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}校对\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.25,0:21:49.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0050,,{\1c&HFDC282&}后期\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}csbeyond
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.25,0:21:50.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0060,,{\1c&HFDC282&}总监\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.00,0:00:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0150,,{\1c&HFDC282&}《南方公园》第12季  第12集\N{\rEng}South Park Season 12 Episode 12
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.00,0:00:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0100,,"昨晚的真相"\N{\rEng}"About Last Night"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.74,0:00:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果今晚还有人质疑\N{\rEng}If there is anyone out there tonight who still doubts
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.99,0:00:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美国是否一切皆有可能\N{\rEng}that America is a place where all things are possible,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.05,0:00:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祖国奠基者的梦想\N{\rEng}who still wonders if the dream of 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.15,0:00:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是否仍存于世\N{\rEng}our founders is alive in our Default,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.21,0:00:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仍在质疑本国民主的力量\N{\rEng}who still questions the power of our democracy.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.95,0:00:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚你们将得到解答\N{\rEng}Tonight is your answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.15,0:00:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马\N{\rEng}Obama!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.11,0:00:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们赢了\N{\rEng}We did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.21,0:00:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们他妈的赢了\N{\rEng}We effin' did it! 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.15,0:00:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一个漫长征程\N{\rEng}It's been a long Default coming,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但今晚  \N{\rEng}but tonight, 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.52,0:01:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在这场选举的决定性时刻\N{\rEng}because of what we did on this date in this election
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.60,0:01:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所做的一切\N{\rEng} at this defining moment,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.79,0:01:06.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美国迎来了变革\N{\rEng}change has come to America.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.90,0:01:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马\N{\rEng}Yeah! Yeah, Obama!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.40,0:01:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变革\N{\rEng}Change!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.65,0:01:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变革\N{\rEng}It's--It's change!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.03,0:01:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨沙和玛丽亚  我非常爱你们\N{\rEng}Sasha and Malia, I love you both more than you can imagine.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.50,0:01:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们得到的新小狗\N{\rEng}And you have earned the new puppy
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.78,0:01:19.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将与我们一起入住白宫\N{\rEng}that's coming with us to the White House.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.90,0:01:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们将为它起名"火花"\N{\rEng}We will name him Sparkles.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.93,0:01:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他太牛逼了\N{\rEng}He's so awesome!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.93,0:01:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太完美牛逼了\N{\rEng}He's so perfect and awesome!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.72,0:01:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我们遭遇讽刺与质疑\N{\rEng}Where we are met with cynicism and doubt 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.90,0:01:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当别人说我们做不到\N{\rEng}and those who tell us that we can't, 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.46,0:01:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们将以凝聚民族精神的\N{\rEng}we will respond with that Defaultless creed 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.83,0:01:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永恒信条回应他们\N{\rEng}that sums up the spirit of a people.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.75,0:01:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我们可以\N{\rEng}Yes, we can.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.80,0:01:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我们可以\N{\rEng}Yes, we can!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.97,0:01:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我可以\N{\rEng}Yes, I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.85,0:01:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我可以\N{\rEng}Yes, I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.35,0:01:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变革终于来了  大伙儿\N{\rEng}Here comes the change, everybody!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.75,0:01:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了吗  我们的英雄当选了\N{\rEng}Did you see? Our man is in! 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.10,0:01:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们赢了\N{\rEng}We did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.95,0:01:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都会变好了\N{\rEng}Everything is going to be awesome now!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.41,0:01:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是咱们一生中最伟大的日子\N{\rEng}This is the greatest day of our lives!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.85,0:01:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我们可以\N{\rEng}Yes, we can!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.28,0:02:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道该干啥了\N{\rEng}I don't even know what to do now!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.61,0:02:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道要干啥\N{\rEng}I know what to do!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.26,0:02:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失败者\N{\rEng}Losers.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.37,0:02:07.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失败者\N{\rEng}Losers!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.68,0:02:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失败者\N{\rEng}Losers!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.38,0:02:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-失败者  -闭嘴\N{\rEng}- Losers! - Oh, shut up!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.00,0:02:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-失败者  -我们输了\N{\rEng}- Losers. - We lost?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.46,0:02:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这很正常\N{\rEng}It is natural.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.01,0:02:19.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚会感到失望非常正常\N{\rEng}It's natural, tonight, to feel some disappointment.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.06,0:02:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们尽了最大努力\N{\rEng}We fought as hard as we could.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.91,0:02:23.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管未能达到目标\N{\rEng}And though we fell short, 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.43,0:02:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但败的是我  不是你们\N{\rEng}the failure is mine not yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.52,0:02:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\rEng}No! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.24,0:02:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可怜的老麦  看起来真的很伤心\N{\rEng}Poor old John McCain. He looks real sad.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.14,0:02:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  这不是真的\N{\rEng}No, this can't happen!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.33,0:02:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史蒂芬\N{\rEng}Steven!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.41,0:02:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都结束了  琳达\N{\rEng}It's all over, Linda!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.95,0:02:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们熟悉的国家要变了\N{\rEng}The country as we know it is about to change.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.43,0:02:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们死定了\N{\rEng}We're all dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.27,0:02:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不一定呢  史蒂芬\N{\rEng}You don't know that, Steven!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.72,0:02:45.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让一个没经验的人当总统  \N{\rEng}With an inexperienced man as president, 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.62,0:02:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果显而易见\N{\rEng}we do know it!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.47,0:02:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说的没错  \N{\rEng}He's right! 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.35,0:02:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们玩完了  好么\N{\rEng}Game over, man, m'kay?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.66,0:02:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们说不定熬不到天亮\N{\rEng}We'll probably be dead by sunrise!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.21,0:02:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  爸爸爱你\N{\rEng}Butters, daddy loves you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.77,0:02:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好记住\N{\rEng}Just remember that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.26,0:02:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸一直都爱你\N{\rEng}He always loved you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.87,0:03:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马\N{\rEng}Whoo, Obama!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.78,0:03:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚出去\N{\rEng}Get outta here!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.86,0:03:09.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  有没看到我爸妈\N{\rEng}Dude, have you seen my parents?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.39,0:03:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  大家都在街上狂欢呢\N{\rEng}No, everyone's out partying in the streets.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.18,0:03:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你弟弟怎么了  \N{\rEng}What's wrong with your brother? 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.43,0:03:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是麦凯恩的支持者\N{\rEng}He was a McCain supporter.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.49,0:03:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  艾克  奥巴马能行的\N{\rEng}It's okay, Ike. Obama will do fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.60,0:03:23.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(400,230,190,230)}凌晨1:10
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.76,0:03:26.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(190,230)}凌晨1:10
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.31,0:03:26.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(190,230,0,230)}凌晨1:10
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.84,0:03:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总统阁下  看这边  \N{\rEng}Mr. President! Over here! 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.03,0:03:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝贺您  阁下\N{\rEng}Congratulations, sir!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.95,0:03:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-干得好  -变革\N{\rEng}- Great job. - Change.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.55,0:03:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得漂亮  总统阁下\N{\rEng}Great job, Mr. President! 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.64,0:03:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得漂亮  奥巴马\N{\rEng}Great job, Obama.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.86,0:03:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢诸位的支持 \N{\rEng}Thank you all for your support. 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.25,0:03:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若不介意\N{\rEng}If you don't mind,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.40,0:03:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想利用余下的时间\N{\rEng}I'm gonna spend the rest of the evening
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.61,0:03:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做些必要的休整\N{\rEng}getting some much needed rest.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.90,0:03:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麦凯恩议员\N{\rEng}Senator McCain?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.47,0:03:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马总统\N{\rEng}President Obama.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.44,0:03:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-轰  宝贝  -轰  宝贝\N{\rEng}- Boom, baby! - Boom, baby!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.90,0:03:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟  太完美了  \N{\rEng}Man, that was perfect! 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.60,0:03:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还担心咱俩会不分上下呢\N{\rEng}I almost thought we were gonna tie for a minute there.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.92,0:03:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话就砸了\N{\rEng}That would have screwed us.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.35,0:04:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把握得很完美  不可能平手\N{\rEng}You played it perfectly. There was no way.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.48,0:04:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是麦凯恩  我们成功了\N{\rEng}It's McCain. We did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.86,0:04:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马是总统\N{\rEng}Obama is president.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.89,0:04:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说了\N{\rEng}Yeah, so I've heard.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.06,0:04:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们简直太疯了  知道吗\N{\rEng}You guys are out of your freaking minds, you know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.44,0:04:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道  集合其他队员\N{\rEng}Yes, we do. Assemble the rest of the team.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.70,0:04:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只剩十个小时\N{\rEng}We've only got ten hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.90,0:04:13.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白  最难的都过去了吧\N{\rEng}Sure. Hard part's over, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.73,0:04:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  最难的现在才开始\N{\rEng}Actually, the hard part's just starting.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.85,0:04:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马  奥巴马  奥巴马\N{\rEng}Obama! Obama! Obama!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.16,0:04:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 庆祝好巴马  来吧 *\N{\rEng}* Celebrate good Obama, come on! *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.57,0:04:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 就是奥巴马 *\N{\rEng}* It's Obama, Obama. *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.11,0:04:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*庆祝好时光  来吧*\N{\rEng}* Celebrate good Defaults, come on! *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.83,0:04:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  我要进行噪音投诉\N{\rEng}Yes, I'd like to make a noise complaint.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.93,0:04:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 谁把狗放出来了 *\N{\rEng}* Who let the dogs out? *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.30,0:04:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 谁把狗放出来了 *  \N{\rEng}* Who let the dogs out? * 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.46,0:04:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马\N{\rEng}Obama!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.89,0:04:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 谁把奥巴马放出来了 *\N{\rEng}* Who let the Obama out? *
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.61,0:05:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 谁把狗放出来了 *  \N{\rEng}* Who let the dogs out? *
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.82,0:05:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察来了耶\N{\rEng}Oh, police are here!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.13,0:05:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  大伙  该散场了\N{\rEng}Okay, people. Default to disperse.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.57,0:05:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狂欢结束了\N{\rEng}Party's over.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.94,0:05:17.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-要狂欢  -奥巴马\N{\rEng}- Party!  - Obama!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.49,0:05:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  都回家吧\N{\rEng}Come on. Default to go home.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.70,0:05:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是麦凯恩的支持者吗\N{\rEng}What are you, a McCain voter?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.05,0:05:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就是  -就是\N{\rEng}- Yeah! - Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.10,0:05:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  老弟\N{\rEng}Sorry, pal. 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.55,0:05:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在奥巴马才是总统\N{\rEng}But Obama's president now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.13,0:05:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马  奥巴马\N{\rEng}Obama! Obama!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.08,0:05:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马  奥巴马  \N{\rEng}Obama! Obama!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.82,0:05:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掀了警车\N{\rEng}Flip the cop car!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.92,0:05:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我的车放下\N{\rEng}Hey! Put down my car!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.66,0:05:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  我们可以  -是的  我们可以\N{\rEng}- Yes, we can! - Yes, we can!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.25,0:05:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手\N{\rEng}Hey, stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.39,0:05:46.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我滴个神哦\N{\rEng}Jesus Christ.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.97,0:05:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 奥巴马  你真好你真好  你打动我的心 *\N{\rEng}* Obama, you're so fine, You're so fine you blow my mind. *
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.99,0:05:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 奥巴马  奥巴马 *\N{\rEng}* Hey Obama, Hey Obama *
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.57,0:05:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要买电视吗\N{\rEng}Hey, you guys wanna buy a TV?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.20,0:06:08.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(400,230,190,230)}上午2:15
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.36,0:06:10.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(190,230)}上午2:15
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.91,0:06:11.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(190,230,0,230)}上午2:15
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.83,0:06:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了  奥巴马和麦凯恩\N{\rEng}Bravo, Obama and McCain.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.13,0:06:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们为这个计划筹备了十年\N{\rEng}Ten years, you two have been working
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.86,0:06:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在终于顺利完成了\N{\rEng}on this plan and you finally pulled it off.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.02,0:06:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们  大家都是老相识了\N{\rEng}Guys, we've all known each other a long Default,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.24,0:06:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都曾一起出生入死\N{\rEng}had many incredible adventures,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.96,0:06:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这将是我们最伟大的杰作\N{\rEng}but this is going to be our greatest feat ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.14,0:06:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道\N{\rEng}I knew it!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.31,0:06:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们去竞选总统\N{\rEng}I knew when you two ran for president. 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.16,0:06:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是迂回战术\N{\rEng}You were just working an angle.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.88,0:06:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向来如此\N{\rEng}Always working the angles.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.02,0:06:36.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友们  举国上下\N{\rEng}My friends, while the entire country 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.97,0:06:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都在为选举忙碌时\N{\rEng}is busy reacting to the election,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.84,0:06:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们将完成人类史上最强的盗窃\N{\rEng}we are about to pull off the greatest heist in human history.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.16,0:06:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就快跟我们讲讲\N{\rEng}So, come on. Enlighten us.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.38,0:06:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这次要偷什么\N{\rEng}What are we stealing this Default?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.67,0:06:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望钻石\N{\rEng}The Hope diamond.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.04,0:06:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,位列世界\N{\rEng}Rated number four 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.09,0:06:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十大名贵钻石之四\N{\rEng}of the ten most precious diamonds in the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.06,0:07:01.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中东市场价值为\N{\rEng}Going street value, Middle Eastern Market, of course,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.19,0:07:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2.1亿美元\N{\rEng}$210 million.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.49,0:07:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2.1\N{\rEng}210?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.70,0:07:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亿元\N{\rEng}Million.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.98,0:07:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\rEng}No, no, no,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.93,0:07:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望钻石偷不了\N{\rEng}the Hope diamond is ungettable.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.53,0:07:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地球贼都知道\N{\rEng}Every thief in the world knows that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.59,0:07:13.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几乎偷不了\N{\rEng}Almost ungettable.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.53,0:07:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钻石存放于\N{\rEng}The diamond is kept 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.50,0:07:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史密森尼自然博物馆\N{\rEng}in the Smithsonian Natural History Museum,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.37,0:07:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公认的最能防贼的建筑\N{\rEng}long considered to be the most thief-proof structure ever built.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.75,0:07:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钻石展室的墙\N{\rEng}The diamond wing is protected
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.15,0:07:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嵌着两英尺厚的钢板\N{\rEng}by impenetrable walls of two-foot wide steel.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.27,0:07:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东北侧有7-5激光系统\N{\rEng}On the northeast side, a seven-five laser system.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.33,0:07:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史密森尼\N{\rEng}There is simply no side 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.32,0:07:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可说是密不透风\N{\rEng}of the Smithsonian that can be breached.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.76,0:07:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就从屋顶进去\N{\rEng}So you go in from the roof.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.23,0:07:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从顶部下去  \N{\rEng}Drop into it from the top. 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.78,0:07:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能从顶部下去\N{\rEng}Can't get to it from the top.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.86,0:07:37.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顶部是聚合物顶棚\N{\rEng}Because a polymer shelf runs the entire expanse.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.41,0:07:39.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  四面密不透风\N{\rEng}Okay, you can't get into the museum from any side
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.70,0:07:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顶部又无懈可击\N{\rEng}and you can't drop in from above.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.15,0:07:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就偷不了钻石\N{\rEng}So you can't get the diamond.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.51,0:07:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隆重介绍总统逃生隧道\N{\rEng}Meet the presidential escape tunnel.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.22,0:07:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一条供总统从白宫\N{\rEng}A two-mile long underground passage
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.07,0:07:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接逃往城外的\N{\rEng}that runs from the White House to a location 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.69,0:07:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两英里长地下隧道\N{\rEng}outside the city limits in case of an attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.66,0:07:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一入口就在总统办公室\N{\rEng}The tunnel is only accessible from the Oval Office
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.35,0:07:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且正好经过\N{\rEng}and just happens to travel...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.02,0:08:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史密森尼自然博物馆下方\N{\rEng}right underneath the Smithsonian National History Museum.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.24,0:08:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-轰  宝贝  -轰  宝贝\N{\rEng}- Boom, baby. - Boom, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.11,0:08:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先安排人进隧道\N{\rEng}You get somebody in the tunnel, 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.73,0:08:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后炸个缺口\N{\rEng}they can blast into the museum
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.24,0:08:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再让其他人进去\N{\rEng}let the others in.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.48,0:08:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情便水到渠成\N{\rEng}The heist is on.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.19,0:08:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都去竞选总统  \N{\rEng}So you both run for president, 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.91,0:08:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就为了让一人获胜\N{\rEng}because one of you has to win
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.74,0:08:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后才能进入隧道\N{\rEng}and you've got your access to the tunnel.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.09,0:08:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还演绎了残酷角逐\N{\rEng}And we run a particularly brutal campaign
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.70,0:08:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来8个多小时\N{\rEng}so that the nation is as distracted as possible
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.82,0:08:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,举国都会因此分心\N{\rEng} over the next eight hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.92,0:08:24.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来都很惊险\N{\rEng}This all sounds very risky.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.03,0:08:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们花了十年时间筹备计划\N{\rEng}We've spent ten years putting this plan together.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.52,0:08:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们真的是世界顶尖窃贼团体\N{\rEng}If we are indeed the greatest thief club in the world
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.13,0:08:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们确实是\N{\rEng}and we are.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.63,0:08:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不会被捉住\N{\rEng}We won't get caught.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.80,0:08:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我想找我爸妈\N{\rEng}Yes, I'm trying to locate my parents.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.43,0:08:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫凯尔·布洛夫斯基\N{\rEng}My name is Kyle Broflovski.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.00,0:08:41.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道奥巴马赢了\N{\rEng}Yes, I know Obama won.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.12,0:08:43.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  快出来一下\N{\rEng}Kyle. Kyle, you gotta get out here!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.86,0:08:44.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.18,0:08:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你弟弟爬到窗外\N{\rEng}Your little brother's climbed out of the window.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.59,0:08:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他好像想跳下去\N{\rEng}I think he's going to jump!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.11,0:08:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐\N{\rEng}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.25,0:08:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾克  别这样 \N{\rEng}Ike, don't do it! 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.59,0:08:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生活还有很多美好的东西\N{\rEng}There's still so much to live for.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.60,0:09:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你很希望麦凯恩当选\N{\rEng}I know you really wanted McCain to win,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.38,0:09:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但一切都会好的\N{\rEng}but it's going to be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.90,0:09:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  那不是真的  艾克\N{\rEng}No, that's not true, Ike.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.31,0:09:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马的计划会让经济保持平稳的\N{\rEng}The economy could easily stabilize with Obama's plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.79,0:09:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾克  别跳\N{\rEng}Ike, don't jump!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.04,0:09:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会扭伤脚踝的\N{\rEng}You could really hurt your ankle or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.07,0:09:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的  艾克\N{\rEng}Really, Ike, 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.46,0:09:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里有五英尺高呢  \N{\rEng}that's like five feet off the ground. 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.84,0:09:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跳\N{\rEng}Don't do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.93,0:09:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永别了\N{\rEng}Goodbye!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.37,0:09:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  -不\N{\rEng}- No! - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.86,0:09:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾克\N{\rEng}Ike?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.23,0:09:30.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕  艾克\N{\rEng}Oh, crap. Ike?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.40,0:09:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  我一会下班\N{\rEng}All right, everyone. I'm turning in for the night.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.68,0:09:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三队  执行标准安全方案\N{\rEng}Go to standard security, team three.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.68,0:09:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官  我们遇到点麻烦\N{\rEng}Sir! Sir, we have a bit of a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.99,0:09:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -新总统当选人来了\N{\rEng}- What? - The new president-elect is here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.30,0:09:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想进入总统办公室\N{\rEng}He wants in to the Oval Office.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.29,0:09:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝拉克·奥巴马\N{\rEng}Barack Obama?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.98,0:09:57.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前面就是了  阁下\N{\rEng}They're all right through here, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.40,0:10:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您好  请问有何能为您效劳  \N{\rEng}Hello. Is there something we can do for you,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.39,0:10:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马先生\N{\rEng}Mr. Obama?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.66,0:10:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是来看看新住所\N{\rEng}Just checking out the new digs.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.48,0:10:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同志们辛苦了\N{\rEng}How are you guys?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.47,0:10:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为人民服务\N{\rEng}Good, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.03,0:10:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想看看总统办公室  劳驾\N{\rEng}I'd like to see the Oval Office, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.20,0:10:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在吗\N{\rEng}Right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.49,0:10:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从不浪费时间  先生们\N{\rEng}I don't waste Default, gentlemen.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.99,0:10:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只有2个月时间考虑如何重整\N{\rEng}I've only got 2 months to figure out how I want to redecorate,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.69,0:10:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理解吧\N{\rEng}if you know what I mean.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.86,0:10:18.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,譬如说  换换窗帘什么的\N{\rEng}You know, change the drapes and stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.25,0:10:23.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  这边请  总统阁下\N{\rEng}Sure. Right this way, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.06,0:10:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要打扰我  明白吗\N{\rEng}I will need absolute privacy. Is that understood?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.97,0:10:28.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  先生\N{\rEng}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.33,0:10:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了\N{\rEng}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.59,0:10:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得了100美元耶\N{\rEng}I got $100!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.07,0:10:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  麦凯恩  我进来了\N{\rEng}All right, McCain. I'm in.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.37,0:10:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得漂亮  B\N{\rEng}Nicely done, B.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.74,0:10:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在史密森尼外准备好了\N{\rEng}We're in position outside the Smithsonian.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.80,0:10:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找到逃生隧道没\N{\rEng}You find the escape tunnel?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.61,0:10:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经在找了\N{\rEng}I'm already on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.32,0:10:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轰  宝贝\N{\rEng}Boom, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.27,0:10:58.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变革\N{\rEng}Change!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.61,0:11:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-变革  -变革\N{\rEng}- Change! - Change!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.06,0:11:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  我们有麻烦了\N{\rEng}Dad, Dad, we have a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.64,0:11:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会再有麻烦了  一切都不同了\N{\rEng}Not anymore we don't. Everything's different now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.15,0:11:07.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  老爸  我们得送凯尔的弟弟上医院\N{\rEng}No, Dad, we gotta take Kyle's brother to the hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.45,0:11:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不用再看富人脸色过日子了\N{\rEng}We don't have to take crap from the rich fat cats anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.35,0:11:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  他醉了\N{\rEng}Dude, he's wasted.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.74,0:11:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我老板  喂  老板\N{\rEng}Hey, it's my boss! Hey, boss!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.96,0:11:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  马什\N{\rEng}Oh, hello Marsh!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.56,0:11:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我日你丫的\N{\rEng}Yeah, you know what? Fuck you!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.90,0:11:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  你丫这坨狗屎\N{\rEng}You heard me, you fucking piece of shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.72,0:11:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终于能说出对你的想法了\N{\rEng}I can finally tell you what I think of you,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.27,0:11:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操你丫的混蛋\N{\rEng}fucking asshole.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.60,0:11:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  你在干嘛\N{\rEng}Dad, what are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.03,0:11:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  斯坦  一切都变了\N{\rEng}It's okay, Stan! Everything's changed.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.16,0:11:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不再需要这份傻逼工作了\N{\rEng}I don't need his stupid fucking job anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.97,0:11:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这狗日的  你这坨狗屎\N{\rEng}You're a fucking assfuck, you piece of shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.65,0:11:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道奥巴马怎么说的吗  \N{\rEng}You know what Obama said? 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.26,0:11:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"是的  我们可以"\N{\rEng}"Yes, we can!"
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.19,0:11:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是奥巴马的支持者  \N{\rEng}Hey, I voted for Obama!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.23,0:11:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马没说你行\N{\rEng}Obama's not talking about you!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.57,0:11:48.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人能帮我吗\N{\rEng}Can someone help us?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.57,0:11:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我弟弟从窗口摔下来了\N{\rEng}My little brother fell out the window!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.60,0:11:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想向对选举结果\N{\rEng}I just want to say to everyone 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.07,0:11:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些失望的诸位说\N{\rEng}who's a little disappointed that we lost the election,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.24,0:12:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有明年\N{\rEng}that there's always next year!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.34,0:12:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许2009年我会再次竞选副总统\N{\rEng}Maybe I'll run for vice president again in 2009!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.91,0:12:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佩林女士  您有约翰·麦凯恩的消息吗\N{\rEng}Mrs. Palin, have you seen or heard from John McCain?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.79,0:12:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  我不知道他去哪了\N{\rEng}No, I don't really know where he went.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.10,0:12:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有点奇怪  但\N{\rEng}Kind of seems a little odd, I guess, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.63,0:12:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我电话响了\N{\rEng}Oh, my phone's going ringy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.47,0:12:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失陪一会\N{\rEng}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.49,0:12:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\rEng}Hello!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.64,0:12:24.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  莎拉  我是麦凯恩\N{\rEng}Hello, Sarah. It's McCain.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.94,0:12:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你告诉我\N{\rEng}I hope to God you're calling to tell me
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.74,0:12:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们带着L-7炸药在金库下就位了\N{\rEng}you're in position below the vault with the L-7 charges?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.13,0:12:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经在隧道里了  莎拉\N{\rEng}I'm in the tunnel now, Sarah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.53,0:12:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该快到博物馆下方了\N{\rEng}Should be almost below the museum.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.37,0:12:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炸隧道时\N{\rEng}Just make sure 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.15,0:12:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得别把变压器也炸了\N{\rEng}you don't blow the transformers along with the tunnel
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.23,0:12:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会拉响5-4激光系统\N{\rEng}because it will trigger the 5-4 laser system.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.29,0:12:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不能破坏任何耦合线\N{\rEng}And don't damage any coupling wires
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.03,0:12:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则加勒特关闭电路时会功亏一篑\N{\rEng}or it'll be worthless when Garrett shuts down the grid.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.13,0:12:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我30分钟后到  \N{\rEng}I'll be there in 30. 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.82,0:12:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  她真麻利\N{\rEng}God, she's awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.66,0:12:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麦凯恩议员要接我回阿拉斯加\N{\rEng}I guess Senator McCain's gonna fly me back to Alaska now.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.27,0:12:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有架私人飞机\N{\rEng}He's got a private jet, you know. 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.16,0:12:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了\N{\rEng}Okay. Bye-bye, then!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.62,0:12:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白痴透顶\N{\rEng}Bloody idiots.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.09,0:13:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  我们开始\N{\rEng}All right. Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.36,0:13:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么声音\N{\rEng}What's that noise?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.86,0:13:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  外面在施工\N{\rEng}It's okay. Just some construction outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.27,0:13:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙\N{\rEng}Oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.67,0:13:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麦凯恩\N{\rEng}McCain,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.07,0:13:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有麻烦了\N{\rEng}we've got a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.00,0:13:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚持住  艾克  我们去找人帮忙\N{\rEng}Hang in there, Ike. We're gonna get you help.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.05,0:13:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边有些人\N{\rEng}There's some people.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.37,0:13:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都听着  往后退  往后退\N{\rEng}Listen! Stay back! Stay back!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.97,0:13:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,避难所里没有位置了\N{\rEng}We don't have any more room in the ark!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.56,0:13:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得让我们进去\N{\rEng}You have to let us in.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.71,0:13:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这国家要完了\N{\rEng}You know the country is doomed.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.03,0:13:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你凭什么赶我们走\N{\rEng}Who are you to turn us away?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.79,0:13:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我建了这座碉堡以防麦凯恩落选\N{\rEng}I built this bunker in case McCain lost!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.96,0:13:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里装不下所有人\N{\rEng}There isn't enough room for everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.19,0:13:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰啦  我们需要帮助\N{\rEng}Hey, excuse me, but we need some help.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.82,0:13:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  但里面已经没地儿了\N{\rEng}I know you do, but there's no more room, I tell ya!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.67,0:14:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你连他们也要拒绝吗\N{\rEng}You're going to deny them, too?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.68,0:14:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看在上帝的份上  他们还是孩子啊\N{\rEng}God sake's man, they're children!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.90,0:14:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着他们的眼睛说你不让他们进去\N{\rEng}Look them in the eyes and tell them you won't take them in.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.83,0:14:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看他们稚嫩的脸颊  \N{\rEng}Look at their little cheeks! 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.63,0:14:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把手拿开  傻逼\N{\rEng}Let go of my face, asshole.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.39,0:14:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  该死的  小孩可以进来\N{\rEng}All right, damn you. The children can come in!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.56,0:14:14.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们才不想进你的傻逼鸟棚\N{\rEng}We don't want in your stupid shelter.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.51,0:14:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那我要他们的位置  -我也是\N{\rEng}- Okay, then I want their place. - Me, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.73,0:14:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要搭车到医院\N{\rEng}We need to get a ride to the hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.65,0:14:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有医院了  你们还不明白吗\N{\rEng}There isn't going to be a hospital. Don't you get it?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.97,0:14:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快让我们进去\N{\rEng}Let us in now!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.85,0:14:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝啊  真的发生了  社会要崩溃了\N{\rEng}Jeez. It's already happening. Society's breaking down.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.55,0:14:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马当选还没四小时\N{\rEng}Obama hasn't been elected four hours
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.60,0:14:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这国家已经如同炼狱\N{\rEng}and already the country is going to hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.27,0:14:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马先生  先生\N{\rEng}Mr. Obama? Sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.56,0:14:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  把钥匙给我\N{\rEng}All right. Give me the keys.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.39,0:14:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事吗  先生们\N{\rEng}Is there a problem, gentlemen?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.13,0:14:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  先生  里面一切正常吗\N{\rEng}No. No, sir. Everything okay in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.66,0:14:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会不正常呢   \N{\rEng}Why wouldn't it be?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.05,0:14:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉  但我说过要独处\N{\rEng}I'm sorry, but I asked to be left alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.34,0:15:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  先生  只是您妻子来了\N{\rEng}Yes, sir. It's just that your wife is here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.10,0:15:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妻子\N{\rEng}My wife?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.12,0:15:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝拉克  大家都在找你呢\N{\rEng}Barack, everyone's been looking for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.27,0:15:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底在干什么\N{\rEng}What on earth are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.58,0:15:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来吧  亲爱的  \N{\rEng}Come on in, darling. 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.81,0:15:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢各位\N{\rEng}Thank you, boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.33,0:15:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝拉克  快告诉我怎么回事\N{\rEng}Okay, Barack. Tell me what's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.80,0:15:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米歇尔  有些事我得告诉你\N{\rEng}Michelle, there's something I need to tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.41,0:15:21.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事\N{\rEng}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.56,0:15:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝拉克  什么事\N{\rEng}Barack, what is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.94,0:15:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保护钻石的激光系统\N{\rEng}The laser system guarding the diamond
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.64,0:15:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三天前换成了光学防盗系统\N{\rEng}was replaced by an optical relay three days ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.81,0:15:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑\N{\rEng}You gotta be kidding me!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.62,0:15:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说金库进不去了\N{\rEng}So the entire diamond vault is inaccessible?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.27,0:15:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麦凯恩在线吗\N{\rEng}Is McCain online?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.32,0:15:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  米歇尔\N{\rEng}Hi, Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.52,0:15:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们怎么不检查安保系统更新记录\N{\rEng}Your guys weren't running update checks on the security logs?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.67,0:15:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米歇尔  我们要你\N{\rEng}Michelle, we need you 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.78,0:15:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新破解金库防盗系统\N{\rEng}to do a different scan hack to the vault relay.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.76,0:15:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一小时内破解新系统  你疯了吗\N{\rEng}On a new system, in an hour? Are you nuts?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.63,0:15:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的工作是跟这个大汉假结婚\N{\rEng}My job was to pretend to be married to this bozo
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.05,0:15:53.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后帮你们仨破解激光系统\N{\rEng}and get you three scan hacks into a laser system.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.55,0:15:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米歇尔  我是莎拉\N{\rEng}Michelle, it's Sarah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.62,0:15:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们确实换了激光系统  \N{\rEng}They did replace the laser system, 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.38,0:15:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也不是啥新牌子\N{\rEng}but the new one isn't brand new.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.59,0:15:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是老式H-7系列  \N{\rEng}It's an old H-7 series. 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.91,0:16:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你30分钟就能破解这玩意\N{\rEng}You can break this baby in 30 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.96,0:16:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫戴维斯给我一个转换发射器\N{\rEng}Tell Davis to get me a fortrans emitter
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.94,0:16:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有足够发电的脉冲驱动\N{\rEng}and enough pulse drives to light a spark.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.78,0:16:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到了吧  戴维斯\N{\rEng}You catch that, Davis?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.25,0:16:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这就去\N{\rEng}I'm on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.00,0:16:12.50,Default,NTP,0000,0010,0180,,{\c&H000000&\fs18}狱通        医院
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.89,0:16:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们到了  艾克  你会没事的\N{\rEng}We made it, Ike. You're going to be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.77,0:16:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去那边坐着\N{\rEng}There! Just take a seat over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.92,0:16:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,劳驾  我弟弟需要治疗\N{\rEng}Excuse me. My little brother needs medical attention.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.47,0:16:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是奥巴马支持者还是麦凯恩支持者\N{\rEng}Was he an Obama supporter or an McCain supporter?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.25,0:16:31.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这有啥关系\N{\rEng}Why does that matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.63,0:16:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们要知道他是狂欢过度\N{\rEng}Because they don't know if he partied too hard
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.26,0:16:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是自杀未遂\N{\rEng}or if he tried to kill himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.17,0:16:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护士  拜托\N{\rEng}Ma'am, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.75,0:16:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我弟弟需要立即治疗\N{\rEng}I think my little brother needs immediate help!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.97,0:16:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不懂  孩子  现在只有两个医生在值班\N{\rEng}You don't understand, kid. There's only two doctors on call.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.03,0:16:50.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而威尔逊医生正在街上狂欢\N{\rEng}And Dr. Wilson is out celebrating in the streets somewhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.14,0:16:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那另一个医生呢\N{\rEng}So where's the other doctor?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.40,0:16:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来啊  大伙儿\N{\rEng}Hey, come on, people!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.17,0:17:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还可以接着狂欢\N{\rEng}We can keep partying, can't we?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.43,0:17:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我们可以\N{\rEng}Yes, we can!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.45,0:17:04.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  歌唱吧\N{\rEng}Come on, let's sing!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.50,0:17:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 奥巴马 你只付出  不求回报 * \N{\rEng}* Obama, well you came and you gave without taking*
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.79,0:17:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-闭嘴  -* 但我却赶你走  奥巴马 *\N{\rEng}- Shut up! - * But I sent you away, Obama, *
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.27,0:17:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 当你吻我  让我不再颤抖 *\N{\rEng}* When you kissed me, And stopped me from shaking, *
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.51,0:17:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 但我却赶你走 *\N{\rEng}* But I sent you away, Obama, *
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.25,0:17:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我快搞定了\N{\rEng}I've almost got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.55,0:17:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只有五分钟时间\N{\rEng}You're only going to have five minutes,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.37,0:17:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白吗\N{\rEng}do you understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.63,0:17:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的不喜欢假结婚吗\N{\rEng}Did you really not like pretending to be married?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.09,0:17:31.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝啊  现在不是时候  B\N{\rEng}Oh, Jesus. Now is not the Default, B.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.54,0:17:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  你得承认我们开心过\N{\rEng}Come on, you have to admit we had some fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.93,0:17:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我女儿需要比世界级\N{\rEng}My girls need somebody better than 
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.01,0:17:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钻石大盗更好的爸爸\N{\rEng}a world class diamond thief.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.70,0:17:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  好了  搞定\N{\rEng}Wait, there, I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.34,0:17:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  各位  我们准备行动\N{\rEng}All right, everyone. We're about to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.77,0:17:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以下为新的计划\N{\rEng}So here's the revised schedule.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.56,0:17:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,临晨4:40  \N{\rEng}4:40 AM, 
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.76,0:17:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,队伍在博物馆西北出口集合\N{\rEng}the team gathers at the northwest exit of the museum.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.11,0:17:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,临晨4:45 米歇尔破解光学防盗系统\N{\rEng}4:45 AM, Michelle hacks the optical relay,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.54,0:17:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就能进入后门\N{\rEng}allowing me access to the rear doors.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.60,0:17:51.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行动\N{\rEng}Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.50,0:17:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4:46  我从里面把门打开\N{\rEng}4:46, from inside, I can open the doors
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.83,0:17:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让其余的人进来\N{\rEng}and let in the rest of the crew.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.43,0:17:59.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凌晨5:10  在电力总部\N{\rEng}5:10 a.m., at the Department of Power,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.24,0:18:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昆西关闭电路\N{\rEng}Quincy shuts down the grid,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.11,0:18:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切断金库电源\N{\rEng}disabling power to the vault room.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.29,0:18:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5:12  我周一假死的奶奶\N{\rEng}5:12, my grandmother who faked her death on Monday
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.53,0:18:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打电话给博物馆说有炸弹\N{\rEng}calls in a bomb threat to the museum.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.29,0:18:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说我在你们楼里放了炸弹  没错\N{\rEng}I said I put a bomb in your building, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.67,0:18:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5:13  警卫打开西南门\N{\rEng}5:13, the guards open the southwest door,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.00,0:18:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排查馆内炸弹\N{\rEng}checking the museum for any bombs.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.49,0:18:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5:14  麦凯恩装扮成榄球运动员\N{\rEng}5:14, McCain, dressed as a football player,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.80,0:18:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进入安全中心  关掉钻石箱的警报\N{\rEng}enters security and shuts off the diamond case alarm.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.80,0:18:27.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  站住\N{\rEng}Hey, you! Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.08,0:18:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和米歇尔回到隧道\N{\rEng}Michelle and I head back into the tunnel
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.44,0:18:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把洞口糊好\N{\rEng}and the hole is patched.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.67,0:18:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凌晨5:15  我走出总统办公室\N{\rEng}5:15 a.m., I walk out of the Oval Office
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.00,0:18:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钻石安全地藏在我菊花里\N{\rEng}with the diamond securely hidden in my anus.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.56,0:18:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完事儿  谢谢\N{\rEng}All done, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.02,0:18:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-轰  宝贝  -轰  宝贝\N{\rEng}- Boom, baby! - Boom, baby!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.84,0:18:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一件事\N{\rEng}But just one thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.46,0:18:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们就这么消失了\N{\rEng}Don't you think people are going to 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.08,0:18:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们不会起疑吗\N{\rEng}be suspicious when you disappear?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.62,0:18:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道不会找你们吗\N{\rEng}Go looking for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.98,0:19:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们几个月前就请了人办这事\N{\rEng}We hired a guy for that a couple months ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.45,0:19:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞啥飞机\N{\rEng}What the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.40,0:19:27.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs10\c&H000000&\pos(245,140)}法医办公室\N非工作人员\N请勿入
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.17,0:19:34.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\c&H0000FF&}{\fscx300,\fscy100)}死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.26,0:19:36.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\c&H0000FF&}{\fscx300,\fscy100)}死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.18,0:19:37.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\c&H0000FF&}{\fscx300,\fscy100)}死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.20,0:19:38.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\c&H0000FF&}{\fscx300,\fscy100)}死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.10,0:19:39.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\c&H0000FF&}{\fscx300,\fscy100)}死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.90,0:19:40.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\c&H0000FF&}{\fscx300,\fscy100)}死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.80,0:19:41.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\c&H0000FF&}{\fscx300,\fscy100)}死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.01,0:19:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾克\N{\rEng}Ike?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.61,0:19:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轰  宝贝\N{\rEng}Boom, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.34,0:20:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你们团的机票  桑切斯先生\N{\rEng}Here are all the tickets for your group, Mr. Sanchez.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.24,0:20:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢\N{\rEng}Thank you very much.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.26,0:20:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友们  出发吧\N{\rEng}Well, friends, let us depart.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.00,0:20:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们走吧\N{\rEng}Hey, uh. You guys go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.43,0:20:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是来道别的\N{\rEng}I just came to say goodbye.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.84,0:20:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.20,0:20:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我决定金盆洗手\N{\rEng}I've decided to hang it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.49,0:20:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试试当个总统\N{\rEng}Maybe give this president thing a shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.88,0:20:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,B  你在开玩笑吧\N{\rEng}B, you can't be serious.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.69,0:20:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经死在落基山脉的飞机上了 知道吗\N{\rEng}Besides, you died in a jet in the Rocky Mountains, remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.26,0:20:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能说没赶上那架飞机\N{\rEng}Could have been I didn't make that flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.73,0:20:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么看  米歇尔\N{\rEng}What do you say, Michelle?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.02,0:20:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你愿意和女儿\N{\rEng}Would you and your girls 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.07,0:20:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我一起搬到白宫吗\N{\rEng}like to move into the White House with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.78,0:20:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,定居下来\N{\rEng}You know, settle down.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.91,0:20:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做做总统和第一夫人\N{\rEng}Just be President and First Lady for a while?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.00,0:20:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说真的\N{\rEng}You're serious.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.58,0:20:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢  也许我们真能变革一下\N{\rEng}Who knows, maybe we could change a few things.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.26,0:20:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得呢\N{\rEng}What do you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.96,0:20:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱咋咋地吧\N{\rEng}What the fuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.98,0:20:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就喜欢大团圆结局\N{\rEng}I just love happy endings.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.34,0:21:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都还在\N{\rEng}It's still here.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.05,0:21:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都还在\N{\rEng}It's all still here!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.78,0:21:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是不是说明我们反应过度了\N{\rEng}Does that mean maybe we overreacted?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.95,0:21:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不觉得\N{\rEng}No, no. I wouldn't say that.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.56,0:21:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是也许\N{\rEng}It's just maybe,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.34,0:21:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许奥巴马也不错\N{\rEng}maybe Obama will be all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.06,0:21:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的裤子哪去了\N{\rEng}Hey, where are my pants?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.24,0:21:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的电视机呢\N{\rEng}Where's our TV?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.78,0:21:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的裤子和电视呢\N{\rEng}Where are my pants and where's my TV?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:32.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  你老板打电话说你被炒了\N{\rEng}Dad, your boss called. He said you're fired.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.50,0:21:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的\N{\rEng}Goddammit!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.43,0:21:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥巴马说一切都会改变\N{\rEng}Obama said things would be different.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那狗日的骗我们\N{\rEng}That son of a bitch lied to us!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.73,0:21:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早知道我该投给麦凯恩\N{\rEng}I knew I should have voted for McCain.
