[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2008-10-10 06:38:08
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayDepth: 0
PlayResX: 1916
PlayResY: 1076
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 2
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H19000000,&H000E0300,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,2,2,134,120,68,1
Style: eng,Microsoft YaHei,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,26,1
Style: Top,微软雅黑,10,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Git,Comic Sans MS,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Chn,微软雅黑,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Eng,Comic Sans MS,60,&H002AF7FF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.00,0:00:10.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm going down to south park\N gonna have myself a time 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.85,0:00:14.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Friendly faces everywhere\N humble folks without temptation 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.13,0:00:16.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Going down to south park\N gonna leave my woes behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.52,0:00:20.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ample parking day or night\N people shouting howdy neighbor
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.76,0:00:23.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heading on out to south park\N gonna see if I can't unwind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.34,0:00:27.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I like girls with big vaginas\N I like girls with big fat titties
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.41,0:00:30.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.00,0:21:45.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0060,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译制作\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}YYeTs人人影视字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.62,0:21:46.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}cam小池
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.47,0:21:47.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}校对\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.23,0:21:47.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0050,,{\1c&HFDC282&}后期\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}csbeyond
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.91,0:21:48.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0060,,{\1c&HFDC282&}总监\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.00,0:00:31.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0150,,{\1c&HFDC282&}《南方公园》第12季  第13集\N{\rEng}South Park Season 12 Episode 13
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.00,0:00:31.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0100,,"小学歌舞青春"\N{\rEng}"Elementary School Musical"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.09,0:00:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧肯尼的午餐\N{\rEng}Look at Kenny's lunch!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.40,0:00:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一份红肠三文治和清水一杯\N{\rEng}A bologna sandwich and water!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.99,0:00:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的  老兄  你家真穷\N{\rEng}Goddamn, your family's poor, dude!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.85,0:00:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们今晚去看《歌舞青春3》吗\N{\rEng}Hey, you fellas wanna go see High School Musical 3 tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.41,0:00:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校其他人都会去重看\N{\rEng}Bunch of kids from school are gonna go see it again.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.53,0:00:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《歌舞青春3》是啥玩意\N{\rEng}What's High School Musical 3?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.59,0:00:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然就是《歌舞青春》1和2的续集啊\N{\rEng}You know, the sequel to High School Musical 1 and 2.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.27,0:00:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那《歌舞青春》1和2又是啥\N{\rEng}What's High School Musical 1 and 2?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.27,0:00:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的红肠三文治里连佐料都没有\N{\rEng}There's not even condiments on his bologna sandwich!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.17,0:01:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是《歌舞青春1》和  老兄\N{\rEng}What's High School Musical 1 and... Dude!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.19,0:01:03.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是时下小学生最热衷的电影\N{\rEng}It's only the most popular thing with kids in our age group!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.21,0:01:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上映时间你们都去哪了\N{\rEng}Yeah, where the hell have you guys been?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.68,0:01:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘鲁\N{\rEng}Peru.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.95,0:01:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我周五又去看了一遍《歌舞青春3》\N{\rEng}And then I saw High School Musical 3 again
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.77,0:01:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜猜我碰到谁了\N{\rEng}on Friday and guess who was there?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.82,0:01:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布莱登·古尔莫\N{\rEng}Bridon Guermo.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.37,0:01:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布莱登·古尔莫  他是理想的梦中情人\N{\rEng}Bridon Guermo? Oh, he's such a dream!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.58,0:01:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能和他在一起我死也甘愿\N{\rEng}I'd give anything to be with Bridon Guermo.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.29,0:01:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他从不鸟我  我是剩女\N{\rEng}But he'd never go for me, I'm nobody.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.36,0:01:23.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小红  别自怨自艾\N{\rEng}That's not true, Red.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.67,0:01:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天生我材必有用\N{\rEng}Everyone has something that makes them unique.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.10,0:01:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 天生我材必有用 *\N{\rEng}* Everyone is special in their own way *
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.86,0:01:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 跟随节奏动起来 *\N{\rEng}* Move to the beat and let your spirit out *
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.93,0:01:33.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 万众一心 *\N{\rEng}* As long as we got each other, *
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.95,0:01:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 其利断金 *\N{\rEng}* we'll never have any trouble *
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.45,0:01:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 这才是友情的真谛 *\N{\rEng}* That's what being friends is about *
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.27,0:01:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 天生我材必有用 *\N{\rEng}* Everyone is special in their own way *
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.38,0:01:44.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 无时无刻心连心 *\N{\rEng}* And we'll always be together as one *
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.36,0:01:46.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她们在干啥  -不知道\N{\rEng}- What the hell are they doing? - I have no idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.85,0:01:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 上下一心  不抛弃  不放弃 *\N{\rEng}* Back together, together we'll stay *
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.24,0:01:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 学校里的每个人 *\N{\rEng}* And every kid in school is *
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.22,0:01:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 都各有所长 *\N{\rEng}* special in their own way *
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.56,0:01:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  咋女生都变拉拉了\N{\rEng}Dude, girls are such fags.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.61,0:01:58.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 支持支持  强烈支持 *\N{\rEng}* Oh yeah, oh yeah! *
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.43,0:02:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 男生  各有个性 *\N{\rEng}* Boys are special in their own way *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.87,0:02:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 女生  各有特色 *\N{\rEng}* Girls are special like a birthday *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.30,0:02:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 我们齐跳舞  放声歌唱 *\N{\rEng}* We'll always be dancing and singing it loud *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.99,0:02:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他来了\N{\rEng}Here he comes!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.49,0:02:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 我最爱与阳光玩游戏 *\N{\rEng}* I like having fun In the hot summer sun *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.73,0:02:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 功课完心欢畅  随节奏齐舞动 *\N{\rEng}* And grooving to the beat when my homework is all done *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.96,0:02:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 如果你问我  秘诀是什么 *\N{\rEng}* If you ask me what I know... *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.54,0:02:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那小子是谁  -那是布莱登·古尔莫\N{\rEng}- Who the hell is that? - That's Bridon Guermo.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.03,0:02:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是三年级生\N{\rEng}He's just a third grader.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.29,0:02:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他的歌喉和舞技超群\N{\rEng}But he can sing and dance better than anybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.64,0:02:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《歌舞青春3》他已看过上百次了\N{\rEng}He's already seen High School Musical 3 over 100 times!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.92,0:02:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 天生我材必有用 *\N{\rEng}* Everyone is special in their own way *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.77,0:02:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-* 必有用 *  -* 随节奏 *\N{\rEng}- * Special in their own way * - * To the beat and *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.88,0:02:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 动起来 *\N{\rEng}* let your spirit out. *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.85,0:02:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 大伙儿  动起来 *\N{\rEng}* Let it out, party people *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.72,0:02:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是全场唯一的小白吗\N{\rEng}Are we the only ones here who are completely confused?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.02,0:02:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我们最好还是去看看这部戏\N{\rEng}Yeah, I guess we better check that movie out.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.54,0:02:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 你要顺应时势 *\N{\rEng}* You got to go with the status quo *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.71,0:02:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 做个随众之人 *\N{\rEng}* If you wanna be a regular Joe *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.11,0:02:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 来吧 *\N{\rEng}* Come on now *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.22,0:02:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 梦想近在咫尺 *\N{\rEng}* And your dreams are only a beat away *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.10,0:02:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 只要永不言弃 *\N{\rEng}* Don't let 'em tell you no *
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.45,0:03:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 你要顺应时势 *\N{\rEng}* You got to go with the status quo *
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.83,0:03:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 继续歌唱时势 *\N{\rEng}* Keep singing about the status quo *
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.98,0:03:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 那才是我们熟知的乐句 *\N{\rEng}* That's the phrase we know *
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.22,0:03:07.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 唱吧 *\N{\rEng}* Get down now *
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.68,0:03:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这好看吗\N{\rEng}This is cool?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.11,0:03:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 歌唱我们所知的 *\N{\rEng}* Singing about what we know *
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.45,0:03:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是给人看的吗\N{\rEng}This is cool?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.98,0:03:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们  我们真的老了\N{\rEng}We are really getting old, you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.96,0:03:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 顺应时势 *\N{\rEng}* Status quo *
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.04,0:03:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 我们一起顺应时势 *\N{\rEng}* We're all going with the status quo *
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.00,0:03:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 那才是我们的归属 *\N{\rEng}* Cuz that's where we should go *
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.17,0:03:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,介绍上说这部戏是最卖座的\N{\rEng}It says this DVD sold more copies than any DVD ever made.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.70,0:03:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第三部续集周末刚上映\N{\rEng}They just released part 3 in theaters
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.25,0:03:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首场就创下八千万票房\N{\rEng}and it made 80 million opening weekend.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.48,0:03:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  我不看了\N{\rEng}Well, I'm out, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.45,0:03:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这是时下最流行的  那我不干了\N{\rEng}If this is what's cool now, I think I'm done.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.46,0:03:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和这世界绝缘了\N{\rEng}I no longer have any connection to this world.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.51,0:03:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要回家把自己灭了\N{\rEng}I'm gonna go home and kill myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.49,0:03:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永别了  朋友\N{\rEng}Goodbye, friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.17,0:03:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不在乎这种歌舞风气有多流行\N{\rEng}I don't care how popular being like these kids becomes.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.70,0:03:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不干了  -我也不干了  肯尼呢\N{\rEng}- I'm not doing it. - I'm not doing it either. Kenny?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.32,0:03:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我干  没门\N{\rEng}No fucking way I'm doing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.72,0:03:50.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我们发誓\N{\rEng}Alright, we promise?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.56,0:03:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们向彼此郑重承诺\N{\rEng}We have to swear to each other right now
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.95,0:03:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们永不跟风\N{\rEng}we'll never become this.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.05,0:03:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我发誓  -我发誓\N{\rEng}- I swear. - I swear, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.83,0:03:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  非常好\N{\rEng}Okay. Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.70,0:04:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\rEng}What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.00,0:04:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你真去领便当呢\N{\rEng}I thought you were going to kill yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.49,0:04:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试过\N{\rEng}I tried.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.67,0:04:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走进车房  开了我妈车子的引擎\N{\rEng}Went to sleep in my mom's car in the garage
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.06,0:04:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在里头睡觉\N{\rEng}with the engine turned on.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.58,0:04:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么没死成呢\N{\rEng}But you didn't die?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.44,0:04:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天杀的混合动力车\N{\rEng}Freaking hybrids, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.63,0:04:17.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这方法再也死不成了\N{\rEng}They just don't do the trick anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.74,0:04:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  孩子们  都回到座位上\N{\rEng}All right, kids in seats. Kids in seats.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.77,0:04:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天  我们来讨论柏林墙\N{\rEng}Today, we are going to discuss the Berlin Wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.75,0:04:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这面矗立在德国的墙\N{\rEng}This was a wall in Germany
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.11,0:04:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上分割了共产主义的东柏林\N{\rEng}that actually separated the Communist east side
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.49,0:04:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和民主主义的西柏林\N{\rEng}and the democratic west side.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.99,0:04:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 东边  西边  不管你在那一边 *\N{\rEng}* East side, west side, Whatever side that you're on *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.88,0:04:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 只要将心比心 *\N{\rEng}* As long as we care about each other, *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.45,0:04:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 就能构建和谐社会 *\N{\rEng}* We can still have some fun, *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.06,0:04:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了\N{\rEng}Oh, man!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.80,0:04:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 别把对方当敌人 *\N{\rEng}* Don't sweat what you might get *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.49,0:04:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 无需紧张到流汗 *\N{\rEng}* by seeing the other side as a threat *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.48,0:04:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你这班孩子  -* 没有对错 *\N{\rEng}- Oh, you kids! - * Neither side is right or wrong *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.89,0:04:45.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 我们要学会和平共处 *\N{\rEng}* We gotta learn to all get along *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.73,0:04:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 东边  西边  这都没关系 *\N{\rEng}* East side, west side, it doesn't matter to me *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.47,0:04:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 我们要学会透过权利实行解放 *\N{\rEng}* We gotta learn to power through and set each other free *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.04,0:04:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 别在意衣着的差异 *\N{\rEng}* Don't care what other people wear *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.09,0:04:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 或发型的差异 *\N{\rEng}* or the way they like to style their hair *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.52,0:04:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 没有对错 *\N{\rEng}* Neither side is right or wrong *
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.30,0:05:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 我们该携手和平共处 *\N{\rEng}* that's why we gotta all get along *
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.12,0:05:03.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-* 西边 *  -难听死了\N{\rEng}- * West side * - God, this sucks!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.92,0:05:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 东边 *\N{\rEng}* East side *
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.16,0:05:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯坦  有没有觉得她不再是你的了\N{\rEng}Do you feel like maybe you're losing her, Stan?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.00,0:05:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\rEng}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.33,0:05:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正我也无能为力\N{\rEng}There's nothing I can do about it anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.47,0:05:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许你该和她谈谈\N{\rEng}Maybe you should just talk to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.87,0:05:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片言只语更胜千言万语\N{\rEng}You know, a little conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.77,0:05:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 对她说出你的心意 *\N{\rEng}* Tell her what you feel. *
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.58,0:05:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 有时你能感受内心有一团火 *\N{\rEng}* Sometimes you feel like there's a burning inside you *
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.18,0:05:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-*就像 *  -别唱了\N{\rEng}- * Like a-- * - Just stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.22,0:05:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\rEng}All righty then.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.57,0:05:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-温蒂  -斯坦  你好\N{\rEng}- Uh, Wendy? - Hey, Stan.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.38,0:05:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我只是想让你知道  如果你想\N{\rEng}Look, I just want you to know, if you want to,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.76,0:05:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和布莱登在一起  我会成人之美\N{\rEng}you know, be with that Bridon kid, then you should.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.95,0:05:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.85,0:05:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我意思是  你俩很般配\N{\rEng}I mean, I see the way you two are together
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.72,0:05:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想成为你的羁绊\N{\rEng}and I don't wanna be in your way.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.25,0:05:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯坦  这太可笑了\N{\rEng}Stan, that's ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.37,0:05:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\rEng}It is?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.03,0:05:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会离开你转投布莱登的怀抱的\N{\rEng}I would never leave you for Bridon.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.87,0:05:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的  -休想  那多蠢啊\N{\rEng}- Really? - No way! That'd be stupid!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.37,0:05:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和布莱登没缘分\N{\rEng}I wouldn't have a chance with Bridon.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.42,0:05:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何女孩他都手到擒来\N{\rEng}He can be with any girl he wants!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.34,0:05:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样  伙计  感觉好点了吗\N{\rEng}There you go. Feel better, pal?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.27,0:06:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要怎么做呢\N{\rEng}What am I supposed to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.64,0:06:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能眼看着\N{\rEng}I can't just sit back and watch 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.06,0:06:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那小子挖我墙角\N{\rEng}some kid steal my girlfriend away!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.24,0:06:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然温蒂说不会离我而去\N{\rEng}I mean, Wendy says she'd never leave me for him,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.63,0:06:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难保她只是在安慰我\N{\rEng}but what if she just doesn't wanna hurt my feelings?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.91,0:06:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说任何女孩  他都能手到擒来\N{\rEng}She said he could get any girl he wants
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.68,0:06:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就表示他也能抢走我的妞\N{\rEng}and that means if he wanted he could have my girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.14,0:06:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这太疯狂了\N{\rEng}This is all so crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.29,0:06:21.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么我的日子比黄连还苦\N{\rEng}I mean really, how could my day get any worse?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.96,0:06:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不会跟风的\N{\rEng}No, no, no. I'm not doing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.43,0:06:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-坚决不做  -来一曲嘛\N{\rEng}- I'm not doing it! - Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.49,0:06:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  滚开  我才不跟风\N{\rEng}No, fuck off. I'm not doing it!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.28,0:06:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真差劲  -太差劲了\N{\rEng}- That sucks. - Too bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.61,0:06:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  你真无趣\N{\rEng}Jeez. You're no fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.44,0:06:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-布莱登  你好  -你好\N{\rEng}- Hey, Bridon. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.50,0:06:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-布莱登  你好  -你好\N{\rEng}- Hi, Bridon. - Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.96,0:06:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-布莱登  你好  -你好\N{\rEng}- Hey, Bridon. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.79,0:06:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  小子  过来\N{\rEng}Hey, kid. Over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.64,0:06:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听着\N{\rEng}Hey, uh, listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.71,0:06:53.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这劲歌热舞的行为\N{\rEng}You know this whole singing and dancing thing you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.96,0:06:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你应该消停一下\N{\rEng}I think you need to... ease off a little bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.02,0:06:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着\N{\rEng}Yeah, look.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.54,0:06:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别以为学校的同学都喜欢你\N{\rEng}I know you think the kids in the school like you,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.60,0:07:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实他们烦透了\N{\rEng}but actually they're all getting really annoyed.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.88,0:07:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是这样吗  -这你有所不知\N{\rEng}- They are? - Yeah, you don't know
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.35,0:07:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你只是三年级生\N{\rEng}'cause you're just a third grader.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.12,0:07:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但相信我  你真的让大家很受不了\N{\rEng}But take it from me, you're driving everyone crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.44,0:07:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不怪他们\N{\rEng}I don't blame them.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.13,0:07:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我也受不了劲歌热舞\N{\rEng}All that singing and dancing. I can't stand it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.72,0:07:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你不喜欢歌舞  -那并不是我\N{\rEng}- You don't like doing it? - It just isn't me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.65,0:07:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真正喜欢的是打篮球\N{\rEng}What I really wanna do is just play basketball.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.60,0:07:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-篮球  -我超爱\N{\rEng}- Basketball? - I love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.53,0:07:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直如此\N{\rEng}Always have.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.60,0:07:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我爸无需我彩排\N{\rEng}I never miss a game on TV,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.74,0:07:24.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就会盯着电视看比赛\N{\rEng}when my dad isn't making me rehearse.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.90,0:07:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我实在很想放弃唱歌跳舞\N{\rEng}I'd love to quit singing and dancing forever
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.53,0:07:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,专心打球\N{\rEng}and just play ball.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.96,0:07:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  按你想的去做\N{\rEng}Dude, you should do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.15,0:07:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该参加篮球队  马上\N{\rEng}You should join the basketball team. Right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.97,0:07:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我做不到  -你做得到\N{\rEng}- I can't. - Yes, you can.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.56,0:07:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么阻碍\N{\rEng}What's stopping you?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.70,0:07:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸\N{\rEng}It's my dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.94,0:07:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他认为纯爷们不打篮球\N{\rEng}He thinks basketball is for sissies.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.63,0:07:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我逆他的意  他会抽我的\N{\rEng}If I don't do what he wants, he beats me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.75,0:07:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  听着  你要立场坚定\N{\rEng}No, dude. Listen. You need to take a stand
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.34,0:07:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向你爸表明心迹\N{\rEng}and tell your dad what you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.05,0:07:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真要这样\N{\rEng}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.87,0:07:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你升上四年级  你就会明白\N{\rEng}When you'll be a 4th grader, you'll understand that
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.81,0:07:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对待父母  态度要直接强硬\N{\rEng}you have to be tough and direct with your parents.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.73,0:07:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去跟你爸说清楚\N{\rEng}Go to your dad and tell him
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.97,0:07:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要放弃歌舞\N{\rEng}you want to give up singing and dancing
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.07,0:07:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加入篮球队\N{\rEng}and join the basketball team.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.90,0:07:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听君一席话  茅塞顿开\N{\rEng}You know, you're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.89,0:07:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今晚就跟我老爸摊牌\N{\rEng}I'm gonna talk to my old man tonight!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.52,0:07:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得逞了\N{\rEng}Sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.50,0:08:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布莱登  坐好一点\N{\rEng}Sit up properly, Bridon.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.01,0:08:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也知道你爸对坐姿要求严格\N{\rEng}You know how strict your father is about posture.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.57,0:08:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老公  晚饭准备好了\N{\rEng}All right, dear. Dinner's ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.21,0:08:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  开动吧\N{\rEng}Okay, let's eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.28,0:08:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  我有话跟你说\N{\rEng}Dad, I need to talk to you about something.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.51,0:08:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得太有感情了\N{\rEng}That sounds emotional!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.28,0:08:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 儿子  怎么了  在想什么呢 *\N{\rEng}* What is it, son? What's on your mind? *
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.15,0:08:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 不管是什么  爸爸都有时间听 *\N{\rEng}* Whatever it is, you know your dad has the time *
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.58,0:08:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  别这样  好好说话行吗\N{\rEng}No. Dad, can we just talk?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.02,0:08:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 能说就能唱 *\N{\rEng}* If you can talk it you can sing it *
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.20,0:08:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 配上节奏更连贯 *\N{\rEng}* You can lay down the rhythm and bring it *
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.57,0:08:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 一句一旋律 *\N{\rEng}* Just put a melody to the words that you're saying *
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.44,0:08:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 这样就能 *\N{\rEng}* and soon you'll be... *
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.15,0:08:36.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  我想加入篮球队\N{\rEng}Dad, I wanna join the basketball team.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.68,0:08:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么\N{\rEng}What did you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.46,0:08:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈今天告诉我\N{\rEng}This kid at school today told me
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.89,0:08:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该随心所欲\N{\rEng}I should do what I want to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.20,0:08:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想打篮球\N{\rEng}That's what I really want to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.29,0:08:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打篮球\N{\rEng}Basketball?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.71,0:08:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我儿就不能沦为满身臭汗的运动员\N{\rEng}No son of mine is going to be a sweaty little jock!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.54,0:08:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  但我真的想打篮球\N{\rEng}But Dad, that's what I really want.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.88,0:08:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,篮球场上没有劲歌热舞\N{\rEng}There's no singing and dancing in basketball!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.83,0:08:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  所以我才喜欢\N{\rEng}I know. That's kind of why I like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.29,0:08:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想都别想\N{\rEng}Don't you even think about it!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.28,0:09:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我的儿子是运动员\N{\rEng}If I had a jock for a son,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.61,0:09:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会被男声合唱团的人笑话的\N{\rEng}I'd be the laughing stock of the men's choir club!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.38,0:09:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的人生听我的  -别让我动手\N{\rEng}- It's my life, Dad! - Don't make me slap you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.56,0:09:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会狠狠地抽你的嘴\N{\rEng}I will slap your face so super hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.32,0:09:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是一家之主\N{\rEng}I am the man of this house!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.01,0:09:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我不敬就要吃巴掌\N{\rEng}You disrespect me and you're gonna get slapped!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.88,0:09:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许你该让他试试\N{\rEng}Maybe you should let him try it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.73,0:09:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婆娘  你说什么\N{\rEng}What did you say, woman?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.53,0:09:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样做不民主\N{\rEng}You aren't being fair.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.24,0:09:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不尊重我  我要抽你耳光\N{\rEng}That's it. I'm gonna slap you!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.61,0:09:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  求求你\N{\rEng}No, please!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.98,0:09:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 左一巴  右一巴 *\N{\rEng}* I slap you! I slap you! *
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.54,0:09:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 巴巴有声  巴巴有力 *\N{\rEng}* I slap, slap, slap you! *
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.17,0:09:30.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 我抽你  抽你这个笨蛋 *\N{\rEng}* I'm slapping you, slapping you silly, *
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.81,0:09:32.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 谁让你对我不敬 *\N{\rEng}* 'cause you disrespected me *
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.78,0:09:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟  课前借数学作业我抄\N{\rEng}You guys, I need to copy your math homework before class.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.90,0:09:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别做梦了  你这坨懒屎\N{\rEng}You're not copying my homework, you lazy turd.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.88,0:09:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  操你妈的\N{\rEng}Fuck you, Kyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.30,0:09:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 我们又在学校欢聚一堂 *\N{\rEng}* And you know we're together at school again *
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.17,0:09:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 又回到学校 *\N{\rEng}* At school again *
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.17,0:09:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 和朋友们在一起 *\N{\rEng}* With all of our friends *
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.19,0:09:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 我们的友谊地久天长 *\N{\rEng}* And you know we'll be doing this forever *
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.97,0:09:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-* 于学校重聚 *  -靠  闭嘴\N{\rEng}- * Together, at school again, * - Goddammit! Shut up!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.59,0:09:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 特别的一天 *\N{\rEng}* What a special day *
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.37,0:09:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-* 我们相信 *  -通通给我住口\N{\rEng}- * We can say that * - Shut up, shut up, shut up!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.51,0:10:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 友谊永不变 *\N{\rEng}* it's never going away! *
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.74,0:10:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你怎么出尔反尔\N{\rEng}Hey, kid, what happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.65,0:10:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你不再唱歌跳舞了\N{\rEng}I thought you didn't wanna sing and dance anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.52,0:10:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想  但我一说  我爸就勃然大怒\N{\rEng}Yeah, well, my dad blew a gasket when I told him
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.47,0:10:13.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还打了我妈\N{\rEng}and then he beat my mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.75,0:10:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  我是怎么说的\N{\rEng}Dude, what did I tell you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.70,0:10:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要理直气壮地自辩\N{\rEng}You have to be tough and stand up for yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.58,0:10:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加勒特老师\N{\rEng}Mr. Garett!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.46,0:10:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子想加入篮球队\N{\rEng}This kid wants to join the basketball team.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.84,0:10:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他打得很棒\N{\rEng}He's really good.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.61,0:10:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\rEng}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.56,0:10:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我要回去上课了\N{\rEng}Look, I should be getting to class.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.83,0:10:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子  我用得上你\N{\rEng}Hey, we sure could use you, kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.58,0:10:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总找不着足够的篮球热爱者\N{\rEng}I can never find enough kids that wanna play ball.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.79,0:10:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学生和学校资金\N{\rEng}All the kids and the school funding 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.07,0:10:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都被戏剧部抢走了\N{\rEng}goes to the theater department.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.65,0:10:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了吗  他们需要你  这叫缘分\N{\rEng}You see? They need you. This is fate, kid. Fate.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.75,0:10:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很茫然\N{\rEng}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.75,0:10:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你休息时间过来\N{\rEng}Look, just come in at recess
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.99,0:10:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随队射几球就好了\N{\rEng}and shoot some balls with the team.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.63,0:10:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  休息时间过去\N{\rEng}Yeah, just go in at recess
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.56,0:10:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随队射上几球  该死的\N{\rEng}and shoot some balls with the team, goddammit.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.08,0:10:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\rEng}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.73,0:10:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-布莱登  射得好  -谢谢\N{\rEng}- Hey, that's great, Bridon! - Thanks!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.22,0:10:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我们夺冠有望了\N{\rEng}We might have a chance at winning now!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.60,0:10:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布莱登\N{\rEng}Bridon!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.60,0:10:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 你在这里干什么  干什么 *\N{\rEng}* What are you doing here? What are you doing here? *
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.86,0:10:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  我只是来打发时间\N{\rEng}Dad, I was just messing around.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.42,0:10:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开车经过学校  看见\N{\rEng}I drove by the school and saw
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.92,0:11:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操场上有学生在排练音乐剧\N{\rEng}kids on the playground doing a music number,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.63,0:11:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你却不在\N{\rEng}and you weren't there.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.89,0:11:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你竟在体育馆投篮\N{\rEng}You're here in the sports gym shooting basket hoops.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.96,0:11:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的儿子投篮很准\N{\rEng}Hey, your kid is really good at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.01,0:11:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跟我说话  你这运动蠢材加饭桶\N{\rEng}Don't talk to me, stupid jock asshole!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.57,0:11:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对他宽容点  好吗\N{\rEng}Just go easy on him, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.98,0:11:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这动作表示什么吗\N{\rEng}You know what this means?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.38,0:11:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表示你将会挨巴掌\N{\rEng}It means you're about to get slapped,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.04,0:11:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你最好还是闭嘴\N{\rEng}so you better shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.55,0:11:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想打篮球  你应该尊重他\N{\rEng}If he wants to play ball, you should let him.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.15,0:11:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要抽你  把你抽个半死不活\N{\rEng}I'll do it! I'll slap the shit out of you!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.70,0:11:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是一个孩子\N{\rEng}He's just a kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.69,0:11:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用你来教我怎么教育儿子\N{\rEng}You don't tell me how to raise my son!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.66,0:11:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我再抽  -爸  住手\N{\rEng}- I'll slap it again... - Dad, stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.86,0:11:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想把我的儿子变成\N{\rEng}You try to turn my son into
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.01,0:11:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你这样的小运动饭桶吗\N{\rEng}a little asshole sports person like yourself?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.42,0:11:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再抽你一嘴巴\N{\rEng}There. There's another slap.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.54,0:11:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许下次你会想清楚再说话\N{\rEng}Maybe you'll think next time you act you...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.59,0:11:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我抽  再抽\N{\rEng}Slap it! I slap it!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.23,0:11:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸  你弄疼我了  -布莱登  闭嘴\N{\rEng}- Dad! Dad, you're hurting me! - Shut up, Bridon!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.11,0:11:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,古尔莫先生  发生什么事了\N{\rEng}What's going on here, Mr. Guermo?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.40,0:11:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麦基  让开\N{\rEng}Get outta my way, Mackey!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.52,0:11:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也想挨巴掌吗\N{\rEng}You wanna piece of this?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.11,0:11:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有必要的话我会让全学校的人\N{\rEng}I'll slap everyone in this goddamn school
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.64,0:11:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挨巴掌\N{\rEng}if I have to!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.85,0:11:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后都不准打篮球\N{\rEng}You are never going to play shooty hoops,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.79,0:11:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂了吗\N{\rEng}do you understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.85,0:12:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只能全力以赴地唱歌跳舞\N{\rEng}You're gonna sing and dance and be the best at it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.35,0:12:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你弄痛我手臂了  -痛就好\N{\rEng}- You're hurting my arm! - That's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.02,0:12:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他妈的\N{\rEng}Oh, shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.70,0:12:08.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  很好\N{\rEng}That's good, that's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.91,0:12:10.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯尔  爆他头\N{\rEng}Yeah, shoot that guy in the face, Kyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.72,0:12:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漂亮\N{\rEng}Yeah, nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.85,0:12:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《歌舞青春》的潮流依然盛行\N{\rEng}You guys, this High School Musical thing isn't gonna go away.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.04,0:12:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我们还是跟上这潮流吧\N{\rEng}I think we better just get on board with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.10,0:12:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  你疯了吗\N{\rEng}What? Are you crazy?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.67,0:12:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  没门\N{\rEng}No way, dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.77,0:12:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们相互发过誓永不跟风的\N{\rEng}We promised each other we would never do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.45,0:12:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-记得吗  -没错\N{\rEng}- Remember? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.61,0:12:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得  但眼看我们快要\N{\rEng}I know, but I think we're really 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.72,0:12:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被学校边缘化了\N{\rEng}starting to become outcasts at school.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.34,0:12:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要丧失在校内的公信力了\N{\rEng}We're losing all our credibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.04,0:12:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你们现在沦落到和谁作伴\N{\rEng}I mean, look at who you guys are hanging out with now.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.39,0:12:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天啊  是斯科特·马金森\N{\rEng}Scott Malkinson for Christ's sake!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.45,0:12:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我作伴有什么不好\N{\rEng}What's so bad about hanging out with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.69,0:12:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯科特·马金森  住口\N{\rEng}Shut up, Scott Malkinson.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.05,0:12:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我是斯科特·马金森"\N{\rEng}"I'm Scott Malkinson."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.98,0:12:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我口吃又尿频"\N{\rEng}"I've got a lisp and I've got diabetes."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.13,0:12:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要取笑我的糖尿病\N{\rEng}Hey, don't make fun of my diabetes.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.94,0:12:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"不要取笑我的糖尿病"\N{\rEng}"Don't make fun of my diabetes."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.92,0:12:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我是斯科特·马金森"\N{\rEng}"I'm Scott Malkinson."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.55,0:12:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以挖苦他\N{\rEng}You can rip on him,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.50,0:12:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不能拿他作伴\N{\rEng}but you guys are hanging out with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.24,0:12:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不认为\N{\rEng}Doesn't that make you think
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.06,0:12:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在校内的影响力下降了吗\N{\rEng}maybe your clout at school has slipped a little?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.73,0:12:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯坦  你只是嫉妒那个三年级生\N{\rEng}Stan, you're just jealous of that third grader
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.39,0:12:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为只有你也劲歌热舞\N{\rEng}and you think Wendy's gonna go for him
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.67,0:12:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能挽回温蒂\N{\rEng}unless you start singing and dancing, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.19,0:12:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.30,0:13:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没有\N{\rEng}That isn't true!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.23,0:13:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你们说中了\N{\rEng}Okay, that's totally true.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.71,0:13:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我们正处在\N{\rEng}But you guys, we are at risk of 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.86,0:13:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为边缘人的危机当中\N{\rEng}becoming the unpopular kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.91,0:13:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  那本该是我的威力加强包\N{\rEng}Hey, that was supposed to be my power up pack."
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.80,0:13:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"那本该是我的威力加强包"\N{\rEng}"That was supposed to be my power up pack.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.36,0:13:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我是斯科特·马金森  我尿频尿急"\N{\rEng}"I'm Scott Malkinson. I have diabetes."
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.24,0:13:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 《歌舞青春》太牛了 *\N{\rEng}* High School Musical is so awesome. *
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.22,0:13:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-古尔莫先生吗  -有何贵干\N{\rEng}- Mr. Guermo? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.86,0:13:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是儿童保护组织的工作人员\N{\rEng}We're from Child Protective Services.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.78,0:13:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人报料说\N{\rEng}There's some concern 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.59,0:13:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在身体上虐待你的孩子\N{\rEng}you might be physically abusing your child.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.03,0:13:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  到底是谁报料的\N{\rEng}What? Who the hell's been saying that?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.55,0:13:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一位热心的学生打电话举报的\N{\rEng}We got a phone call from a concerned student
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.74,0:13:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他希望身份保密\N{\rEng}who wishes to remain anonymous.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.60,0:13:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的名字是斯坦·马什\N{\rEng}His name is Stan Marsh.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.41,0:13:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们最好立马转身\N{\rEng}You better just turn your asses around 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.38,0:13:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开车走人  否则\N{\rEng}and get back in your little car, 'cause there's
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.40,0:13:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会让你们吃不了兜着走\N{\rEng}a world of hurt about to come your way.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.52,0:13:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,古尔莫先生  我们要进去\N{\rEng}Mr. Guermo, we need to come in 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.20,0:13:49.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你的儿子谈谈\N{\rEng}and have a word with your son.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.93,0:13:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那务必请进\N{\rEng}Oh, by all means.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.39,0:13:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有种你们就进来  进来啊\N{\rEng}You got the balls to come in here, do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.55,0:13:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来啊\N{\rEng}Do it!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.85,0:13:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布莱登  你好  我是凯利先生\N{\rEng}Hello, Bridon. My name is Mr. Kelly.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.04,0:14:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以的话  我们想和你聊几句\N{\rEng}We just wanted to talk to you for a few minutes, if that's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.97,0:14:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同时或能\N{\rEng}And just maybe...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.05,0:14:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是赏你的  我抽\N{\rEng}Yeah, there it is! Slapped you!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.98,0:14:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别以为我会就此作罢\N{\rEng}You probably think I'm finished, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.88,0:14:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-再来一巴  -我的天\N{\rEng}- There's another one! - Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.24,0:14:13.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  婊子  我不会忘了赏你一巴\N{\rEng}Don't worry, bitch. I didn't forget about you!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.76,0:14:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是赏你的  我抽  我抽抽抽\N{\rEng}There's a slap for you! Slap! Slap! Slap!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.92,0:14:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再赏你一巴\N{\rEng}There you go!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.82,0:14:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是后脑回旋抽\N{\rEng}Here's a little reach-around back of the head slap!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.76,0:14:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  求求你们  快走吧  \N{\rEng}Oh, God, please! You have to get away. 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.60,0:14:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然他不会停的\N{\rEng}He won't ever stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.48,0:14:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我抽得正爽呢\N{\rEng}I'm going slap happy!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.31,0:14:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 我抽得正爽  我抽  我再抽 *\N{\rEng}* I'm going slap, slap happy. Slap-ati, slap. *
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.06,0:14:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 教你以后别再踏进我家门一步 *\N{\rEng}* And teaching you a lesson for coming in my house! *
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.74,0:14:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伯逊  你看什么看\N{\rEng}What are you looking at, Robertson?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.73,0:14:43.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出炉了\N{\rEng}They're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.55,0:14:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校歌舞剧的试音结果出炉了\N{\rEng}The audition results for the school musical are in!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.08,0:14:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-温蒂  你是领唱  -好的\N{\rEng}- Hey, you got the lead, Wendy! - All right!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.90,0:14:53.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁是男主音  -毫无疑问\N{\rEng}- Who's the male lead? - No surprise there!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.88,0:14:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是布莱登  -实至名归\N{\rEng}- It's Bridon! - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.25,0:14:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是后备\N{\rEng}I get to be a stand-in!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.27,0:15:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布莱登  恭喜你\N{\rEng}Congratulations, Bridon!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.73,0:15:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱俩将会有很多对手戏\N{\rEng}Guess we'll be working a lot together.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.62,0:15:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  很好啊  -天杀的\N{\rEng}- Yeah, great. - Goddammit!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.28,0:15:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管我做什么  那小子就是不放弃\N{\rEng}No matter what I do, this kid just won't stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.74,0:15:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在他们还要一起演出\N{\rEng}Now they're gonna be in a show together?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.37,0:15:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我没戏了\N{\rEng}Jesus, it's all over for me!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.39,0:15:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们可能会有接吻戏\N{\rEng}They'll probably even have a kissing scene!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.61,0:15:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么会落得如此下场\N{\rEng}What did I do to deserve this?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.08,0:15:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在应该怎么做呢\N{\rEng}And what am I supposed to do now?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.37,0:15:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 有人和黛娜在厨房里 *\N{\rEng}* Someone's in the kitchen with Dinah *
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.56,0:15:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 我知道  有人在厨房里 *\N{\rEng}* Someone's in the kitchen, I know *
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.01,0:15:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 有人和黛娜在厨房里 *\N{\rEng}* Someone's in the kitchen with Dinah *
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.97,0:15:38.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 弹着古老的班卓琴并高唱 *\N{\rEng}* Strumming on the old banjo and going... *
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.17,0:15:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 弹着古老的班卓琴 *\N{\rEng}* Strumming on the ol' banjo, jo, jo, *
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.25,0:15:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 告诉萝蒂阿姨 *\N{\rEng}* Go tell aunt Rhodie *
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.19,0:15:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 告诉萝蒂阿姨 *\N{\rEng}* Go tell aunt Rhodie *
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.17,0:15:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 告诉萝蒂阿姨那只老灰天鹅 *\N{\rEng}* Go tell aunt Rhodie The old Grey Goose is... *
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.26,0:15:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 祝你生日快乐 *\N{\rEng}* Happy birthday to you *
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.20,0:16:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 祝你生日快... *\N{\rEng}* Happy birthday to... *
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.49,0:16:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 听这节奏  时间到了  到了 *\N{\rEng}* Hear the rhythm? Now is the time! The time! *
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.82,0:16:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 睡觉时间到了 *\N{\rEng}* It's time to go to bed! *
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.86,0:16:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 一天的生活到此结束 *\N{\rEng}* Yes, time to call it a day! *
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.05,0:16:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 你可以摘星 *\N{\rEng}* You can reach the stars... *
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.52,0:16:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你  你要阻止他\N{\rEng}Oh, please! You have to do something!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.47,0:16:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干啥打断我\N{\rEng}What are you interrupting me for?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.27,0:16:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们的儿子要离家出走  -什么\N{\rEng}- It's our son. He's running away. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.99,0:16:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 发生什么事了  这是干什么 *\N{\rEng}* What's going on here? What's this all about? *
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.60,0:16:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 知道你自己在做什么 *\N{\rEng}* What do you think you're doing? *
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.85,0:16:34.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  我讨厌你老是\N{\rEng}Dad, I'm sick of you trying to always--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.49,0:16:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用说的  用唱的\N{\rEng}No, no. Sing it!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.48,0:16:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  我讨厌唱歌\N{\rEng}No, I'm sick of singing!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.20,0:16:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 你能相信吗  他刚才说的话 *\N{\rEng}* Can you believe it? What'd he just say? *
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.41,0:16:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 现在的孩子都怎么了 *\N{\rEng}* What's the matter with kids these days? *
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.31,0:16:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 现在的孩子 *\N{\rEng}* Kids these days. *
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.93,0:16:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 现在的孩子 *\N{\rEng}* Kids these days! *
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.46,0:16:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上给我回房\N{\rEng}Just go right back to your room 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.95,0:16:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-练歌  -让我走\N{\rEng}- and sing a ballad, mister! - Just let me go.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.97,0:16:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走啊\N{\rEng}Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.09,0:16:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逆我意啊\N{\rEng}Make my day.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.12,0:17:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再不上楼  我就把你抽得\N{\rEng}You get upstairs or I will slap you until
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.46,0:17:05.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一脸都是手掌印\N{\rEng}there's little red hand prints all over your face.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.84,0:17:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天啊  你造反了你\N{\rEng}Oh, my God, what was that?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.08,0:17:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看见了吗  天啊  痛死我了\N{\rEng}Did you see that? Oh, my God. It hurt so bad!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.01,0:17:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟怎么回事了\N{\rEng}What the "H" is going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.05,0:17:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么  大家都疯了\N{\rEng}What are you doing? Everyone's crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.60,0:17:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳听为虚  眼见为实\N{\rEng}Well, I had to see it to believe it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.50,0:17:32.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你们说了  他一直\N{\rEng}I told you guys. He's been watching
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.58,0:17:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在看《歌舞青春》\N{\rEng}High School Musical over and over again.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.64,0:17:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  我在看《歌舞青春2》\N{\rEng}Actually, this is High School Musical 2.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.45,0:17:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面有舞蹈教学部分\N{\rEng}It has a dance-along part.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.49,0:17:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们说过永不跟风的\N{\rEng}We said we wouldn't be a part of this fad
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.31,0:17:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但看看你\N{\rEng}and look at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.16,0:17:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  看看你现在的样子\N{\rEng}Yeah. Look at yourself, man!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.70,0:17:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  你们或许愿意做边缘人\N{\rEng}Look, you guys might be fine with being outcasts
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.58,0:17:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愿意和斯科特·马金森作伴  我可不愿\N{\rEng}and hanging out with Scott Malkinson, but I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.87,0:17:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗\N{\rEng}You know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.60,0:17:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少斯科特·马金森懂得自重\N{\rEng}At least Scott Malkinson has some self-respect!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.85,0:17:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少他不会受同伴压力影响\N{\rEng}At least Scott doesn't cave in to peer-pressure
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.22,0:17:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而开始学习歌舞\N{\rEng}and start doing musicals!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.21,0:17:54.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯科特·马金森有口吃和尿频\N{\rEng}Scott Malkinson has a lisp and diabetes!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.35,0:17:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人邀他唱歌跳舞\N{\rEng}Nobody's going to let him do a musical!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.59,0:17:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  你们太伤人了\N{\rEng}That's enough, you guys. It's not cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.46,0:17:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多小孩都有糖尿病  你们不能\N{\rEng}Lots of kids have diabetes, and you shouldn't be...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.60,0:18:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"你们不能取笑患糖尿病的小孩"\N{\rEng}"You shouldn't rip on kids with diabetes."
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.93,0:18:02.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"这太伤人了  我是斯科特·马金森"\N{\rEng}"That's not cool. I'm Scott Malkinson."
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.71,0:18:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都听着  时代变了\N{\rEng}Look, guys, the world is changing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.86,0:18:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们扭转不了  就只能随波逐流\N{\rEng}We can't fight it. We have to change with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.26,0:18:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在看同类电影\N{\rEng}I've been watching these movies
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.68,0:18:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种种迹象表明\N{\rEng}and from the looks of it,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.58,0:18:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,升上高中后  这种歌舞的风气\N{\rEng}there's going to be a lot more singing and dancing
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.39,0:18:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只会有增无减\N{\rEng}when we get to high school.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.65,0:18:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们认为无视这风气\N{\rEng}And if you think we'll gain any respect 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.51,0:18:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保持特立独行  就能获得尊重\N{\rEng}by ignoring this thing and being individuals,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.00,0:18:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那想想这件事  \N{\rEng}then think about this... 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.53,0:18:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  大伙都认为\N{\rEng}Right now, everyone thinks
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.27,0:18:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯比你们酷多了\N{\rEng}Butters is way cooler than any of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.75,0:18:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯坦  这招太损了\N{\rEng}That's a low blow, Stan.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.94,0:18:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西部杰夫山猫队集体犯规三次\N{\rEng}Third team foul on West Jeff Bobcats, m'kay?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.72,0:18:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,控球权回到公牛队队手里\N{\rEng}Ball goes back over to the Cows.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.61,0:18:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  布莱登  准备好上场没\N{\rEng}All right. You ready to get in there, Bridon?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.81,0:18:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-教练  我准备好了  -打趴他们\N{\rEng}- I'm ready, Coach. - Give 'em hell!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.26,0:18:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离第一节结束还剩一分钟\N{\rEng}Just a minute to go in the first quarter.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.37,0:19:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 我们将震撼你 *\N{\rEng}* We will, we will rock you *
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.11,0:19:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 大家一起唱 *\N{\rEng}* Sing it, y'all *
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.04,0:19:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 我们  我们将 *\N{\rEng}* We will, we will... *
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.95,0:19:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布莱登  你昨晚怎么\N{\rEng}Hey, Bridon. How come you weren't 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.10,0:19:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没来参加歌舞剧的彩排\N{\rEng}at musical rehearsals last night?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.80,0:19:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我加入了篮球队\N{\rEng}I joined the basketball team.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.31,0:19:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会再唱歌跳舞了\N{\rEng}I gave up singing and dancing forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.95,0:19:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一点都不喜欢\N{\rEng}I'm just not into it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.81,0:19:39.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你放弃了  -没错\N{\rEng}- You gave it up? - That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.76,0:19:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时你必须\N{\rEng}You know, sometimes you just have to go 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.45,0:19:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随心所欲\N{\rEng}what your heart tells you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.16,0:19:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于我们擅长的事物\N{\rEng}There's things we're all good at.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.15,0:19:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能只把它藏在心底\N{\rEng}And we can't just keep them bottled up inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.50,0:19:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 因为你必须随心所欲 *\N{\rEng}* 'Cause you got to do what you wanna do *
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.52,0:19:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 排除万难 *\N{\rEng}* Don't let nothing get in your way, *
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.43,0:19:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 追逐梦想 *\N{\rEng}* chase your dream every day, *
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.47,0:19:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 美女  这就是真理 *\N{\rEng}* True, girl, you know it's true *
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.33,0:19:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 随心所欲 *\N{\rEng}* That if you really wanna be you, *
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.79,0:20:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 回归真我 *\N{\rEng}* you gotta do what you wanna do *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.39,0:20:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 他曾失落  因为他只想打篮球 *\N{\rEng}* He was unhappy 'cause he just wanted to play ball *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.65,0:20:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 但他拾起勇气  回应内心呼召 *\N{\rEng}* But he finally got the courage to answer his call *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.39,0:20:13.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 就如同我  我只想劲歌热舞 *\N{\rEng}* Just like me all I every wanted was to sing and dance *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.98,0:20:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 现在我终有机会 *\N{\rEng}* And now that I stood up for my dream *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.83,0:20:16.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 追逐梦想 *\N{\rEng}* I finally have the chance *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.03,0:20:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 随心所欲 *\N{\rEng}* You gotta do what you wanna do *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.19,0:20:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 即便旁人反对 *\N{\rEng}* Even if other people don't really want you to *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.70,0:20:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 美女  这就是真理 *\N{\rEng}* True, girl, you know it's true *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.96,0:20:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 心之所向 *\N{\rEng}* That the thing you wanna do *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.16,0:20:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 路之所往 *\N{\rEng}* is the thing that you should do *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.61,0:20:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 有人说我怪 *\N{\rEng}* Some kids think I'm strange *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.10,0:20:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 只因测验是我爱 *\N{\rEng}* 'cause I like studying for an exam *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.23,0:20:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 不要迷恋哥  哥只是传说 *\N{\rEng}* But I don't let that bother me because it's who I am *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.90,0:20:44.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 尽管我最喜欢取笑 *\N{\rEng}* And I like nothing better than making fun at yous *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.18,0:20:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 同学和黑人 *\N{\rEng}* and ripping on black people *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.01,0:20:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 有人说我坏  但你必须 *\N{\rEng}* though some people think it's rude but you gotta *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.09,0:20:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 随心所欲 *\N{\rEng}* Do what you wanna do *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.65,0:20:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 确保你做的事 *\N{\rEng}* Just make sure that what you're doing *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.46,0:20:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 是大势所趋 *\N{\rEng}* is what's cool and popular with everyone *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.39,0:20:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 宝贝 去深思  去细想*\N{\rEng}* Chew, baby, chew and chew *
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.24,0:21:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布莱登  我们可以去看你\N{\rEng}Hey, Bridon. Can we watch you 
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.28,0:21:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-练习篮球吗  -可以\N{\rEng}- practice basketball? - Uh, sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.97,0:21:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 随心所欲  别压抑 *\N{\rEng}* Do what you want don't have restraint *
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.71,0:21:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 太有压力  会头晕 *\N{\rEng}* Don't stress about it or you just might faint *
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.66,0:21:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 随意高潮和手淫  做人要做灰太狼 *\N{\rEng}* If you wanna get high and jack off, it's cool *
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.61,0:21:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 随心所欲 *\N{\rEng}* You gotta do what you wanna do. *
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.29,0:21:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 畅所欲为 *\N{\rEng}* Do what you wanna do *
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.58,0:21:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 只要那是 *\N{\rEng}* As long as what you wanna do *
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.02,0:21:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 人心所向的事 *\N{\rEng}* is what everybody wants you to *
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.31,0:21:21.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 宝贝  买点胶水 *\N{\rEng}* Glue, baby, buy some glue! *
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.25,0:21:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 以防你和你做的事 *\N{\rEng}* Just in case you what you do with... *
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.78,0:21:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你们  别唱了\N{\rEng}Hey, guys. Hey, guys!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.99,0:21:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人都去哪了  \N{\rEng}Where'd everybody go? 
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.23,0:21:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女生都去围观\N{\rEng}The girls all wanted to go watch
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.44,0:21:35.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布莱登练习篮球去了\N{\rEng}that Bridon kid practice basketball.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.01,0:21:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女生不是喜欢劲歌热舞吗\N{\rEng}But the girls like singing and dancing.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.44,0:21:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  女生只是喜欢布莱登而已\N{\rEng}No, I think the girls just like that Bridon kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.83,0:21:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论他做什么\N{\rEng}No matter what he does.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.15,0:21:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但  不  我们才\N{\rEng}But... No, we just...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.53,0:21:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  等等  我们才刚上手啊\N{\rEng}No. No, wait! We just got good at this.
