[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由TimeM生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.net
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayDepth: 0
PlayResX: 1916
PlayResY: 1076
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 2
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H19000000,&H000E0300,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,2,2,134,120,68,1
Style: eng,Microsoft YaHei,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,26,1
Style: Top,微软雅黑,10,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Git,Comic Sans MS,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Chn,微软雅黑,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Eng,Comic Sans MS,60,&H002AF7FF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.00,0:00:11.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm going down to south park\N gonna have myself a time 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.85,0:00:15.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Friendly faces everywhere\N humble folks without temptation 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.13,0:00:17.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Going down to south park\N gonna leave my woes behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.52,0:00:21.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ample parking day or night\N people shouting howdy neighbor
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.76,0:00:24.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heading on out to south park\N gonna see if I can't unwind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.34,0:00:28.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I like girls with big vaginas\N I like girls with big fat titties
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.41,0:00:31.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.78,0:21:45.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0040,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译制作\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}YYeTs人人影视字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.71,0:21:47.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0120,,{\1c&HFDC282&}翻译\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Foresee
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.71,0:21:47.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0020,,{\1c&HFDC282&}校对\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.29,0:21:48.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0020,,{\1c&HFDC282&}后期\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}csbeyond
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.33,0:21:48.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0060,,{\1c&HFDC282&}总监\N{\1c&HFFFFFF&}Tina
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.00,0:00:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0150,,{\1c&HFDC282&}《南方公园》第12季  第14集\N{\rEng}South Park Season 12 Episode 14
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.00,0:00:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0100,,"囚不住的巴特斯"\N{\rEng}"The Ungroundable"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.97,0:00:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好么  此时电脑会出现一个命令栏\N{\rEng}M'kay, so now the computer will show a command bar.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.67,0:00:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好么  输入x=y+1\N{\rEng}M'kay, and we type in "X" equal "Y" plus one.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.97,0:00:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好么  然后点击"Y"\N{\rEng}M'kay, and then it says we hit command "Y"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.11,0:00:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打开主菜单\N{\rEng}to bring up the menu screen.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.22,0:00:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  你耍我吧\N{\rEng}Oh, man. You've got to be kidding me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.45,0:00:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到处都是该死的日本人\N{\rEng}Goddamn Japs are everywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.16,0:01:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好么  右击菜单项中的"全等"\N{\rEng}M'kay, now, right click on menu item "Equate all"
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.17,0:01:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,输入"Y"\N{\rEng}and type in input "Y".
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.25,0:01:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯坦  你是美国这边的吗  \N{\rEng}Dude. Are you on America's side, Stan? 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.12,0:01:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  我是日本这边的\N{\rEng}No, I'm on the Japanese side.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.05,0:01:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚谁朝我开枪了\N{\rEng}Who just shot me?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.01,0:01:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好么  右击是指点击上面的\N{\rEng}M'kay, let's see. A right click is the upper right...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.40,0:01:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么\N{\rEng}But then what the hell...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.79,0:01:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好么  同学们  我先弄清楚这个\N{\rEng}M'kay, kids. I'm gonna need to get some clarification on this.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.60,0:01:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们先计算  我马上回来    \N{\rEng}Just keep entering the calculations. I'll be right back, m'kay?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.89,0:01:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们\N{\rEng}Oh, dude!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.78,0:01:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真希望有把真的火焰枪\N{\rEng}I wish I had a real flame-thrower.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.13,0:01:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个对付日本人很有用\N{\rEng}It works awesome on Japs!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.86,0:01:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  天啊\N{\rEng}Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.00,0:01:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯坦  斯坦  出大事了\N{\rEng}Stan. Stan, we have a big problem!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.37,0:01:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哥们  啥事  -学校里有吸血鬼\N{\rEng}- Dude, what? - There's vampires in the school!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.99,0:01:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -吸血鬼  我看到了\N{\rEng}- What? - Vampires! I seen 'em!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.93,0:01:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁在用防弹衣作弊\N{\rEng}Dude! Who's using the flak jacket cheat?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.59,0:01:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兵不厌诈\N{\rEng}Not a cheat if you rank up!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.67,0:01:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼  外面有个吸血鬼\N{\rEng}Kenny. There's a vampire on the loose.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.68,0:01:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯蒂·吉尔森跟他混在一起\N{\rEng}Then Katie Gelson was hanging out with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.40,0:01:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在她也变成了吸血鬼\N{\rEng}And now she's a vampire, too!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.10,0:01:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  哪有什么吸血鬼\N{\rEng}Butters, there's no such thing as vampires.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.28,0:01:56.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的  你们要相信我\N{\rEng}But there is! You guys gotta believe me!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.40,0:01:57.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚开始只有少数几个 \N{\rEng}First, there was just a couple, 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.57,0:01:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 现在越来越多了\N{\rEng}but now, it's like they're growing.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.63,0:02:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们长着獠牙  喝血  还有好多特征\N{\rEng}They have fangs and drink blood and everything!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.77,0:02:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  巴特斯\N{\rEng}All right, Butters.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.43,0:02:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去记下那些吸血鬼的行踪\N{\rEng}Well, you go document the vampires' movements
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.05,0:02:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我们就能识破他们的阴谋\N{\rEng}so we know what their intentions are.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.61,0:02:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  你看我合适吗\N{\rEng}Really? You think that's best?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.82,0:02:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  快滚吧  -遵命\N{\rEng}- Yeah, now get outta here. - All right!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.00,0:02:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我不能活着回来 \N{\rEng}If I don't make it back, 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.71,0:02:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 请代我转告我妈\N{\rEng}tell my mom what happened to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.50,0:02:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你死定了  贝贝小日本\N{\rEng}You got powned, Bebe. You Jap bitch!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.55,0:02:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷吧\N{\rEng}Isn't this cool?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.51,0:02:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这时候体育馆里没人\N{\rEng}This time of day nobody's in the gym.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.48,0:02:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该把这里作为南方公园\N{\rEng}We should make this one of our official South Park 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.32,0:02:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸血鬼俱乐部的根据地\N{\rEng}vampire's club hangouts.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.85,0:02:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外套不错  迈克  冷酷傲慢\N{\rEng}That's an awesome new coat, Mike. Looks totally badass.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.60,0:02:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要叫我迈克  叫我韦皮尔\N{\rEng}Don't call me Mike. My name is Vampir now.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.61,0:02:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  很酷\N{\rEng}Oh, that's cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.36,0:02:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备改名叫韦拉迪米尔\N{\rEng}I'm gonna change my name to Vladimir.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.47,0:02:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  跟韦皮尔太像了\N{\rEng}You can't. It's too close to Vampir.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.58,0:02:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下午12点32分\N{\rEng}12:32 PM.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.07,0:02:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸血鬼们在学校体育馆集合\N{\rEng}Vampires meeting in the school gymnasium.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.34,0:02:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,领头的是个五年级生\N{\rEng}Leader appears to be a fifth grader.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.82,0:02:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道《暮光之城》里的女孩贝拉吧  \N{\rEng}You know that girl Bella in "Twilight"? 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.84,0:02:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我像她\N{\rEng}I think I'm like her.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.72,0:02:52.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个嗜能吸血鬼  喜欢我的亮片吗\N{\rEng}I'm a psi-vampire. Do you like these sparkles I got?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.06,0:02:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安妮·巴特利特是个嗜能吸血鬼\N{\rEng}Annie Bartlett is a psi-vampire.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.65,0:02:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我更像个嗜血吸血鬼\N{\rEng}Yeah, I'm more a sanguinarian vampire.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.68,0:03:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我更依靠生命力\N{\rEng}In that I rely more on the life force energy, per se.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.42,0:03:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该是个混种吸血鬼\N{\rEng}Yeah, I'm gonna be a hybrid vampire.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.58,0:03:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗜能并且嗜血\N{\rEng}Both psi and sanguinarian.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.29,0:03:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是瑞安·艾利斯\N{\rEng}That's Ryan Ellis.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.49,0:03:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看样子他也入伙了\N{\rEng}Looks like they've gotten to him, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.35,0:03:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午餐时间快结束了  要不要再喝点血\N{\rEng}Lunchtime's almost over. Should we drink some more blood?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.65,0:03:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好啊  -酷\N{\rEng}- Yeah! - Cool!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.78,0:03:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我们该进食了\N{\rEng}Yeah, and I think it's time for us to feed, per se.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.53,0:03:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[蛤蜊番茄汁]
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.96,0:03:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  看来他们要喝血了\N{\rEng}Oh, God. I think they're gonna drink blood now!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.46,0:03:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们拿着高脚杯  并且\N{\rEng}They've got some kind of chalice and they're...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.66,0:03:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是德州大巴特斯秀\N{\rEng}It's the Big Texas Butters show!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.85,0:03:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有请德州大巴特斯\N{\rEng}And now here is Big Texas Butters!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.73,0:03:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好啊  伙计们\N{\rEng}Why howdy there, partners!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.21,0:03:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是德州大巴特斯  下面是我的祝福语\N{\rEng}I'm Big Texas Butters and this here's my horse toast.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.81,0:03:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝您\N{\rEng}Happy trails...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.45,0:03:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旅途愉快\N{\rEng}to you!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.33,0:03:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干吗\N{\rEng}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.25,0:03:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退后  都退后\N{\rEng}Get back! You stay back!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.15,0:03:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我用圣体驱赶你们\N{\rEng}The body of Christ compels you!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.58,0:03:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那小子刚被我们吓坏了\N{\rEng}That kid was really scared of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.41,0:03:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  吸血莱恩\N{\rEng}That's true, Bloodrayne.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.51,0:04:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们会害怕我们  \N{\rEng}People are going to be frightened of us 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.66,0:04:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他们不了解我们的生活方式\N{\rEng}because they don't understand our ways, per se.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.07,0:04:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我们多酷啊\N{\rEng}Yeah, we're cool, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.03,0:04:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些家伙在搞什么鬼\N{\rEng}What the hell are those kids doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.78,0:04:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们怎么突然都穿成那样\N{\rEng}Why are they all dressing like that all of a sudden?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.05,0:04:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们想做哥特派吗\N{\rEng}Are they trying to be goth?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.03,0:04:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他们是吸血派\N{\rEng}No, they're vamp.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.82,0:04:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴塑料的獠牙  喝蛤蜊番茄汁\N{\rEng}They wear plastic fangs and drink freakin' clamato juice.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.38,0:04:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不能那么穿 \N{\rEng}But they can't dress like that. 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.35,0:04:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 那是我们的风格\N{\rEng}That's our style!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.40,0:04:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,托米·佩罗说\N{\rEng}Hey, Tommy Petros is thinking 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.33,0:04:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也想成为吸血派\N{\rEng}he might wanna be a vamp kid, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.65,0:04:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,托米·佩罗  他酷吗  \N{\rEng}Tommy Petros, is he cool? 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.43,0:04:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺酷的\N{\rEng}Yeah, he's cool enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.27,0:04:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好吧\N{\rEng}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.01,0:04:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然之间  你们这些追星族觉得\N{\rEng}So all of a sudden, you Justin and Britney wannabes
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.75,0:04:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,模仿我们很酷吗\N{\rEng}think it's cool to dress like us?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.79,0:04:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们按自己的想法穿 \N{\rEng}We dress the way our souls feel. 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.55,0:04:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是对黑暗的诠释\N{\rEng}To express the darkness, per se.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.03,0:04:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是迈克·麦考斯基吧\N{\rEng}Aren't you Mike McCalsky?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.30,0:04:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在是韦皮尔·麦考斯基\N{\rEng}That's Vampir McCalsky now.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.35,0:04:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们还是穿回\N{\rEng}You kids need to all go put your 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.40,0:04:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,香蕉共和国的衣服吧\N{\rEng}freaking Banana Republic clothes back on right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.10,0:04:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们同样黑暗  不比你们差\N{\rEng}Hey, we're just as dark as you guys. Maybe darker.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.91,0:04:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  你们抽烟吗\N{\rEng}Really. Do you guys even smoke?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.80,0:05:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不抽  抽烟对身体不好\N{\rEng}Of course not. Smoking's bad for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.85,0:05:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\rEng}Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.22,0:05:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我晕\N{\rEng}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.02,0:05:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们身上都是\N{\rEng}You know, you guys are really 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.12,0:05:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的消极能量\N{\rEng}giving off a negative human energy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.03,0:05:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们宁愿到别处去汲取\N{\rEng}We prefer to take our darkness somewhere else, per se.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.77,0:05:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  伪吸血鬼  去吧\N{\rEng}All right, Count Fagula. You go do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.22,0:05:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  我有事要说\N{\rEng}Mom! Mom, I gotta tell you something!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.09,0:05:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定不相信\N{\rEng}You're not gonna believe it!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.32,0:05:23.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不行  巴特斯\N{\rEng}Not now, Butters.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.18,0:05:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸在厨房等你谈话\N{\rEng}Your father wants to have a talk with you in the kitchen.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.37,0:05:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不太高兴\N{\rEng}He is not happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.24,0:05:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晕  我又做错什么了\N{\rEng}Oh, no. What I'd do this time?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.18,0:05:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赶紧过去\N{\rEng}You just march on in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.16,0:05:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神啊\N{\rEng}Oh, jeez.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.17,0:05:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了吗  巴特斯\N{\rEng}You see this, Butters?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.85,0:05:41.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我倒出来的一杯牛奶\N{\rEng}It's a glass of milk I poured for myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.92,0:05:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这个\N{\rEng}And you see this?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.56,0:05:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是汉堡包伴侣\N{\rEng}It's Hamburger Helper.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.13,0:05:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在告诉我  \N{\rEng}Now, would you mind telling me 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.87,0:05:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么汉堡包伴侣会在牛奶里\N{\rEng}what Hamburger Helper is doing in this glass of milk?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.30,0:05:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么汉堡包伴侣会在牛奶里  巴特斯\N{\rEng}Why is Hamburger Helper in a glass of milk, Butters?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.07,0:05:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  爸爸\N{\rEng}I have no idea, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.96,0:05:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉你为什么\N{\rEng}I'll tell you why!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.26,0:06:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食品柜一直是按字母顺序排列的\N{\rEng}Our pantry is always kept organized alphabetically.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.78,0:06:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但某人把汉堡包伴侣\N{\rEng}But somebody put the Hamburger Helper
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.38,0:06:07.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放到了雀巢速溶咖啡的位置\N{\rEng}where the Nestle Quick is supposed to go!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.92,0:06:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  爸爸\N{\rEng}I'm sorry, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.07,0:06:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最近精神不太好\N{\rEng}It's just I've been really preoccupied lately.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.09,0:06:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校里有些孩子 \N{\rEng}See, there's these kids at school--
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.21,0:06:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么凝聚一个家庭  巴特斯\N{\rEng}What keeps a family together, Butters?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.45,0:06:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个排放有序的食品柜\N{\rEng}A well-organized pantry.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.20,0:06:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得对\N{\rEng}That's right!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.23,0:06:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你老是把食物放错位置\N{\rEng}If you keep putting food back under the wrong letter,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.12,0:06:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情全会乱套\N{\rEng}it all goes wrong!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.90,0:06:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上把整个食品柜\N{\rEng}Now you will reorganize this entire pantry 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.31,0:06:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新排好\N{\rEng}and you will do it right.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.86,0:06:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  但是爸爸  听我说几句\N{\rEng}Okay, but Dad, you gotta listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.78,0:06:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校里的孩子开始变了\N{\rEng}Kids at school are starting to change.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.78,0:06:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不马上排好  就等着被禁足\N{\rEng}You do it right now or you're going to be grounded.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.51,0:06:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到了吗\N{\rEng}You got that?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.80,0:06:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  爸爸\N{\rEng}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.84,0:06:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\rEng}Jeez.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.88,0:06:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人愿意听我说\N{\rEng}Nobody will even listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.15,0:06:46.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像没人关心学校里是否有吸血鬼\N{\rEng}It's like nobody even cares that there's vampires at the school.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.42,0:06:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我努力想帮忙  却总是被责骂\N{\rEng}I try to help and all I ever do is get hollered at.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.05,0:06:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸血鬼就从来不会被责骂\N{\rEng}I'll bet vampires never get hollered at.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.80,0:06:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸血鬼总能随心所欲\N{\rEng}Vampires just get to do whatever they want.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.38,0:07:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当所有凡人安详入眠\N{\rEng}All mortals share a soft repose.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.61,0:07:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的灵魂在夜间苏醒\N{\rEng}My soul doth dreadful vigils keep,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.67,0:07:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡人无法想象的清醒\N{\rEng}more keen than which hell scarcely knows.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.73,0:07:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子在干吗\N{\rEng}What is that kid doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.69,0:07:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  巴特斯  你这是在干嘛\N{\rEng}Oh, Jesus. Oh, God. Butters, what are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.68,0:07:26.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫巴特斯\N{\rEng}I'm Butters.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.45,0:07:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\rEng}So?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.81,0:07:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暗夜的生灵  我在邪恶的黑夜中\N{\rEng}Oh, creatures of the night, I seek audience to engage with thee
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.58,0:07:35.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追寻你们\N{\rEng}in unholy darkness and thus do,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.75,0:07:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等待召唤\N{\rEng}and thus do unto your bidding.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.23,0:07:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.34,0:07:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想当吸血鬼\N{\rEng}I wanna be a vampire.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.17,0:07:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还不够酷\N{\rEng}You're not cool enough to be one of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.45,0:07:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\rEng}Yeah, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.64,0:07:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我觉得我能做个不错的吸血鬼  \N{\rEng}But... I think I would make a really good vampire if you just...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.45,0:07:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要给我一个机会\N{\rEng}just give me the opportunity.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.01,0:07:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会考虑的\N{\rEng}We'll think about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.27,0:07:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去食堂的售卖机给我们弄点汽水\N{\rEng}Go get us some sodas out of the pop machine in the commons.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.65,0:07:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命\N{\rEng}Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.58,0:08:02.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还要别的吗  -我想要点奇多\N{\rEng}- Yes, anything else? - I want some Cheetos.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.45,0:08:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汽水和奇多  遵命  马上就来\N{\rEng}Soda and Cheetos, yes! I'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.07,0:08:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,球跑哪去了\N{\rEng}Where'd it go?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.80,0:08:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到了吗\N{\rEng}You see where it went?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.89,0:08:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那群吸血鬼旁边\N{\rEng}Yeah, it's right over there by those vampire kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.53,0:08:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\rEng}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.91,0:08:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  喂\N{\rEng}Hey, hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.18,0:08:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是吸血鬼  我们是哥特\N{\rEng}We aren't vampire kids, we're freaking goth!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.75,0:08:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁鸟你  德拉库拉\N{\rEng}Whatever, Dracula.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.50,0:08:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有本事变成吸血蝙蝠\N{\rEng}Why don't you turn into a bat or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.21,0:08:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太衰了\N{\rEng}So lame.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.90,0:08:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太  衰  了\N{\rEng}So... lame.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.04,0:08:35.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  我可不想被看成\N{\rEng}You guys, I do not want to be grouped in
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.26,0:08:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻逼吸血派\N{\rEng}with douchy little vampire kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.89,0:08:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太衰了\N{\rEng}So lame.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.20,0:08:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  这里很酷吧\N{\rEng}See? Isn't it cool back here? 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.80,0:08:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既黑暗又孤寂\N{\rEng}It's all dark and isolated.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.12,0:08:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这地方很适合吸血鬼聚会\N{\rEng}This would be a great place for a vampire meeting!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.39,0:08:48.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚出我们的地盘  废球\N{\rEng}Get out of our space, you little twerps!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.97,0:08:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越来越多全优预科生变成了吸血鬼\N{\rEng}More preppy straight-A students turning into vampires.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.92,0:08:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这到底怎么回事\N{\rEng}What the hell is going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.35,0:09:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我按你们说的\N{\rEng}I've done what you've asked.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.06,0:09:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带了一打七喜汽水  还有樱桃软糖\N{\rEng}A case of Dr. Pepper and cherry Twizzlers.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.53,0:09:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些东西是给谁吃的\N{\rEng}Who are you gonna give this to?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.67,0:09:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸血鬼不是不食人间烟火吗\N{\rEng}I mean, vampires can't eat people food.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.10,0:09:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做得很好\N{\rEng}You have done well.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.31,0:09:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好加入我们了吗\N{\rEng}Are you ready to become one of us, per se?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.79,0:09:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想是吧\N{\rEng}Yeah, I guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.33,0:09:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定吗  \N{\rEng}Are you sure? 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.23,0:09:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦你加入了南方公园吸血鬼社团\N{\rEng}Because once you're in South Park Vampire Society,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.60,0:09:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就永远不得离开\N{\rEng}you can't ever leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.65,0:09:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我厌倦了任人教训\N{\rEng}Well, I'm sick of being pushed around.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.85,0:09:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸  还有学校里的同学\N{\rEng}By my dad, by kids at school.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.46,0:09:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你转化的时刻到了\N{\rEng}Then it is time for your transformation, per se.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.21,0:09:41.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始吧\N{\rEng}Let it begin!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.86,0:09:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边走  做好准备\N{\rEng}This way. Prepare thyself.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.35,0:10:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在只要喝下吸血鬼的血\N{\rEng}And now you shall drink vampire blood
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.51,0:10:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的转化即可完成\N{\rEng}and your transformation will be complete, per se.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.49,0:10:23.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝下它  汝之变形即完毕\N{\rEng}With this thy transformation is done!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.49,0:10:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真难喝\N{\rEng}That tastes awful!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.42,0:10:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仪式结束\N{\rEng}It is finished!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.72,0:10:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎你  巴特斯\N{\rEng}Welcome, Butters,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.86,0:10:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加入南方公园吸血鬼社团\N{\rEng}to the South Park Society of Vampires.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.45,0:10:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  巴特斯  知道几点了吗\N{\rEng}There you are, Butters! Do you know what time it is?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.90,0:10:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪了\N{\rEng}Where have you been?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.20,0:10:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  你头发怎么了\N{\rEng}Butters, what have you done to your hair?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.93,0:10:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  我们在跟你说话呢\N{\rEng}Hey! Butters, we are talking to you!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.59,0:10:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我解释清楚  臭小子\N{\rEng}Explain yourself, mister.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.93,0:11:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不必再对你做任何解释  父亲\N{\rEng}I no longer need to explain anything to you, father.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.23,0:11:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么回事  -够了\N{\rEng}- What on Earth... - That does it!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.30,0:11:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要禁足两周  听到了吗\N{\rEng}You are grounded for two weeks, you got that?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.21,0:11:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们囚不住我\N{\rEng}You can't ground me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.91,0:11:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我非生非死\N{\rEng}For I am neither living nor dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.10,0:11:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,囚不住的我  你们怎么禁足呢\N{\rEng}How can thy ground that which is ungroundable?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.87,0:11:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  我不知道你着了什么魔  \N{\rEng}All right. I don't know what's gotten into you, mister,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.90,0:11:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你必须\N{\rEng}but you're gonna...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.72,0:11:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯\N{\rEng}Butters!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.73,0:11:27.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要回房了\N{\rEng}I am going to my room now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.51,0:11:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要睡眠\N{\rEng}For I must slumber, per se.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.12,0:11:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们  我知道\N{\rEng}Now kids, I understand 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.64,0:11:40.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们很迷所谓的"吸血鬼"\N{\rEng}that you are very into this "vampire" thing,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.05,0:11:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我不希望情况变得失控\N{\rEng}but I don't want to see it get out of hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.23,0:11:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要知道\N{\rEng}You kids need to understand
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.81,0:11:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种新热潮吓到了某些同学\N{\rEng}that your new little fad is scary to some.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.66,0:11:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我晕\N{\rEng}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.22,0:11:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找错教训对象了\N{\rEng}You've got the wrong flippin' people!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.41,0:11:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是吸血鬼\N{\rEng}We aren't vampires.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.00,0:11:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你们不是真的吸血鬼\N{\rEng}I know that you aren't really vampires.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.33,0:12:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也很欣赏你们想变酷的热情\N{\rEng}And I appreciate that you want to be cool
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.46,0:12:03.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为吸血鬼确实是当下最"潮"的事物\N{\rEng}because vampires are the "in" thing right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.20,0:12:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是要赶时髦\N{\rEng}We aren't trying to be popular!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.78,0:12:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不要对新热潮\N{\rEng}But just make sure that this new little trend
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.75,0:12:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太过狂热\N{\rEng}doesn't become a distraction.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.26,0:12:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有几个  维多利亚校长  好么\N{\rEng}Here's a couple more, Principal Victoria, m'kay?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.18,0:12:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们惹事了吗\N{\rEng}Oh no, are we in trouble?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.04,0:12:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在告诉你们的朋友们\N{\rEng}I was just telling your friends about what I expect...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.71,0:12:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是朋友\N{\rEng}We aren't friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.46,0:12:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  女士\N{\rEng}Don't worry, ma'am.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.74,0:12:21.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我常对新下属说\N{\rEng}As I was just explaining to my new minions,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.02,0:12:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸血鬼其实是很有灵魂和深度的生灵\N{\rEng}vampires are actually very spiritual and deep beings, per se.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.33,0:12:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾利森·默茨也成吸血派啦\N{\rEng}Allison Mertz is a vampire kid, now?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.91,0:12:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还有完没完\N{\rEng}This thing isn't going to stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.97,0:12:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还是面对现实吧\N{\rEng}Let's just face it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.40,0:12:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们山寨了我们的风格\N{\rEng}They bogarted our style.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.02,0:12:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都以为我们想当垃圾吸血鬼\N{\rEng}Everyone's gonna think we're trying to be butthole vampires.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.70,0:12:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还是去盖普\N{\rEng}Now we might go to the frickin' Gap 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.69,0:12:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买普通衣服穿吧\N{\rEng}and buy normal clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.02,0:12:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少现在没人把我们当成吸血鬼了\N{\rEng}Well, at least nobody can refer to us as vampire kids now.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.48,0:12:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,球去了这边吗\N{\rEng}It went this way?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.92,0:12:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那个肥妞  大鼻子男\N{\rEng}Yeah, it's over there by the fat girl, the big nose kid,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.60,0:12:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小侏儒  还有麻子脸旁边\N{\rEng}the midget and the kid with pock marks on his face.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.76,0:13:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们又变成什么了\N{\rEng}So we're back to that, are we?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.89,0:13:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠\N{\rEng}Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.65,0:13:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱还是脱掉这身盖普装吧\N{\rEng}Let's get out of these freakin' Gap clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.80,0:13:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  埃里克\N{\rEng}Sorry, Eric.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.22,0:13:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在是吸血鬼 \N{\rEng}But I'm a vampire now, 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.91,0:13:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 必须吸人血存活\N{\rEng}and I can no longer survive on human food.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.99,0:13:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果必须牺牲一个人\N{\rEng}And if someone must die so that I can feed,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.07,0:13:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我选择了你\N{\rEng}I choose thee.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.79,0:13:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该吸哪边呢\N{\rEng}Wonder what side I'm supposed to do it on.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.52,0:13:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计哪边都一样\N{\rEng}Probably doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.48,0:13:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯\N{\rEng}Butters?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.53,0:13:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯\N{\rEng}Butters!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.38,0:13:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我办不到\N{\rEng}I can't do it!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.09,0:13:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我办不到\N{\rEng}I can't do it!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.79,0:13:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  太恶心了  \N{\rEng}Dude, gross. 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.83,0:13:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞得我满脖子口水  妈妈\N{\rEng}You got spit all over my neck. Mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.41,0:13:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯刚亲了我的脖子  \N{\rEng}Butters just gave me a hickey! 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.10,0:13:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太饿了\N{\rEng}I'm so hungry,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.83,0:13:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但一想起上次喝的血的味道\N{\rEng}but just remembering how that blood tasted before...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.63,0:13:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粘腻的番茄味\N{\rEng}Blood is all clammy and tomatoey.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.52,0:14:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我想\N{\rEng}It makes me want to...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.66,0:14:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哥们  -没事吧  宝贝\N{\rEng}- Dude!  - Are you all right, sweetie?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.95,0:14:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事\N{\rEng}What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.69,0:14:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  显然巴特斯是个同志\N{\rEng}Well, Mom, apparently, Butters is gay,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.69,0:14:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现我很有魅力\N{\rEng}finds me very attractive
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.68,0:14:17.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混淆了他的性取向\N{\rEng}and confused about his sexual identity.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.66,0:14:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是吐了一地\N{\rEng}Puked up all over my floor.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.04,0:14:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  -没错\N{\rEng}- Oh, dear. - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.18,0:14:27.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我去自助餐厅  \N{\rEng}I walked into the cafeteria today, 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.29,0:14:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽贝卡·米勒和菲利普·拉斯特\N{\rEng}Rebeca Miller and Phillip Rust
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.29,0:14:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿得像吸血鬼一样  \N{\rEng}were dressed like vampires 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.49,0:14:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和足球队的4个孩子一起喝蛤蜊茄汁\N{\rEng}drinking clamato juice with four kids from the football team.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.72,0:14:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\rEng}Jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.04,0:14:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸血派的人好像日益增多了\N{\rEng}It's like there's more vampire kids every freakin' day.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.46,0:14:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样  \N{\rEng}Why is this happening? 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.47,0:14:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么是现在\N{\rEng}I mean, why now?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.21,0:14:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管为什么\N{\rEng}Doesn't matter why.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.48,0:14:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个学校很快就会变成\N{\rEng}Pretty soon the whole school
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.95,0:14:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一堆吸血鬼追随者的			\N{\rEng}is going to be an endless hive of conformist,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.79,0:14:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逍遥老巢\N{\rEng}happy-go-lucky vampire wannabes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.59,0:14:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是迈克·麦考斯基那个预科生带的头\N{\rEng}It seems like that preppy Mike McCalsky kid started all this.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.25,0:14:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解铃还需系铃人\N{\rEng}Maybe he's the way to stopping it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.46,0:14:55.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思\N{\rEng}What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.87,0:14:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是\N{\rEng}I mean,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.98,0:14:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要让吸血鬼变回常人\N{\rEng}what do you do when you want to change
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.24,0:15:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会怎么做\N{\rEng}vampires back to normal?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.49,0:15:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摆平领头的吸血鬼\N{\rEng}You get rid of the head vampire.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.43,0:15:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈知道你开走了她的车吗\N{\rEng}Does your mom know you took her car?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.77,0:15:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我在乎吗\N{\rEng}Do I care?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.25,0:15:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 差不多了\N{\rEng}Alright, this is probably good enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.23,0:15:19.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠边停\N{\rEng}Yeah, pull over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.26,0:15:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你们了  你们想干什么\N{\rEng}Please! What do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.84,0:15:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放我走\N{\rEng}Let me go!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.71,0:15:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么处置他\N{\rEng}What should we do with him?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.64,0:15:33.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要是吸血鬼\N{\rEng}Well, if he's a vampire,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.06,0:15:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就要用木桩刺穿他的心脏\N{\rEng}I guess we should drive a stake through his heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.70,0:15:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不是吸血鬼\N{\rEng}No, I'm not a vampire.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.07,0:15:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是吸血鬼\N{\rEng}I'm not a vampire!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.44,0:15:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你说什么  -我不是真的吸血鬼\N{\rEng}- What's that? - I'm not really a vampire!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.06,0:15:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是真的吸血鬼\N{\rEng}You're not really a vampire?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.99,0:15:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\rEng}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.05,0:15:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太让我震惊了\N{\rEng}I'm so freaking shocked.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.56,0:15:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是有合适的包装箱\N{\rEng}If we get the right packaging,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.05,0:15:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能把他联邦快递得远远的\N{\rEng}we can just FedEx him somewhere far away.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.61,0:15:56.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他送到特兰西瓦尼亚怎么样\N{\rEng}How about we send him to Transylvania?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.15,0:15:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许有一天\N{\rEng}He'd probably see it
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.44,0:15:59.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会把这件事\N{\rEng}as something to brag about some day 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.25,0:16:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当成和其他吸血鬼吹牛的资本\N{\rEng}to his little vampire buddies.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.60,0:16:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要送就要把他送到\N{\rEng}If we're gonna send him somewhere,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.34,0:16:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世上最恐怖最凄惨的地方\N{\rEng}it should be the most horrible, most miserable place on Earth.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.81,0:16:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯科特斯德\N{\rEng}Scottsdale!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.43,0:16:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  \N{\rEng}Butters, 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.28,0:16:18.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚接到卡特曼太太的电话\N{\rEng}we just got a call from Mrs. Cartman!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.39,0:16:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯\N{\rEng}Butters?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.55,0:16:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信  他把门反锁了\N{\rEng}Unbelievable! He's locked the door!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.05,0:16:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  我是你老子\N{\rEng}Butters! This is your father!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.82,0:16:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我说清楚  \N{\rEng}Explain why you snuck into 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.71,0:16:27.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么溜进男孩子的卧室\N{\rEng}another boy's bedroom
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.98,0:16:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还亲他的脖子\N{\rEng}and gave him a hickey!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.99,0:16:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯\N{\rEng}Butters?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.37,0:16:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  马上给我开门\N{\rEng}Butters, you will open this door right now!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.80,0:16:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对自己做了什么\N{\rEng}What have I done to myself?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.01,0:16:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早该清楚\N{\rEng}I should have known 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.22,0:16:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己没有当吸血鬼的胃\N{\rEng}I wouldn't have the stomach to be a vampire.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.09,0:16:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太饿了\N{\rEng}I'm so hungry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.72,0:16:46.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  限你五秒内开门\N{\rEng}Butters, you have five seconds to unlock this door.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.72,0:16:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一\N{\rEng}One.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.03,0:16:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二\N{\rEng}Two.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.56,0:17:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯\N{\rEng}Butters?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.74,0:17:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸\N{\rEng}Hey, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.94,0:17:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  \N{\rEng}Butters, 
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.71,0:17:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今晚是不是对一个同学无礼了\N{\rEng}did you get gay with one of your schoolmates tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.25,0:17:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要进食\N{\rEng}I have to eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.50,0:17:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我办不到 \N{\rEng}But I can't do it. 
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.52,0:17:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 我越来越虚弱了\N{\rEng}I'm getting weak.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.18,0:17:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  你给我听好\N{\rEng}All right. Now you listen and you listen good.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.05,0:17:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是再这样疯疯癫癫的  \N{\rEng}Until you stop behaving this way, 
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.52,0:17:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就永远别想离开这个房间\N{\rEng}you are not going the leave this room!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.73,0:17:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听懂了吗\N{\rEng}Do you understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.97,0:17:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道要做什么\N{\rEng}I know now what I have to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.98,0:17:35.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史蒂芬  我们家儿子是怎么了\N{\rEng}Steven, what has happened to our boy?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.35,0:17:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他变成了另一种东西  琳达\N{\rEng}He's become something, Linda.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.96,0:17:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一种\N{\rEng}Something that...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.53,0:17:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们关不住的东西\N{\rEng}we cannot ground.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.96,0:17:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是不明白\N{\rEng}I just don't get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.23,0:17:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把吸血派老大送到了斯科特斯德\N{\rEng}We sent the head vampire kid to Scottsdale.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.93,0:17:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还是有更多孩子打扮成吸血鬼\N{\rEng}But still more and more kids are dressing up like vampires.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.79,0:18:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们肯定搞错原因了\N{\rEng}It must not have been what was causing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.02,0:18:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原因肯定在别处\N{\rEng}It must be something else.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.54,0:18:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们到底点不点餐\N{\rEng}Hey, you kids are gonna order any food
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.06,0:18:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道又打算一晚上喝咖啡吗\N{\rEng}or just sit there and drink coffee all night, again?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.16,0:18:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别烦我们\N{\rEng}Leave us alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.81,0:18:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伺候你们几个哥特派已经够糟糕了\N{\rEng}Bad enough if I always get stuck with you goth kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.60,0:18:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在整个区都是哥特派\N{\rEng}Now I've got goth kids in my entire section.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.67,0:18:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不是哥特派  他们是吸血派\N{\rEng}They aren't goth, they are douchy little vampire kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.15,0:18:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看不出有啥区别\N{\rEng}Looks the same to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.75,0:18:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们肯定不喝咖啡\N{\rEng}I bet they aren't even drinking coffee.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.14,0:18:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说自己年纪太小  不能喝咖啡因\N{\rEng}No, they said they were too young to drink caffeine,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.45,0:18:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以喝橙汁\N{\rEng}so they're having an orange juice.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.65,0:18:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去告诉他们\N{\rEng}Let's go over there
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.88,0:18:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别想走我们的路线\N{\rEng}and tell them they're not taking their legend from us too.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.25,0:18:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了\N{\rEng}Forget it!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.31,0:18:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都结束了\N{\rEng}It's over, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.75,0:18:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们人太多了  我们没法阻止\N{\rEng}There's too many of them now. We can't stop them.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.80,0:18:42.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受事实吧\N{\rEng}Let's just face it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.24,0:18:44.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸血派赢了\N{\rEng}The freakin' vampires beat us.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.99,0:18:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未必\N{\rEng}Maybe not.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.79,0:18:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们刚才说想摆平吸血派吗\N{\rEng}Did you say you're trying to get rid of the vampires?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.56,0:18:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想帮你们\N{\rEng}I want to help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.20,0:18:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚开  傻逼\N{\rEng}Get away, douchebag.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.82,0:18:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传说中  如果吸血鬼的巢穴被摧毁\N{\rEng}Some legends say that if you destroy the vampire's lair,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.78,0:19:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就会重新转变成人\N{\rEng}the vampires go back to being human again.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.08,0:19:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啥意思\N{\rEng}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.59,0:19:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能带你们\N{\rEng}I can take you
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.90,0:19:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吸血鬼转化的地方\N{\rEng}to the place where kids are being transformed into vampires.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.88,0:19:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新热潮  这家店什么时候开的\N{\rEng}Hot Topic? When did this open?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.56,0:19:19.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两周前  以前是香蕉共和国\N{\rEng}Two weeks ago. It used to be a Banana Republic.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.12,0:19:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难怪\N{\rEng}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.18,0:19:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的新热潮  原来如此\N{\rEng}Freaking Hot Topic. That explains everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.10,0:19:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们怎么没想到呢\N{\rEng}How did we not figure that out?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.73,0:19:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是镇上开了家新热潮\N{\rEng}Of course a new Hot Topic must have come to town. Duh.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.48,0:19:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家应该都知道该怎么做了吧\N{\rEng}Well, I think we all know what has to be done.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.65,0:19:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们动手吧\N{\rEng}Let's get to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.58,0:19:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们到底在干吗\N{\rEng}Hey, what the hell are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.37,0:19:53.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好还是离开这里\N{\rEng}You should probably get out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.11,0:20:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们搞什么名堂  -他们在做个了结\N{\rEng}- What the hell are they doing? - They're putting an end to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.93,0:20:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  爸爸\N{\rEng}Mom! Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.63,0:20:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我又变回来了  -什么\N{\rEng}- I've changed back! - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.03,0:20:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥特派果然烧了新热潮\N{\rEng}Goth kids burnt down the Hot Topic and sure enough!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.71,0:20:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一烧完我就吃了条热狗  \N{\rEng}Soon as they did, I tried eating a hot dog 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.93,0:20:27.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉好极了\N{\rEng}and it tasted good!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.71,0:20:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咬热狗时  我的尖牙也掉了\N{\rEng}My vampire teeth even fell out when I bit into it!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.38,0:20:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又变回人了\N{\rEng}I'm human again!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.89,0:20:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们根本听不懂你在说什么  巴特斯\N{\rEng}We have no idea what you're talking about, Butters,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.37,0:20:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们很高兴你回来了\N{\rEng}but we're glad you're home!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.82,0:20:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就对了  儿子\N{\rEng}That's right, son.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.83,0:20:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在只关心一件事\N{\rEng}There's only one thing I care about.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.75,0:20:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事  爸爸\N{\rEng}What's that, Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.00,0:20:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能告诉我\N{\rEng}Well, would you mind telling me 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.25,0:20:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我的咖啡里有米面吗\N{\rEng}why there is rice-a-roni in my coffee?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.36,0:20:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特斯  你被禁足了\N{\rEng}Butters, you are grounded!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.35,0:20:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼\N{\rEng}Ah, dangit!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.38,0:20:53.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事了  琳达\N{\rEng}It worked, Linda.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.21,0:20:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的儿子又能被禁足了\N{\rEng}Our son is groundable once more.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.21,0:21:01.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同学们 \N{\rEng}Fellow students, 
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.12,0:21:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 过去几周出现了很多混乱\N{\rEng}over the past week there's been a lot of confusion
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.98,0:21:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此我们把大家召集在一起\N{\rEng}and so we have asked for this assembly
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.88,0:21:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声明哥特派和吸血派间的差异\N{\rEng}to clarify the difference between goth kids and vampire kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.34,0:21:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请大家务必明确\N{\rEng}Let us make it abundantly clear...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.64,0:21:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你厌世  讨厌阳光  \N{\rEng}If you hate life, truly hate the sun, 
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.77,0:21:16.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想吸烟和喝咖啡\N{\rEng}and need to smoke and drink coffee,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.12,0:21:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是哥特派\N{\rEng}you are goth.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.15,0:21:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你只因好玩而穿黑装\N{\rEng}If, however, you like dressing in black because it's fun,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.17,0:21:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在脸上贴亮片  崇拜超能力\N{\rEng}enjoy putting sparkles on your cheeks and following the occult
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.33,0:21:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却不敢接触对健康有害的东西\N{\rEng}while avoiding things that are bad for your health,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.66,0:21:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就是一个\N{\rEng}then you are most likely 
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.39,0:21:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻逼吸血鬼粉丝\N{\rEng}a douchebag vampire-wannabe boner.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.55,0:21:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为任何把自己当成吸血鬼的人\N{\rEng}Because anybody who thinks they're actually a vampire
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.25,0:21:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都他妈是智障\N{\rEng}is freaking retarded.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.93,0:21:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日死你们\N{\rEng}Fuck all of you.
